[
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is a good salary for an Indian software engineer (MCA) working abroad?",
        "answer": "The salary for an Indian software engineer (MCA) working abroad can vary widely depending on a number of factors such as the country of employment, the company they work for, their level of experience, and the specific skills they bring to the job. However, in general, a good salary for an Indian software engineer (MCA) working abroad would be one that is competitive with the market rate for their position and experience level in the country they are working in.\n\nAccording to some reports, the average salary for an Indian software engineer (MCA) working in the United States can range from $80,000 to $120,000 per year depending on the location and the specific industry. In Europe, the average salary for an Indian software engineer (MCA) can range from €35,000 to €55,000 per year depending on the country and industry. However, it's important to keep in mind that these figures are just averages and can vary depending on many factors.\n\nUltimately, a good salary for an Indian software engineer (MCA) working abroad is one that is competitive, fair, and allows them to live comfortably and save for the future.",
        "name": "ADITYA Kumar",
        "views": "71 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-a-good-salary-for-an-Indian-software-engineer-MCA-working-abroad",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/antiwork",
        "author": "u/WinterSolgia",
        "question": "Application Developer with 4+ years experience and Computer Science Bachelor's Degree for $18/hr",
        "upvotes": "5",
        "comment": "5",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/antiwork/comments/xdkzg6/application_developer_with_4_years_experience_and/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What is the full form of MCA?",
        "answer": "MCA stands for \"Master of Computer Applications\".",
        "name": "Kajal Kumari",
        "views": "109 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-ONLEI-Technologies-Institute-the-best-or-not-for-summer-internship-training",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/PortugalExpats",
        "author": "u/summer2205",
        "question": "Master’s Degree Application in Portugal",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "6",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/PortugalExpats/comments/12524pv/masters_degree_application_in_portugal/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/careerguidance",
        "author": "u/DustLiving2085",
        "question": "on what should I focus more: masters or upskilling?",
        "upvotes": "5",
        "comment": "4",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/careerguidance/comments/10f1cnm/on_what_should_i_focus_more_masters_or_upskilling/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/contaicollegeoflearn",
        "author": "u/contaicollegeoflearn",
        "question": "Best BCA colleges in Purba Medinipur | Bachelor in Computer Application",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/contaicollegeoflearn/comments/ly8ezk/best_bca_colleges_in_purba_medinipur_bachelor_in/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which is best university for distance MCA?",
        "answer": "Masters of computer application (MCA) is one the most popular courses among the students who want to work as software developers and IT field. Students who want to learn computer languages can choose MCA. The syllabus and subjects are similar to the regular Masters of computer application (MCA).\n\nDistant education is best during these times as the Covid -19 pandemic situation is rising again.\n\nThere are various advantages of distance education such as:-\n\n· You will save your traveling time and can invest that time in extracurricular activities or your hobbies.\n\n· You will save traveling expenses that you can invest in other things and good returns on your savings.\n\nEvery student is supposed to dedicate some time to their passion and hobbies, but a MCA degree is equally essential. Solution is ONLINE MASTERS OF COMPUTER APPLICATION, student can access the lectures from wherever they want, all they need is access to internet and a device.\n\nMany Universities provide Masters of computer application (MCA) online, one such University is Manav Rachna International Institute of Research and Studies. Faculty of Manav Rachna is very experienced and they give practical knowledge for clearing the concepts.\n\nYou can check the Manav Rachna International Institute of Research and Studies Online MCA program from the given link below:-\n\nCentre for Distance and Online Education\nHome 1 June 19, 2021 2023-03-09 12:24 Home 1\nhttps://manavrachnaonline.com/mca/?utm_source=stu&utm_medium=promo&utm_campaign=28",
        "name": "Nishant Jawa",
        "views": "2.2K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-MCA-admission-available-in-Bangalore",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/technepal",
        "author": "u/DarkMagic2000",
        "question": "Can anyone tell me how to learn CSS and JS more effectively?",
        "upvotes": "2",
        "comment": "10",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/technepal/comments/111d9ou/can_anyone_tell_me_how_to_learn_css_and_js_more/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Does MIT-WPU offer an MCA program?",
        "answer": "Yes, MIT-WPU (MIT World Peace University) offers an MCA (Master of Computer Applications) program.\n\nThe MCA program at MIT-WPU is a three-year postgraduate program that aims to provide students with advanced knowledge and skills in computer applications. The program covers topics such as software engineering, programming languages, database management, computer networks, and web technologies, among others.\n\nTo be eligible for the MCA program at MIT-WPU, candidates should have a bachelor's degree in any discipline with Mathematics as a subject at the 10+2 or undergraduate level. Admissions to the program are usually based on the candidate's performance in an entrance exam and an interview conducted by the university.",
        "name": "Adnan Sohail",
        "views": "58 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-do-you-do-when-a-dementia-patient-refuses-to-shower",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are the job opportunities after completing an MCA degree?",
        "answer": "The Master of Computer Applications (MCA) degree is a postgraduate program that provides students with advanced knowledge and skills in various areas of computer applications. Graduates of an MCA program have a wide range of job opportunities available to them.\n\nHere are some of the job opportunities that graduates of an MCA program may pursue:\n\nSoftware Engineer/Developer: MCA graduates can work as software engineers or developers for IT companies. They can work on developing software applications, testing software, and maintaining software systems.\nWeb Developer: MCA graduates can also work as web developers, creating and maintaining websites and web applications for companies.\nDatabase Administrator: MCA graduates can work as database administrators, managing and maintaining the databases of organizations.\nSystem Analyst: MCA graduates can work as system analysts, analyzing the computer systems of organizations and recommending improvements.\nIT Consultant: MCA graduates can also work as IT consultants, providing advice and guidance on IT-related issues to organizations.\nTechnical Writer: MCA graduates can work as technical writers, creating user manuals, technical documentation, and other materials related to IT products and services.\nProject Manager: MCA graduates can also work as project managers, overseeing the development and implementation of IT projects.\nNetwork Administrator: MCA graduates can work as network administrators, managing and maintaining computer networks for organizations.\nCybersecurity Analyst: MCA graduates can work as cybersecurity analysts, protecting the computer systems of organizations from cyber attacks and security threats.\nMobile Application Developer: MCA graduates can work as mobile application developers, designing and developing mobile apps for various platforms like Android and iOS.\nData Scientist: MCA graduates with a strong background in mathematics and statistics can work as data scientists, analyzing and interpreting complex data sets to identify insights and trends.\nArtificial Intelligence/Machine Learning Engineer: MCA graduates can work as AI/ML engineers, developing and implementing AI/ML solutions for organizations.\nSoftware Quality Assurance (QA) Engineer: MCA graduates can work as software QA engineers, ensuring that software products meet quality standards and perform as expected.\nCloud Architect: MCA graduates can work as cloud architects, designing and implementing cloud-based solutions for organizations.\nTechnical Support Engineer: MCA graduates can work as technical support engineers, providing support to customers and resolving technical issues related to software products and services.",
        "name": "Aniket Sharma",
        "views": "14 views",
        "link": "https://collegeforum.quora.com/What-are-the-job-opportunities-after-completing-an-MCA-degree-1",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/uvic",
        "author": "u/admissionguru1",
        "question": "Question Regarding my application status , I applied for masters in computer science and few days ago i saw the status as recommended by department, not sure what this as it wasn't in the predefined statuses , Can anybody help clear my doubt ?",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "9",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/uvic/comments/txvwjt/question_regarding_my_application_status_i/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/tnvisa",
        "author": "u/Intrepid_Arrival_166",
        "question": "My bachelor is in science and master is in computer applications , I am working as cloud engineer from last 6-7 years, do you guys think I can get the TN status once I get the job in IT in US ?",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "2",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/tnvisa/comments/10sa6xc/my_bachelor_is_in_science_and_master_is_in/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/AskReddit",
        "author": "u/doktaAce",
        "question": "Which fully funded Masters in Computer Science programs that are open right now for applications?",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "1",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/12ce3ym/which_fully_funded_masters_in_computer_science/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is the full form of BBA and BCA? What is the difference between them?",
        "answer": "The full form of BBA is Bachelor of Business Administration.\n\nThe BBA programme serves as a foundation for a wide range of job opportunities in a variety of industries, including administration, education, marketing, sales, finance and banking.\n\nThe full form of BCA is Bachelors in Computer Application. BCA is a three-year degree course for people who wish to dive into the world of programming language. BCA is the most popular option for starting a professional life in information technology.",
        "name": "Sumitra Mukerji",
        "views": "9 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-full-form-of-BBA-and-BCA-What-is-the-difference-between-them",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What are the best government colleges for an MCA in Delhi?",
        "answer": "Hii!\n\nThese are 4 the Best Govt. Universities for doing MCA in Delhi:-\n\nAmbedkar Institute of Technology\n\nIGNOU - Indira Gandhi National Open University\n\nJMI-Jamia Millia Islamia\n\nJNU-Jawaharlal Nehru University\n\nI hope this will help you.",
        "name": "Minjul",
        "views": "384 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-college-in-Chennai-for-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Can I do an MCA from NIT after a BA?",
        "answer": "Yes, you can pursue an MCA (Master of Computer Applications) degree from NIT (National Institute of Technology) after completing a BA (Bachelor of Arts) degree. However, you need to meet the eligibility criteria set by the respective NIT.\n\nThe eligibility criteria for an MCA program at NITs typically include a bachelor's degree in any discipline with Mathematics as a subject at the 10+2 or graduation level, along with a minimum percentage of marks. Some NITs may also require candidates to have a valid score in an entrance exam like NIMCET (NIT MCA Common Entrance Test).\n\nTherefore, if you have completed a BA degree with Mathematics as a subject at the 10+2 or graduation level and meet the minimum percentage of marks and other eligibility criteria set by the NIT of your choice, you can apply for an MCA program.",
        "name": "Eduxprts",
        "views": "12 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-do-an-MCA-from-NIT-after-a-BA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What is it that Remainers find so irresistible about the EU that they are in favour of UK Laws being made by people who aren’t elected in this country, don’t live in this country and are utterly unaccountable to the people of this country?",
        "answer": "This “Laws made by Johnny Foreigner” schtick is such a load of cobblers (as Albert Steptoe might have said). Many of the statues adopted by the EU had their origins in the UK; for example the guidelines adopted for pharmaceutical manufacturers in EUDRALEX (The European Drug Regulatory Agency Lexicon) where pretty much a wholesale “lift & shift” of the UK “Orange Guide”, originally published by the MCA, now the MHRA. The EU adopted it because it was good, and they listened. And so it was with many other statutory instruments, they were as much ours as anyone else’s. Now we have no influence on coming EU laws that we may have to align with (because no one will deal with us if we don’t), but which may not be in out greater interests. It’s always better to be inside the tent, pissing out, than outside the tent, pissing in…",
        "name": "Arthur Montague",
        "views": "5.5K views",
        "link": "https://itcompaniesemployees.quora.com/I-have-no-work-experience-in-the-IT-sector-I-m-just-pursuing-my-MCA-from-a-B-category-college-My-age-is-41-now-Can-I",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/dataanalysis",
        "author": "u/Boring_Success_1656",
        "question": "I am an international job applicant and just completed my Masters here in the US. I have an MSc in engineering management and a bachelors in Computer science. I know python, sql, tableau And advanced excel. Have applied to around 400 jobs by now, got rejected. I don’t know what to do. Please help.",
        "upvotes": "17",
        "comment": "22",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/dataanalysis/comments/omf0x8/i_am_an_international_job_applicant_and_just/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is the future scope of BCA?",
        "answer": "Hello there,\n\nAfter completing your BCA, you are eligible for various entry-level jobs in the IT sector. You can also go for higher studies and pursue an MCA, which will open even more doors to success for you. The BCA degree is an efficient enabler that sets you up for a bright career in terms of jobs.\n\nIf you need any kind of assistance regarding admission feel free to contact through Whatsapp. (Link is in bio)\n\nHappy Learning……….",
        "name": "Suraj Late",
        "views": "72 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-future-scope-of-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "I am a 12th student and aspire to drew carrier in IT field.Does BCA with specialisations a better carrier degree. Does it have job opportunities?i am confused about what to do.. If I choose BCA with big fees.. At last i end in nothing🤧.. So many questions around.. Anyone can help me..?? Any BCA graduates with secure job here?? I wish to devolop my skill in programming!!",
        "answer": "BCA gives you very less opportunities in IT comparing to BE & BTech, If you wanted to do Bca then i will suggest you to do MCA after that, Since most of the companies offers more opportunities to MCA grads.",
        "name": "Roobesh P",
        "views": "1K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-better-MCA-or-MSc-Computer-Science-from-a-private-college",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/avviareeducation12",
        "author": "u/avviareeducation12",
        "question": "Best College for BCA Noida",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/avviareeducation12/comments/11jsg7e/best_college_for_bca_noida/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What are the benefits of doing an MCA after graduation if you want to be a software developer?",
        "answer": "Why MCA?\n\nWhat is an MCA anyway?",
        "name": "Kurt Guntheroth",
        "views": "704 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-the-Venkatapathy-manpower-consultancy-fake-or-real",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/AngelaKrist22",
        "author": "u/AngelaKrist22",
        "question": "The Edge of an MCA: Advantages of Pursuing a Master's in Computer Applications",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/AngelaKrist22/comments/11nleuf/the_edge_of_an_mca_advantages_of_pursuing_a/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/Adventurous-Band5267",
        "author": "u/Disastrous-Stick-329",
        "question": "MCA full form: Subjects, Career, Top Colleges in India, Entrance Exam, Admission Process, Salary, Job Scope.",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/Adventurous-Band5267/comments/w3f9gx/mca_full_form_subjects_career_top_colleges_in/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/asbnoida",
        "author": "u/KisekiKusanagi",
        "question": "The Most Important Skills for BCA Aspirants!",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/asbnoida/comments/wgovds/the_most_important_skills_for_bca_aspirants/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What is the difference between a Master's in Computer Science (MS) and a Master of Computer Application (MCA)? I have pursued a a Bachelor of Computer Application (BCA) this year, which degree should I opt for now?",
        "answer": "There are a few key differences between a Masters in Computer Science (MS) and a Master of Computer Application (MCA).\n\nFirstly, an MS focuses more on the theoretical aspects of computer science, while an MCA emphasizes practical applications.\n\nSecondly, an MS typically takes two years to complete, while an MCA can be finished in as little as 18 months.\n\nFinally, the job prospects for graduates with an MS tend to be better than those with an MCA.\n\nSo if you're looking to further your career in computer science, pursuing an MS would be the best option.",
        "name": "April Grant",
        "views": "589 views",
        "link": "https://itcompaniesemployees.quora.com/What-should-I-do-if-I-have-a-Capgemini-job-2-years-bond-or-should-I-go-for-an-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/saryuun12",
        "author": "u/blackapple56",
        "question": "Best BCA college in Dehradun| Bachelor of Computer Application",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/saryuun12/comments/12bayrc/best_bca_college_in_dehradun_bachelor_of_computer/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Which is best to do, an online MCA or an offline MCA?",
        "answer": "In my opinion, online MCA is the better option. All we need to do is choose the right place. Online MCA proves flexible; it offers flexibility to study at your own pace and time, making it a convenient option for those with other responsibilities or commitments. It makes a variety of job options available. An online MCA has many benefits, including: 1. Saves time: Taking a standard degree program can be physically and mentally exhausting, and traveling to and from the university takes a lot of time. Additionally, travel time may reduce productivity at work and in the classroom. However, one can study at their own convenience and pace online with online learning, and they can regularly access recorded sessions that are still accessible long after the program has ended. 2. Saves money: Most online programs are less expensive while retaining better quality than conventional offline programs. 3. Reputation/credibility: MCA specialties are only offered by a few universities that have received various levels of accreditation, including Amity University, LPU Online, and Manipal University. I was a student of the LPU online MCA course, and I must say, all those who are planning to do MCA online should grab the opportunity here at this university. This university provides all that one needs, from the top-notch curriculum, professors, interactive features, placement and other career support, and mentorship for personalized learning to the best LMS.",
        "name": "Sumaya Sofi",
        "views": "95 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-best-to-do-an-online-MCA-or-an-offline-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "How can I get admission for a BCA at Lovely Professional University?",
        "answer": "Let me tell you admission procedure here in LPU :\n\nSteps of taking admission Step 1 - Signup\n\nRegister onto LPUADMIT with basic details (Name, Email ID, Mobile No., State, Gender and Password). Your email id will act as your username for the portal and password will be set by you while registering on the portal.\n\nYou will get a mail on your registered email id regarding this.\n\nLogin to the LPUADMIT with already created username/ password\n\nStep 2 - Application for Admission\n\nRecent Photograph\n\nDate of Birth proof (Matric certificate, Aadhaar card)\n\nQualifying exam Certificate/ Marksheet. Also, if the applicant is claiming scholarship on the basis of\n\nStep 3- Apply LPUNEST (for Scholarship)\n\nLPUNEST is an online test for scholarship. Student can avail huge scholarship based on performance in this test.\n\nDeposit the test fee:\n\nCost of Application form and Soft copy of LPUNEST Kit is ₹1000 (for Boys) and ₹500 (for Girls).\n\nCost of Application form and Printed LPUNEST Kit is ₹1500 (for Boys) and ₹1000 (for Girls).\n\nFill the test application form.\n\nSTEP 4- Book the Exam Slot and Appear\n\nBook the slot (preferred venue, date and time) to appear in the LPUNEST Exam.\n\nAppear and qualify the exam.\n\nPerform STEP 2 in case admission is not taken already.",
        "name": "Ria Agnihotri",
        "views": "251 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-get-admission-for-a-BCA-at-Lovely-Professional-University",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Does MIT-WPU offer an MCA program?",
        "answer": "Yes, MIT-WPU (MIT World Peace University) offers an MCA (Master of Computer Applications) program.\n\nThe MCA program at MIT-WPU is a three-year postgraduate program that aims to provide students with advanced knowledge and skills in computer applications. The program covers topics such as software engineering, programming languages, database management, computer networks, and web technologies, among others.\n\nTo be eligible for the MCA program at MIT-WPU, candidates should have a bachelor's degree in any discipline with Mathematics as a subject at the 10+2 or undergraduate level. Admissions to the program are usually based on the candidate's performance in an entrance exam and an interview conducted by the university.",
        "name": "Adnan Sohail",
        "views": "58 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Does-MIT-WPU-offer-an-MCA-program",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/CharteredAccountants",
        "author": "u/walkerF27",
        "question": "MCA(Masters in Computer Application) along with CA?",
        "upvotes": "9",
        "comment": "10",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/CharteredAccountants/comments/vn77in/mcamasters_in_computer_application_along_with_ca/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "How good is KR Mangalam University for an MCA?",
        "answer": "K.R.Mangalam University focuses on honing the skills of MCA students in computer applications. The university provides fully-equipped computer labs for the advantage of practical learning. K.R.Mangalam University gives a chance to avail stipend during their course period based on the student's marks percentage scored during their graduation. K.R.Mangalam offers you placements from reputed companies. the university has skilled and qualified faculties. In any case of financial problems, the university provides you with financial assistance.",
        "name": "Mohit Malik",
        "views": "2.1K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-bands-came-to-regret-having-kicked-a-member-out-of-the-band",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are the benefits of doing an MCA from Delhi or Mumbai?",
        "answer": "MCA stands for Master of Computer Applications, which is a postgraduate program in the field of computer applications. Some benefits of doing an MCA from Delhi or Mumbai include:\n\nTop-tier institutions: Both Delhi and Mumbai have some of the best MCA colleges in the country, which offer high-quality education and training in the field of computer applications.\nIndustry exposure: Both cities have a thriving IT industry, with many software development firms and multinational corporations having their offices there. This provides ample opportunities for students to gain industry exposure and practical experience.\nJob opportunities: The IT industry in Delhi and Mumbai is growing rapidly, and there is a high demand for skilled professionals in this field. Graduates with an MCA degree from a reputed institution in these cities are likely to find lucrative job opportunities in the IT sector.\nNetworking opportunities: Delhi and Mumbai are both major hubs for business and commerce in India, and offer numerous networking opportunities for students and professionals in the IT industry.\n\nThe cost of doing an MCA program in Delhi or Mumbai varies depending on the institution and the course duration. On average, the course fee ranges from INR 1 lakh to INR 4 lakhs per year.",
        "name": "Tech Dhaval",
        "views": "5 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-benefits-of-doing-an-MCA-from-Delhi-or-Mumbai",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are the eligibility criteria for pursuing an M.Tech after a BCA?",
        "answer": "The eligibility criteria for pursuing M.Tech after BCA varies from university to university. Generally, a candidate should have a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science or a related field with a minimum of 50% marks (or equivalent CGPA) from a recognized university. Some universities may also require candidates to have a valid GATE score.",
        "name": "Eit Faridabad",
        "views": "17 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-eligibility-criteria-for-pursuing-an-M-Tech-after-a-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "twitter",
        "name": "mark mile",
        "handle": "@milegardening",
        "timestamp": "Jul 1, 2009",
        "text": "Assistant Professor in Computer Application and Science ANDHRA ...: A Bachelor's degree in Agriculture/Horti.. http://bit.ly/2SDbs",
        "link": "https://twitter.com/milegardening/status/2421753205",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/tuberlin",
        "author": "u/purplewizard997",
        "question": "How Competitive are Course Applications - Computer Science Masters?",
        "upvotes": "4",
        "comment": "6",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/tuberlin/comments/10t9wm1/how_competitive_are_course_applications_computer/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/careerguidance",
        "author": "u/getadmision",
        "question": "Which UG degree should I pursue if I want to do MBA afterwards?",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "8",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/careerguidance/comments/zdb7gp/which_ug_degree_should_i_pursue_if_i_want_to_do/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Do I opt for CA or BCA+ MCA as the demand of CA will be less in the next 10 years due to the modernization of accounting software?",
        "answer": "Choose CA over BCA+MCA because CA is a professional degree whereas these two academic courses. CAs will always be in demand and regardless of the modernization of accounting software, human interreference will always be relevant in the higher management level in companies as well in practice.",
        "name": "Bhumika Chopra",
        "views": "36 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Do-I-opt-for-CA-or-BCA-MCA-as-the-demand-of-CA-will-be-less-in-the-next-10-years-due-to-the-modernization-of-accounting-software",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which are the some best private college for MCA in Delhi?",
        "answer": "Here’s a list of some of the top private colleges for Masters in Computer Application s in Delhi NCR:\n\n1. World College of Technology and Management (WCTM), Gurugram\n\n2. Lingaya’s Vidyapeeth, Faridabad\n\n3. RC Institute of Technology (RCIT), New Delhi\n\n4. Manav Rachna International Institute of Research and Studies (MRIIRS), Faridabad\n\n5. JSS Academy of Technical Education (JSSATE), Noida\n\n6. Vivekananda Institute of Professional Studies (VIPS), New Delhi\n\n7. KIET Group of Institutions (KIET), Ghaziabad\n\nMasters in Computer Applications is a professional degree for those who want to build a career in the IT industry and thus its very crucial to receive an MCA from one of the top colleges in the country. The World College of Technology and Management stands out as the first choice in this regard. Also, WCTM, along with the best academic education provides best extra-curricular opportunities, placements and an amazing study culture with world class faculty. MCA being a two-year degree course, I would suggest you to go for WCTM because its curriculum constitutes academic knowledge as well as hardcore industry requirement upgradations.\n\nThe world class infrastructure with air-conditioned multi-media library, course books, reference books for academic fulfilment, in-campus Café Coffee Day, the most popular hangout joint amongst youth and is world-renowned for its fine selection of coffee, various sports facilities to choose from (Badminton, Basketball, Cricket, Football, Volleyball, Table Tennis, etc), bus facilities, etc makes it stand out and check off all the boxes that a world class college is supposed to have.\n\nThe World College of Technology and Management has a great placement record too. The college provides ample opportunities to each and every one of the eligible students to secure good placement. The college has been rated high also with regard to the placement of its students.\n\nI hope this will help you in your hunt for the best college for MCA in Delhi NCR.\n\nGood Luck!\n\nClick on the link for more information- Best engineering college in Gurgaon | Best engineering college in Delhi NCR | WCTM",
        "name": "Jyotsna Sharma",
        "views": "927 views",
        "link": "https://scholar.smu.edu/cgi/viewcontent.cgi?article=1867&context=jalc",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/uidmudaipur",
        "author": "u/Delicious-Dust-4811",
        "question": "Best BCA colleges in Udaipur",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/uidmudaipur/comments/tnj4zq/best_bca_colleges_in_udaipur/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Are degrees like BCA and MCA recognised in the UK and USA?",
        "answer": "There is no simple answer to this question as it depends on the specific degree and institution.\n\nIn general, however, degrees from accredited institutions are typically recognised in the UK and USA.",
        "name": "James Britt",
        "views": "431 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-mca-books-to-refer-to-crack-NIMCET",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the top BCA colleges in North India?",
        "answer": "I think BCA colleges are to be double-checked before taking admission. BCA has now become a generic course and is not as specified as CSE. BCA is an undergraduate degree that provides a wide spectrum of computers and their applications. To further specialize in this, you need to get an MCA degree to secure better job prospects.\n\nNowadays, students prefer to do engineering in CSE, AI, or MI as these are more futuristic but these courses come with high costs. Therefore, many of them who have a cost constraint but still want to pursue this stream go for the likes of BCA and MICA.\n\nComing back to your question, I have done my BCA from Graphic Era Hill University, which is in Dehradun, Uttarakhand. Personally, I liked my course because of two reasons:\n\n1. The university is renowned for its CSE specialization and since BCA as a course is kind of a younger brother to it, good attention is given to theoretical as well as practical knowledge in our university. The labs are good, the books in the library are up to date, and a lot of experiential learning is given as projects like creating smaller apps, etc.\n\nThe university also provides MCA and most of the faculties are well-educated and have expert knowledge.\n\nAnother factor why I took admitted to GEHU is that I am from Dehradun itself and so I got a 25%. discount on tuition fees which is available for all the domicile students from Uttarakhand or\n\nHimachal Pradesh taking admission in any course in Hill campus\n\nOverall, I would recommend you do thorough research as per your requirements and check out this university in North India.",
        "name": "Anurag Negi",
        "views": "124 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-top-BCA-colleges-in-North-India",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "How do you remember Gary Rossington, the last original member of Lynyrd Skynyrd, who passed away Sunday at age 71? How do you recall the musical legacy left by him and the band?",
        "answer": "Prince Charming as he was once referred to by former singer Ronnie Van Zant.\n\nThe Les Paul sound of Gary Rossington was the sound of Lynyrd Skynyrd, along with the single coil tone of guitarist Allan Collins. Lynyrd Skynrd took what The Allmans started, and followed it up with a three axe attack! Those early Skynrd tunes such as “Tuesday’s Gone” and “Workin’ For MCA” featured Rossington’s dirty, gritty Gibson sound accentuated by Collins nimble, quick fingered, Strat play. Along with West Coast transplant Ed King, Skynrd rose to fame on the backs of a long road of touring and concert dates. Rossington suffered from bad health for much of his life, in particular, his addiction to pain medication following the 1977 plane crash that claimed the lives of singer Ronnie Van Zant, guitarist Stevie Gaines, and sister Cassie Gaines, and tour manager Dean Kilpatrick.\n\nRossington was the last surviving member of the band that had its roots in the Sixties, in Jacksonville, Fla. I would’ve loved to hear more playing with Stevie Gaines, but unfortunately that would not be. The Rossington/Collins Band formed in 1979 mirrored Skynrd’s blues based attack, with vocals by Rossington’s future wife Dale Krantz. Supposedly, the two guitar players had tried to move away from the Skynrd formula sound, but with four ex-members (inc. Billy Powell and Leon Wilkerson), the comparisons were obvious. But Gary Rossington, for all the triumphs and tragedy, will always be known for his slide guitar work on the Skynrd anthem “Free Bird”. The bluesy, melodic play, followed by the furious, intense guitar work later in the track. Many fans define it as the quintessential mark of Southern Rock.\n\nGary eventually got his health back together following the plane crash, but he suffered from a serious addiction to pain pills following the event, which would last for years. He was 71 years old. R.I.P. brother!",
        "name": "Rocci Disopa",
        "views": "11.8K views",
        "link": "https://classicrockcafe.quora.com/How-to-remember-Gary-Rossington-the-last-original-member-of-Lynyrd-Skynyrd-who-passed-away-Sunday-at-age-71-How-do-yo",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/MechanicalEngineering",
        "author": "u/asbnoida",
        "question": "Can I study mechanical engineering in master if I have degree in bachelor in computer science ? If yes which university in US will accept me?",
        "upvotes": "10",
        "comment": "5",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/MechanicalEngineering/comments/12alvtr/can_i_study_mechanical_engineering_in_master_if_i/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Concordia",
        "author": "u/Illustrious_Act9979",
        "question": "Masters in Computer Science application",
        "upvotes": "4",
        "comment": "1",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Concordia/comments/ysgrvr/masters_in_computer_science_application/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/MentionSoft7518",
        "author": "u/MentionSoft7518",
        "question": "Just finished a demo reel for a computer graphics master's program application",
        "upvotes": "2",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/MentionSoft7518/comments/10r90mv/just_finished_a_demo_reel_for_a_computer_graphics/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Is it good to pursue MCA from LPU Lovely Professional University? What is the placement scenario for MCA students?",
        "answer": "Hello readers,\n\nLovely Professional University (LPU) is a private university located in Jalandhar, Punjab, India. The university is known for its diverse academic programs, including its Master of Computer Applications (MCA) program. In this article, we will discuss whether it is good to pursue MCA from LPU and what the placement scenario for MCA students is like.\n\nIs it good to pursue MCA from LPU?\n\nYes, pursuing MCA from LPU is a good option as the university offers a comprehensive curriculum that covers all aspects of computer science, programming languages, software engineering, and more. The MCA program at LPU is designed to provide students with both theoretical knowledge and practical skills. The course curriculum is updated regularly to keep up with the changing trends in the IT industry. The faculty at LPU is highly qualified, experienced, and committed to providing students with a high-quality education.\n\nLPU has state-of-the-art infrastructure and facilities that enable students to get hands-on experience in the latest technologies. The university has several computer labs equipped with the latest software and hardware, allowing students to gain practical experience in programming, software development, and more. The university also has tie-ups with leading IT companies, providing students with ample internship and job opportunities.\n\nIn addition, LPU has a strong emphasis on industry exposure, which helps students to develop a better understanding of the IT industry and its workings. The university regularly organizes workshops, seminars, and guest lectures by industry experts, providing students with an opportunity to interact with professionals and learn from their experiences.\n\nPlacement Scenario for MCA Students at LPU:\n\nThe placement scenario for MCA students at LPU is good, with several top companies visiting the campus for recruitment. The university has a dedicated placement cell that works tirelessly to ensure that students get placed in reputed companies.\n\nThe placement cell at LPU provides students with ample opportunities to interact with recruiters and attend pre-placement talks. The cell also helps students prepare for interviews, conduct mock interviews, and provide them with feedback to improve their skills.\n\nSome of the top companies that visit the LPU campus for recruitment include Infosys, TCS, Wipro, HCL, IBM, Cognizant, Capgemini, Accenture, and more. The average salary package for MCA students at LPU ranges from 4 to 7 lakhs per annum, depending on their academic performance, skills, and experience.\n\nThe university also has a strong alumni network that helps students to connect with industry professionals and explore job opportunities. The alumni network at LPU is spread across the world, providing students with a global perspective on the IT industry.\n\nPursuing MCA from Lovely Professional University is a good option as the university offers a comprehensive curriculum, state-of-the-art infrastructure, and a strong emphasis on industry exposure. The placement scenario for MCA students at LPU is good, with several top companies visiting the campus for recruitment. The university has a dedicated placement cell that works tirelessly to ensure that students get placed in reputed companies. In addition, the university has a strong alumni network that helps students to connect with industry professionals and explore job opportunities.\n\nHope this helps!!",
        "name": "Sankalp Shrivastava",
        "views": "33 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-good-to-pursue-MCA-from-LPU-Lovely-Professional-University-What-is-the-placement-scenario-for-MCA-students",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/kth",
        "author": "u/Humorous_Artist",
        "question": "Missing some documents for application MSc in Computer Science",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/kth/comments/126j1r8/missing_some_documents_for_application_msc_in/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which are the top institutes offering MCA and BCA courses in Delhi NCR?",
        "answer": "Delhi NCR is a home to many private institutes offering a Bachelors as well as a Masters in computer Applications. Are you looking forward to a career as an IT expert?\n\nWell, pursuing your degree from a top college will offer a cutting-edge curricula and pedagogy, top-notch infrastructure and facilities, and chances for you to complete foreign internships.\n\nSome of the top colleges in Delhi NCR for pursuing a BCA/MCA degree are:\n\nWorld College of Technology and Management (WCTM), Gurugram\nInstitute of Management studies (IMS), Noida\nLingaya’s Vidyapeeth, Haryana\nManav Rachna International Institute of Research and Studies (MRIIRS), Faridabad\nAmity University, Noida\nKR Mangalam University, Gurgaon\nInstitute of Professional Excellence and Management (IPEM), Ghaziabad\n\nBCA is one of the most sought-after technical courses because of the growing demand for IT experts both in India and internationally. There is also a lot of demand for MCA graduates due to their technical and analytical skills, which helps them excel in the IT field.\n\nWell, the World College of Technology and Management is the one that checks off all the boxes for being the best college. All the recommendations and pointers I put forward come from an experience of three years at WCTM. Yes, I’m a third year BCA student at WCTM, Gurugram.\n\nThe exposure at this college is commendable. Being an BCA student, there’s a constant need for industrial experience and well as technical guidance under experienced professionals, which WCTM provides. The internships and first-hand experience I’ve had here, has apparently improved me as a professional individual.\n\nHere at WCTM, you don’t just get to learn theories, but practice, experiment, perform during internships and inculcate your skills to excel in the professional world.\n\nFor more information, head over to this link- Best engineering college in Gurgaon | Best engineering college in Delhi NCR | WCTM",
        "name": "Ashok Deshmukh",
        "views": "284 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-college-has-low-fees-and-good-placements-in-Delhi-NCR-for-an-MCA-course",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/OrientalSchool2018",
        "author": "u/OrientalSchool2018",
        "question": "Bachelor in computer application | Educational Institution India",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/OrientalSchool2018/comments/b9owwh/bachelor_in_computer_application_educational/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What is your salary? Are you happy with it?",
        "answer": "I’m from Chennai (living in Tamil Nadu, India). I was jobless when I completed MCA in 2017. I hope you can imagine how hard it would be being an unemployed guy as well as first born in a middle class family.\n\nPrior to MCA, I worked in US Healthcare based call center for 2 years(2013-2015) which ruined my health so badly. After completing B.SC computer science in 2013, I had no options as I was the sole breadwinner of my family, my father was bed ridden due to a major accident, brother and sister were in school. I was urged by my Ex-Girlfriend to pursue Master Degree and I'm still grateful to her.\n\nI did Masters in Computer Applications 2015 – 2017 batch. Through my friend’s reference I got an offer in a call center right after completing MCA but it’s a night shift job. My boss supported me to learn python programming that too in the office desktop. I worked in that call center for 2.3 years. Started job search and attended 3 to 5 interviews, finally I got an offer in an education based company in 2019 and my salary was 13000 per month, at that time my close friends were earning 7+ LPA and one by one they started getting married. I was already 26 in 2019.\n\nAfter working in that company for 2+ years my salary was just 17000 per month. Therefore I started preparing for interviews and also attended more than 35 interviews, but I was rejected in all of them. Many times I cried like anything for being a failure.\n\nBut I didn’t give up and kept trying. Luckily in the next interview I was able to crack the technical rounds and secured an offer as a Python Developer in a product based company in October 2021 and my age was 28.\n\nBelow are the details of my salary raise.\n\nTrainee Programmer(2019) : 2.3 LPA\n\nPython developer(2021): 6.5 LPA(fixed)\n\nCurrent CTC: 13 LPA\n\nSo in a span of 3.5 years my salary raised from level zero to 13 LPA.\n\n“Am I happy with my salary?”\n\nWith no doubts yes I’m. I managed to repay my education loan, bought myself a bike, washing machine and Air conditioner for my parents finally Invested some money in gold.\n\nEdit1: I bagged an offer for 13 LPA!\n\nEdit2: Thanks for 3k upvotes\n\nEdit3: 4k upvotes, thanks for the overwhelming response!\n\nThanks for reading!!!",
        "name": "Selwin Sam",
        "views": "562.7K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Why-are-people-still-joining-TCS-Infosys-Wipro-Accenture-and-several-other-IT-companies-or-any-other-private-companies-when-they-have-understood-that-even-a-tea-stall-owner-or-Ola-drivers-earn-more-than-them",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/ProgrammingLanguages",
        "author": "u/Responsible-Dealer21",
        "question": "Teaching Category Theory to Computer Scientists (applications in programming language semantics)",
        "upvotes": "12",
        "comment": "1",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/ProgrammingLanguages/comments/12c7kuw/teaching_category_theory_to_computer_scientists/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "twitter",
        "name": "latest in india",
        "handle": "@latest_in_india",
        "timestamp": "Aug 13, 2009",
        "text": "\"bachelor of computer application in maharastra\" is getting popular in india: bachelor of computer application i.. http://bit.ly/CwxkM",
        "link": "https://twitter.com/latest_in_india/status/3275068342",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/ishit_sharma",
        "author": "u/Dumb_aloo",
        "question": "Bachelor of Computer Applications, course, fees, career | DBUU",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/ishit_sharma/comments/118r56b/bachelor_of_computer_applications_course_fees/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Is LPU good for a BCA?",
        "answer": "Hello readers, Lovely Professional University (LPU) is a private university located in Jalandhar, Punjab, India. LPU offers a Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA), which is a three-year undergraduate program designed to prepare students for careers in the field of computer applications.\n\nThe BCA program at LPU covers a wide range of topics related to computer applications, including programming languages, software engineering, database management, and computer networking. The program is designed to provide students with the knowledge and skills they need to become successful professionals in the field of computer applications.\n\nLPU has a good reputation for its academic programs, and its BCA program is no exception. The university has a strong faculty with expertise in the field of computer applications, and the program is designed to be practical and hands-on, with opportunities for students to gain real-world experience through internships and other experiential learning opportunities.\n\nAdditionally, LPU has state-of-the-art facilities for its BCA program, including well-equipped computer labs and access to the latest software and hardware technologies. The university also hosts coding competitions, hackathons, and other events to showcase the skills of its students and provide them with exposure to the industry.\n\nOverall, Lovely Professional University is a good choice for BCA, particularly for students who are interested in pursuing careers in the field of computer applications in India. The university's emphasis on practical, hands-on learning and access to the latest technologies make it a strong option for students looking to gain practical skills and real-world experience in the field of computer applications. However, it's always a good idea to do your own research and compare LPU's program with other options to ensure that it aligns with your goals and expectations.\n\nThank you!!",
        "name": "Vidushi Sharma",
        "views": "71 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-LPU-good-for-a-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "twitter",
        "name": "chalocampus",
        "handle": "@chalocampus",
        "timestamp": "Jul 23, 2009",
        "text": "BCA AICMT DELHI ADMISSIONS 2009: Bachelor Degree(BCA)2009 Admissions in Computer Application at Apar India Colle.. http://bit.ly/187O5q",
        "link": "https://twitter.com/chalocampus/status/2783022518",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Should one grow old gracefully or fight it all the way?",
        "answer": "I have no idea what is meant by gracefully. Does that mean be inactive and get fat and old? Be in poor physical condition? Drink oneself into a coma? I have exercised for about an hour and a half a day at least 4 days a week since childhood. I am in excellent physical shape. My body is better than most 30 year olds. My body fat is 11% I weigh 192 lbs. I can see my six pack a bit and have a hard chiselled body from a life time of exercise. My mind is better than its ever been. I also meditate for 40 minutes a day and have done since 1993. I read only non fiction and have since my 20’s and am very well read and educated. My girlfriend is in great shape as well and equally fit and healthy. My face is a bit lined but it doesnt bother me and I am living my life and doing what I enjoy. As a person I wish I knew then what I know now and life is generally pretty good.",
        "name": "Neil McA.",
        "views": "692 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-best-colleges-for-MCA-in-India",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/CareerSuccess",
        "author": "u/TheGeorgeTelegraph",
        "question": "Advantages of Learning BCA Bachelor in Computer Application",
        "upvotes": "2",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/CareerSuccess/comments/c56j8k/advantages_of_learning_bca_bachelor_in_computer/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What happened between Riyan Parag and Harshal Patel after making the last over of 18 roughly runs during RCB vs RR?",
        "answer": "Fight 😅\n\nRR innings against RCB in the Indian Premier League on Tuesday as Riyan Parag and Harshal Patel seemed to get into a heated argument after the 20th over.\n\nHarshal's last over, Parag hit → 4,2,6,6 = 18 runs off it.\n\nParag scored → 56 off 31b\n\nWatch the whole incident 👇\n\nThis was after 2 sixes were hit off the last over pic.twitter.com/qw3nBOv86A\n\n— ChaiBiscuit (@Biscuit8Chai) April 26, 2022\n\nSource:- Twitter\n\nRiding on Riyan Parag's superb batting effort and Kuldeep Sen's clinical bowling performance Rajasthan Royals defeated Royal Challengers Bangalore by 29 runs in the Indian Premier League clash at the MCA Stadium, Pune on Tuesday evening.",
        "name": "Pratik Das",
        "views": "40.2K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-Mca-colleges-in-Delhi-NCR",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Which are the best colleges in Nashik for a BCA?",
        "answer": "Nashik is one of the major cities in India. There are lots of colleges in Nahsik to study but there are some really best colleges.\n\nBCA is one of the hottest courses, where the student wants to get admission.\n\nSandip University\n\nK.K.Wagh Institute\n\nBYK college and many other colleges are offering BCA but these are the best colleges in Nashik.\n\nSandip University has located on outskirts of the Nashik city but the campus is very huge, it is spread across 250 acres. The college campus is one of the attraction points. If you see the campus with your eyes you will fix your decision to take admission only here. Even the professors are highly qualified and have a good amount of knowledge.\n\nK.K.Wagh college is located near Nashik City and this is the main USP for admission. If you want near the city it will best place\n\nYou can take your decision where you want for me I would choose Sandip University because they are good in all formats even though they are giving 100% placement and I also visited their website they mention as well there.",
        "name": "Rahul Pawar",
        "views": "50 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-best-colleges-in-Nashik-for-a-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which is better, a BCA with an MCA or a B.Engineering (B.E.) in CS?",
        "answer": "Bachelor of Engineering is always better than BCA with MCA.\n\nIn addition to BE, if you persue MBA or MCA or any other Masters Course, if would be offer you a good scope in future.\n\nFor information, reach us.\n\nAdnan Sohail\n\n81 49 45 95 93",
        "name": "Adnan Sohail",
        "views": "281 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-engage-with-you-as-my-personal-and-company-legal-advisor",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/HEC",
        "author": "u/Cybedra",
        "question": "Application for Master’s in Marketing",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "5",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/HEC/comments/11ywge2/application_for_masters_in_marketing/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/sanjanasbm",
        "author": "u/sanjanasbm",
        "question": "Best master of computer application colleges in mumbai | Top MCA College",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/sanjanasbm/comments/vk7cvw/best_master_of_computer_application_colleges_in/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the top MCA colleges in Bangalore?",
        "answer": "There are several top MCA (Master of Computer Applications) colleges in Bangalore, known for their quality education, experienced faculty, and excellent facilities. Here are some of the top MCA colleges in Bangalore:\n\nChrist University\nPES University\nRV College of Engineering\nBMS College of Engineering\nAcharya Institute of Technology\nMS Ramaiah Institute of Technology\nJain University\nDayananda Sagar College of Engineering\nNew Horizon College of Engineering\nCMR Institute of Technology\n\nThese colleges offer a comprehensive curriculum in computer applications, including programming languages, database management, data structures, and algorithms. They also provide practical training through industry visits, internships, and project work, which helps students to develop real-world skills and knowledge. Overall, these colleges have a reputation for producing skilled and knowledgeable MCA graduates who are well-equipped to succeed in the dynamic and ever-changing field of computer applications.",
        "name": "Ujjwal Matoliya",
        "views": "55 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-top-MCA-colleges-in-Bangalore",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/ICSE",
        "author": "u/saryuun12",
        "question": "How to present programs in Computer Applications paper?",
        "upvotes": "2",
        "comment": "12",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/ICSE/comments/11xgkok/how_to_present_programs_in_computer_applications/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/rrcekun",
        "author": "u/rrcekun",
        "question": "Best MCA Colleges in Bangalore – Master of Computer Applications",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/rrcekun/comments/10ez8v2/best_mca_colleges_in_bangalore_master_of_computer/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "When intoxicated drinks are reason for unruly behavior of some airline travelers, then why don’t airlines stop supplying the same and instead go only for soft drinks?",
        "answer": "Liquor “isn't free of cost” despite being served unlimited, you pay 8 times the inflated price along with the ticket. It covers 45% of airlines' profit. 2 pegs at 10,000 to 12,000 ft height attitude equals the physiological effect of 4 pegs. The effect almost doubles. This is one reason why it’s marketed as ‘unlimited free drinks’. This is why a few passengers who drink less get high quicker and behave worse.\n\nNext - Legal disputes.\n\nEach country/state/district has its individual law on times, places, and circumstances under which liquor may be served within its borders. When a flight is in mid-air there is a controversy on which country/state law should be applicable for unruly behavior as the flight passes through several states and countries in a journey.\n\nAAI - MCA calls it “navigable airspace” beyond borders.\n\nAn airway has been defined as a free highway in the sky.\n\nAAI- MCA doesn’t own the airlines but merely regulates the industry as a whole to promote safe air travel. The purpose of the AAI -MCA regulation controlling alcohol service is to protect the “safety of flights from intoxicated passengers”, not fellow passengers from a drunk person.\n\nThe law can be based on AAI- MCA regulations and Indian Aviation Act. plus the state or country district court law (Here is a question of which state law applies)\n\nIf someone gets injured by unruly behavior, they can sue the airline on the following two grounds\n\nFailure to protect passenger safety\nServing excess alcohol to an already intoxicated person.\n\nSo legally, the airline is answerable - not the drunk passenger.\n\nUnder this theory, liability can be imposed for:\n\nServing alcohol to a visibly intoxicated person\nServing alcohol to a person known to become violent after drinking\nServing alcohol with the knowledge that the intoxicated person will drive\n\nThis is because a reasonable person (crew member) should have known that serving liquor under those conditions would cause injury to a third party.\n\nNext, legally “intoxication is considered a disability”, so the airlines have to treat him with care as if they handle a disabled person, not behave rudely towards him.\n\nOn the other hand, the airline has NO special duty to protect him from the dangers of his own voluntary intoxication. Means he can consume more alcohol, loose concious till death and the airlines isn't liable for it.\n\nThese are the reasons why airlines continue to serve alcohol during long flights. Because there are fewer legal consequences and even lesser laws to protect the victim - here the victim may be a fellow passenger or even the person who gets drunk.\n\nOriginal question - When intoxicated drinks are the reason for the unruly behavior of some airline travelers, then why don’t airlines stop supplying the same and instead go only for soft drinks?\n\nhttps://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/0010880401424001\n https://scholar.smu.edu/cgi/viewcontent.cgi?article=1867&context=jalc",
        "name": "Naveen Subramanian",
        "views": "24.6K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/When-intoxicated-drinks-are-reason-for-unruly-behavior-of-some-airline-travelers-then-why-don-t-airlines-stop-supplying-the-same-and-instead-go-only-for-soft-drinks",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/careerguidance",
        "author": "u/digiomg",
        "question": "What do I do?",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "2",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/careerguidance/comments/uzsglf/what_do_i_do/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/saryuun12",
        "author": "u/Steven666v2",
        "question": "Best BCA college in Dehradun| Bachelor of Computer Application",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/saryuun12/comments/12cb9a5/best_bca_college_in_dehradun_bachelor_of_computer/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is the difference between MCA and MTech?",
        "answer": "Master of Computer Applications (MCA) and Master of Technology (MTech) are both postgraduate programs in the field of computer science and engineering. While both these programs have similarities in terms of course content and career prospects, there are significant differences between the two.\n\nThe following are some of the key differences between MCA and MTech:\n\nCourse Content: The MCA program is primarily focused on computer applications and software development. The program includes courses in programming languages, database management, software engineering, web development, mobile computing, and other related areas. The program is designed to provide students with a strong foundation in computer science and its applications.\n\nOn the other hand, MTech is a more specialized program that focuses on a particular area of computer science or engineering. The program includes courses in areas such as computer networks, artificial intelligence, machine learning, data science, cybersecurity, and others. MTech programs are designed to provide students with advanced knowledge and skills in a specific area of computer science.\n\nAdmission Requirements: The admission requirements for MCA and MTech programs differ. MCA programs usually require a Bachelor's degree in any discipline, with a minimum of 50% marks. The candidates must also have studied mathematics at the 10+2 level or in their Bachelor's degree. Some universities also require candidates to have a background in computer science or related fields.\n\nIn contrast, MTech programs require a Bachelor's degree in engineering or technology in the relevant field with a minimum of 60% marks. Some universities also require candidates to have a valid GATE score or to appear for an entrance test conducted by the university.\n\nCareer Prospects: The career prospects for MCA and MTech graduates are similar in some ways, but they also differ. MCA graduates are typically employed in software development companies, IT consulting firms, banks, healthcare organizations, educational institutions, and government agencies. They can work as software engineers, system analysts, database administrators, web developers, project managers, and other related roles.\n\nMTech graduates, on the other hand, are typically employed in research and development (R&D) organizations, product development companies, and technology startups. They can work as research engineers, data scientists, cybersecurity analysts, network architects, and other related roles. MTech graduates also have the option to pursue a career in academia or research.\n\nDuration: The duration of MCA and MTech programs also differs. The MCA program is usually of three years duration, and it consists of six semesters. The program includes both theoretical and practical courses, and the students are required to complete a project in the final semester.\n\nMTech programs are usually of two years duration, and they consist of four semesters. The program includes advanced courses in a specific area of computer science, and the students are required to complete a thesis or a research project in the final semester.\n\nConclusion: In summary, while MCA and MTech programs have some similarities, they also have significant differences. MCA programs are more focused on computer applications and software development, while MTech programs are more specialized and focused on a specific area of computer science or engineering. The admission requirements, career prospects, and duration of the programs also differ. Students should carefully consider their interests, career goals, and academic background before choosing between MCA and MTech programs.",
        "name": "Aniket Sharma",
        "views": "9 views",
        "link": "https://collegeforum.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-MCA-and-MTech",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/KULeuven",
        "author": "u/Extra-Cucumber8381",
        "question": "[GRE] Does a low Verbal Reasoning or Analytical Writing score affect my application for the Computer Science master's?",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "1",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/KULeuven/comments/11ljlm8/gre_does_a_low_verbal_reasoning_or_analytical/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/SBU",
        "author": "u/SnooDrawings405",
        "question": "How competitive is application for Masters in Computer Science? Do I have a chance of being admitted?",
        "upvotes": "3",
        "comment": "5",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/SBU/comments/yxv40g/how_competitive_is_application_for_masters_in/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/saryuun12",
        "author": "u/saryuun12",
        "question": "Best College for BCA in Dehradun | Bachelor of Computer Application",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/saryuun12/comments/11zc0ru/best_college_for_bca_in_dehradun_bachelor_of/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Can I do an MCA from NIT after a BA or a BSc in zoology?",
        "answer": "Hello Aspirant,\n\nYes, you can pursue an MCA (Master of Computer Applications) from a National Institute of Technology (NIT) after completing a BA or a BSc in Zoology. However, you will have to fulfill certain eligibility criteria to be eligible for admission to the MCA program at an NIT.\n\nThe eligibility criteria for MCA admission at NITs usually include:\n\nCompletion of a Bachelor's degree in any discipline with Mathematics as a subject in Class 12 or at the undergraduate level.\nA minimum aggregate score of 60% or 6.5 CGPA (on a 10-point scale) in the qualifying examination.\nQualifying in a national-level entrance exam like NIMCET (NIT MCA Common Entrance Test).\n\nIf you fulfill the above eligibility criteria, you can appear for the NIMCET entrance exam and qualify for admission to the MCA program at any of the participating NITs, subject to the availability of seats and other admission criteria.\n\nIt is important to note that a background in Zoology may not be directly relevant to the MCA program, which is focused on computer applications and software development. However, if you have a strong interest in computer applications and are willing to work hard to develop your skills, you can certainly pursue an MCA and build a successful career in the field of information technology.\n\nIf it is advisable and informative\n\nplz follow , upvote and share.\n\nThanks",
        "name": "Career Initiative",
        "views": "84 views",
        "link": "https://careerinitiativesspace.quora.com/Can-I-do-an-MCA-from-NIT-after-a-BA-or-a-BSc-in-zoology",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is the best placement MCA university in India?",
        "answer": "Leading Campus Placement Institution: Chandigarh University\n\nMCA FROM CHANDIGARH UNIVERSITY\n\nThe distance MCA from Chandigarh University is a highly acknowledged technical degree. It seeks to enhance the abilities required for employment in programming and computing. The Institute for Open & Remote Education at Chandigarh University strives to offer its online students helpful e-mentoring, interesting e-content, job placement assistance, and more.\n\nThree years are spent on the course.\n\nThe MCA\n\nThe course aims to strengthen pupils' computer application skills and software development abilities. Students will be better equipped to succeed in the corporate IT sector because to this preparation. MCA courses have a structured curriculum that spans five semesters and are more concentrated on applying topics like IT Skills, Programming Languages, and other similar ideas.\n\nThe MCA programme places a major emphasis on providing students with both a solid theoretical framework and extensive practical experience in the linked fields. It aims to offer fresh, business-focused instruction in applied computer science. Its goal is to create skilled workers who can successfully satisfy the demands of the information technology sector.",
        "name": "Kapish Goyal",
        "views": "7 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-placement-MCA-university-in-India",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Is it true that Mca is now for 1year for BCA graduate?",
        "answer": "No, MCA is Currently a 2-year full-time course.",
        "name": "Himanshu Shekhar",
        "views": "545 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Can-a-BCom-student-study-an-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/getadmision",
        "author": "u/Maybeajey",
        "question": "What is BCA Course",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/getadmision/comments/yfgcgo/what_is_bca_course/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are the benefits of pursuing a BA or BCA degree at LPU?",
        "answer": "Hello reader,\n\nI hope you are doing well,\n\nLovely Professional University (LPU) is a well-known private university in Jalandhar, Punjab, India, offering a wide range of undergraduate and postgraduate courses. The university offers BA and BCA degrees, which can be beneficial for students looking to pursue a career in various fields of study. Here are some of the benefits of pursuing a BA or BCA degree at LPU:\n\nWide range of specializations: LPU offers a wide range of specializations under its BA and BCA programs. Students can choose from a variety of subjects such as Computer Science, Animation, Multimedia, Economics, Political Science, Sociology, and many more.\nIndustry tie-ups: LPU has tie-ups with several top companies in various industries, which provides students with internships and placements in top companies. This helps students gain practical experience and opens up job opportunities.\nState-of-the-art infrastructure: LPU has world-class infrastructure, including modern laboratories, libraries, and classrooms equipped with the latest technology. The university provides students with access to these facilities, enabling them to learn and grow.\nExperienced faculty: LPU has experienced and qualified faculty members who are experts in their fields. They provide students with comprehensive education and guide them through their academic journey.\nGlobal exposure: LPU has a diverse student population from over 50 countries, providing students with a multicultural learning environment. The university also offers exchange programs with top universities around the world, providing students with the opportunity to study abroad and gain international exposure.\nScholarship opportunities: LPU offers scholarships to deserving students based on merit and financial need, making education accessible to all.\nStudent support: LPU provides its students with a range of support services, including academic support, career guidance, and counseling services, to ensure that they have a fulfilling and successful academic journey.\n\nIn conclusion, pursuing a BA or BCA degree at LPU can be a beneficial option for students looking to pursue a career in various fields of study. The university offers a wide range of specializations, industry tie-ups, state-of-the-art infrastructure, experienced faculty, global exposure, scholarship opportunities, and student support services. However, it is important to conduct further research and make an informed decision based on individual requirements and preferences.\n\nI hope it helps!\n\nThank you:)",
        "name": "Vidushi Sharma",
        "views": "22 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-benefits-of-pursuing-a-BA-or-BCA-degree-at-LPU",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What are good private colleges for a BCA?",
        "answer": "Hi Everyone,\n\nIn the upcoming years, it is anticipated that there will still be a high demand for qualified IT experts. There will be a demand for experts in fields like software development, data analysis, and cybersecurity as technology develops and is more deeply interwoven into numerous businesses.\n\nTypically, a wide range of computing-related topics, such as programming languages, data structures, computer architecture, and computer theory, are covered. The following are some advantages of earning a BCA degree:\n\nYou may be eligible for a range of entry-level IT positions with a BCA degree, including those in network administration, data analysis, and software development. A BCA degree can serve as a solid starting point for additional study in computer science or related subjects, which may result in more challenging and lucrative jobs.\n\nThe demand for highly qualified IT specialists is high and is anticipated to increase over the next several years. You may take advantage of these job chances with a BCA degree.\n\nThe college has a strong track record of placing graduates with major companies such as Oracle, IBM, and HCL, among others. It provides advanced technical training in various fields, including SAP, ESD, Java, and AutoCAD. The campus has a modern, aesthetically pleasing infrastructure spread across 18 acres of green space. The faculty consists of experienced professionals with advanced degrees in engineering and management, and the college encourages project-based learning to allow students to apply their knowledge to real-world problems and challenges. The college has partnerships with a range of organizations, including SAP University Alliance, Microsoft, IIT Delhi, and IIT Mumbai, to provide its students with additional opportunities and a competitive edge.\n\nWCTM has a perfect track record of making successful careers for many IT aspirants, you can check out more about the college through this link: - Best engineering college in Gurgaon | Best engineering college in Delhi NCR | WCTM",
        "name": "Dharmender Kumar",
        "views": "603 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-good-private-colleges-for-a-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/FAU_university",
        "author": "u/Less-Change-7466",
        "question": "Admission results for the Master in Computational Engineering (International Applicants)",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "7",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/FAU_university/comments/vh9aq5/admission_results_for_the_master_in_computational/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is the eligibility criteria for MCA?",
        "answer": "Master of Computer Applications (MCA) is a postgraduate degree program in computer applications that prepares students for a career in the IT industry. The program provides in-depth knowledge of various aspects of computer science, including programming, software development, database management, networking, and information systems.\n\nThe eligibility criteria for MCA may vary depending on the institute offering the program. However, some common requirements for MCA admission are\n\nEducation Qualification\n\nThe candidate should have a bachelor's degree in any discipline from a recognized university. The duration of the degree should be at least three years. In addition, candidates should have studied mathematics as a subject either at 10+2 or at graduation level.\n\nMinimum Marks\n\nThe candidate should have secured a minimum of 50% marks in their bachelor's degree. However, some institutes may have a relaxation in minimum marks for reserved category candidates.\n\nEntrance Exam\n\nMost institutes require candidates to appear for an entrance exam to be eligible for MCA admission. The most popular entrance exam for MCA admission in India is NIMCET (National Institute of Technology Master of Computer Applications Common Entrance Test). Other entrance exams include IPU CET (Indraprastha University Common Entrance Test), MAH MCA CET (Maharashtra Common Entrance Test for MCA), etc. The candidate must score minimum qualifying marks per the institute’s cutoff. Some institutes also consider the scores of other national-level entrance exams like CAT, MAT, XAT, etc.\n\nAge Limit\n\nThere is no age limit for MCA admission. However, some institutes may have a specific age limit for admission.\n\nWork Experience\n\nSome institutes may require candidates to have work experience in computer applications.\n\nApart from the above-mentioned requirements, some institutes may also consider the candidate's performance in the personal interview round. The interview may assess the candidate's communication skills, logical and analytical skills, and knowledge of computer science concepts.\n\nIt is essential to note that some institutes may have additional eligibility criteria for MCA admission. For instance, some institutes may require candidates to study a particular bachelor's level subject, such as computer science or information technology. Additionally, some institutes may conduct their entrance exam for MCA admission instead of accepting scores from national-level entrance exams.\n\nIn conclusion, the eligibility criteria for MCA admission may vary from institute to institute. Therefore, candidates should check the eligibility criteria of the institute they are interested in before applying for admission. Moreover, candidates should prepare well for the entrance exam and personal interview rounds to enhance their chances of admission to their preferred institute.",
        "name": "Aniket Sharma",
        "views": "9 views",
        "link": "https://collegeforum.quora.com/What-is-the-eligibility-criteria-for-MCA-1",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "I have done my 12th with PCB and want to do a BCA. Will I be eligible to take the MCA entrance exam like the NIMCET or else without having maths in 12th?",
        "answer": "Yes, if you have mathematics/ statistics in graduation and have secured a 60% or 6.5 cgpa aggregate then definitely.",
        "name": "Rishav Bajaj",
        "views": "10 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/I-have-done-my-12th-with-PCB-and-want-to-do-a-BCA-Will-I-be-eligible-to-take-the-MCA-entrance-exam-like-the-NIMCET-or-else-without-having-maths-in-12th",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Which university is best for an MCA, Chandigarh University or Lovely Professional University?",
        "answer": "Well, MCA is excellent course which is targeted for those aspirants who are willing to dive deeper into the development of computer applications with the support of contemporary programming language. The students pursuing the Computer \nApplication course are given a chance to develop modern software through the help of sophisticated tools and techniques . I think for this course you have to choose Lovely professional University as you will attain lucrative job packages and excellent job opportunities.\n\nEligibility- candidate must have done BCA with minimum 60% marks\n\nHere are the top MCA specialisations :\n\nMCA in Management Information Systems (MIS) ...\nMCA in Systems Management. ...\nMCA in Systems Engineering. ...\nMCA in Systems Development. ...\nMCA in Cloud Computing. ...\nMCA in Mobile Computing. ...\nMCA in Networking. ...\nMCA in Hardware Technology\n\nFeatures of MCA course in LPU:\n\nRankings- LPU is ranked among the top four Computer Applications Institutes of North India by NASSCOM.The Lovely Professional University (LPU) is declared 47th among all the government and private universities in India.It is a UGC-approved university which has been ranked well by various agencies\nLPU provides a great academic exposure to its students. It provides a chance to the students to attend guest lectures or workshops, so that they get to learn as much as they can.\nThe students also work on live projects, so that they are able to apply their knowledge to practical settings.\nMCA students exposed to real time software development environment, we run In-house Incubation Centre where students get chance to work on third party project during six months internship\nStudents have an instant access to latest technology labs like iMac, SAP, Cisco, etc that keeps them updated with the ever-changing technologies.SCA students gain competitive edge through in-house training opportunities.\nMany prestigious firms like,CODE NATION, CLOUDERA, COMMVAULT SYSTEMS INDIA PVT. LTD., Q2E BANKING, CYPHEROCK, CHUTNEY, SECURONIX etc. seek LPU to employ students for internships in addition to placements. At LPU, the maximum package available for the MCA programme is 31 LPA, while the average package is 4 LPA.\n\nThank you!",
        "name": "Nirweh",
        "views": "13 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-university-is-best-for-an-MCA-Chandigarh-University-or-Lovely-Professional-University",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What is better, preparing for SSC CGL or preparing for NIMCET MCA during my BCA? My financial condition is not well.",
        "answer": "Preparing for NIMCET & entering into NITs for MCA is definitely a better option than preparing for SSC CGLE.\n\nI said so based on below factors :\n\nTIME : Preparation of CGLE to getting final joining may take about 2.5–3 years or more in the current scenario because their process is exhausting & time taking. WHILE from NIMCET you can complete your preparation and enter NITs — one of the best colleges in India for placements after MCA.\nOUTCOME : After clearing CGLE, You enter Central Government departments where most of the posts are clerical & job nature monotonous in nature. WHILE after completing an MCA, it highly likely that you will be placed in the leading Tech/IT giants like Amazon, Google, Adobe, Infosys, Microsoft, Oracle, HP, Nvidia, Accenture, IBM, Wipro, Lava, Cypress, Philips, etc. Even if you don't get in-campus placements, you'll definitely make yourselves as an great IT professional in any industry or have your own start-up because NITs really build & polish your calibre to the next level.\nDIVERSIFIED EXPERIENCE : Serving as a government servant for lifetime through SSC CGL will make you tied to the salary-service-salary cycle. WHILE after doing MCA from NITs you'll have independence to become a freelancer, switch jobs, travel & explore the world if you enter an MNC and many endless opportunities.\n\nAfter clearing NIMCET, the fees of NITs per year for three year MCA course is about ₹ 80,000 including Hostel fees. It means you'll complete your MCA course in about ₹ 2.5 Lakh in 6 semesters. You'll easily get an Education loan from Banks if your financial situation is not well.\n\nYou should always follow your basic Instincts and passion so that you don't have regrets in future. I also suggest to have one option of your choice as back-up as thinking practical is necessary.\n\nAll the very best ! 👍",
        "name": "Abhineet",
        "views": "2.2K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-private-universities-for-an-MCA-in-Delhi-NCR",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is the difference between a B.Tech and a MCA from VIT University? Which course is better for me, and why?",
        "answer": "Hello Aspirant,\n\nB.Tech (Bachelor of Technology) and MCA (Master of Computer Applications) are both computer science programs offered by VIT University. Here are the key differences between the two courses:\n\nLevel of study: B.Tech is an undergraduate program, while MCA is a postgraduate program. This means that MCA is a more advanced degree and requires more in-depth study and specialization.\nCurriculum: B.Tech focuses on building a strong foundation in computer science and engineering fundamentals, while MCA is more specialized and focuses on advanced topics such as software engineering, database management, and advanced programming languages.\nDuration: B.Tech is typically a four-year program, while MCA is a two-year program.\nJob opportunities: B.Tech graduates may find entry-level positions in software development, web development, IT support, and other related fields, while MCA graduates may be more specialized and may find job opportunities in areas such as software development, database administration, and systems analysis.\nSalary potential: In general, MCA graduates may earn a higher salary than B.Tech graduates due to their advanced degree and specialized knowledge.\n\nIn terms of which course is better for you, it depends on your academic background, interests, and career goals. If you are interested in computer science and engineering and want to build a strong foundation in the field, then B.Tech may be a better option for you. On the other hand, if you want to specialize in a particular area of computer science such as software engineering or database management, then MCA may be a better fit.\n\nIt is recommended that you research and compare the curricula, job opportunities, and career prospects of both courses to make an informed decision. You may also consider consulting with a career counselor or admission consultant who can provide you with personalized guidance based on your academic background, preferences, and career goals.\n\nIf it is advisable and informative\n\nplz follow , upvote and share.\n\nThanks",
        "name": "Career Initiative",
        "views": "101 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-a-B-Tech-and-a-MCA-from-VIT-University-Which-course-is-better-for-me-and-why",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past hour",
        "question": "What is the process of getting placed in Zoho after completing a Master of Computer Applications (MCA)? What is the average salary for a fresher in this company?",
        "answer": "Depends on the department and role they are hiring you for….. and that is applicable across the industry. On an average 5–7 lakhs for a fresher with zero work experience.",
        "name": "B Raj",
        "views": "2 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-process-of-getting-placed-in-Zoho-after-completing-a-Master-of-Computer-Applications-MCA-What-is-the-average-salary-for-a-fresher-in-this-company",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Is it worth doing a MCA after a BCA?",
        "answer": "Yes it is worth to do a master degree always.",
        "name": "Poshiplatta Bagati",
        "views": "275 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-should-I-pursue-an-MCA-or-MBA-after-a-BCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "How do I get into a good college for an MCA?",
        "answer": "To get into a good college for an MCA (Master of Computer Applications), you can follow these steps:\n\nResearch: Start by researching the top colleges that offer MCA programs in your country or region. Look for colleges that have a good reputation, experienced faculty, excellent facilities, and placement opportunities.\nEligibility: Check the eligibility criteria for admission to MCA programs in different colleges. Typically, candidates should have a bachelor's degree in Computer Science or a related field with a minimum percentage of marks specified by the college.\nEntrance exams: Many colleges require candidates to take an entrance exam to be eligible for admission to the MCA program. The most common entrance exams for MCA include NIMCET, MAH MCA CET, TANCET, etc. You can check the entrance exam requirements for different colleges and prepare accordingly.\nApplication process: Once you have identified the colleges and entrance exams you want to apply for, you need to submit your application. The application process may involve filling out an online or offline application form, uploading required documents such as transcripts, entrance exam scorecards, and other necessary documents, and paying the application fee.\nPreparation: Start preparing for the entrance exams well in advance. You can refer to textbooks, online resources, or join coaching classes to improve your chances of success.\nInterview: Some colleges may also conduct interviews as part of the selection process. Prepare for the interview by researching the college, practicing common interview questions, and presenting yourself professionally.\n\nIn summary, to get into a good college for an MCA, you need to research the top colleges, meet the eligibility criteria, prepare for entrance exams and interviews, and submit a strong application.",
        "name": "Sharma Shaan",
        "views": "2 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-get-into-a-good-college-for-an-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "How will I get a summary list of companies in India?",
        "answer": "There are various ways to get a summary list of companies in India. Here are some options:\n\nMinistry of Corporate Affairs (MCA) website: The MCA is the government agency responsible for regulating companies in India. They maintain a database of all registered companies in India, which you can access through their website. To access this database, go to the MCA website (www.mca.gov.in) and click on the \"MCA Services\" tab. From there, you can access the \"View Company Master Data\" option to get a list of companies.\nUse online business directories: There are several online directories that list Indian companies, such as IndiaMART, TradeIndia, and Justdial. These directories allow you to search for companies based on their location, industry, and other parameters.",
        "name": "Casper Boy",
        "views": "14 views",
        "link": "https://casperboysspace.quora.com/How-will-I-get-a-summary-list-of-companies-in-India",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Which is better, a B.Tech from NIT or an MCA from IIM?",
        "answer": "It is difficult to compare a B.Tech from NIT with an MCA from IIM as they are different programs with different career paths. However, here are some factors to consider when making a choice between the two:\n\nCareer Goals: If your goal is to become a software developer or work in the IT industry, then a B.Tech from NIT would be a better choice. On the other hand, if you want to pursue a career in IT management or consulting, then an MCA from IIM might be a better fit.\nCurriculum: The curriculum of B.Tech from NIT focuses more on technical skills related to software development, programming languages, and engineering principles. On the other hand, the MCA program from IIM focuses more on business administration, management principles, and IT strategy.\nPlacement opportunities: Both NITs and IIMs have a good track record of placements. However, the type of companies that visit for recruitment may differ based on the program. B.Tech graduates from NITs are likely to be recruited by software companies, whereas MCA graduates from IIMs are likely to be recruited by consulting firms, financial institutions, and IT management firms.\n\nUltimately, the choice between a B.Tech from NIT and an MCA from IIM depends on your interests, career goals, and personal preferences.",
        "name": "Eduxprts",
        "views": "16 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-better-a-B-Tech-from-NIT-or-an-MCA-from-IIM",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is the admission process for MCA?",
        "answer": "The admission process for MCA (Master of Computer Applications) programs in India generally involves a series of steps that students must follow to secure a seat in their preferred college. In this article, we will discuss the MCA admission process in detail, including eligibility criteria, application process, entrance exams, and counseling.\n\nEligibility Criteria for MCA Admission: Before applying for an MCA program, students must ensure that they meet the eligibility criteria set by the college or university. The basic eligibility criteria for MCA admission are as follows:\n\nA Bachelor's degree in Computer Science, IT, or any other related field with a minimum of 50% aggregate marks (45% for SC/ST candidates)\nMathematics as a subject in class 12th or graduation\nSome colleges may require candidates to have a certain minimum score in entrance exams like NIMCET, IPU CET, MAH CET, or TANCET.\n\nApplication Process for MCA Admission: Once students ensure that they meet the eligibility criteria for MCA admission, they can begin the application process. The application process for MCA admission generally involves the following steps:\n\nOnline Registration: Students must register themselves on the official website of the college or university they wish to apply to. They will have to provide basic personal information, contact details, and academic qualifications.\nFilling the Application Form: After registration, students must fill the application form by providing their educational details, work experience (if any), and other relevant information. They must also upload scanned copies of their photograph, signature, and relevant documents.\nPayment of Application Fee: After filling the application form, students must pay the application fee. The fee may vary depending on the college or university and can be paid online using a credit card, debit card, or net banking.\nSubmission of Application Form: Once the application fee is paid, students must submit their application form online. They must take a printout of the application form and keep it for future reference.\n\nEntrance Exams for MCA Admission: Most colleges and universities offering MCA programs in India conduct entrance exams to shortlist candidates for admission. Some of the popular MCA entrance exams in India are.\n\nIndraprastha University Common Entrance Test (IPU CET)\nMaharashtra Common Entrance Test (MAH CET)\nTamil Nadu Common Entrance Test (TANCET)\n\nThese exams generally consist of multiple-choice questions (MCQs) and test a candidate's aptitude in areas like mathematics, reasoning, and computer science.\n\nCounseling for MCA Admission: After the entrance exams are conducted, colleges and universities release merit lists based on the scores obtained by candidates. Candidates who clear the cutoff score are called for counseling, which is the final stage of the MCA admission process.\n\nDuring counseling, students must report to the designated counseling center and verify their documents. They must also select their preferred college or university and course based on the availability of seats. The counseling process is generally conducted in multiple rounds until all the seats are filled.\n\nIn conclusion, the MCA admission process in India involves eligibility criteria, application process, entrance exams, and counseling. Students must carefully follow these steps to secure a seat in their preferred college or university. They must also ensure that they meet the eligibility criteria and prepare well for the entrance exams to increase their chances of getting admission.",
        "name": "Aniket Sharma",
        "views": "9 views",
        "link": "https://collegeforum.quora.com/What-is-the-admission-process-for-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Can I become a data scientist after BCA? If no, what should I do?",
        "answer": "The answer is yes.\n\nI am a data scientist and also Graduate from BCA.\n\nFollow this link\n\nhttps://analytical.quora.com/Roadmaps-to-becoming-a-Full-Stack-AI-Developer-Data-Scientist-Machine-Learning-Engineer-and-more-https-www-kdnugge https://analytical.quora.com/Roadmaps-to-becoming-a-Full-Stack-AI-Developer-Data-Scientist-Machine-Learning-Engineer-and-more-https-www-kdnugge?ch=15&oid=100796846&share=d13e4823&srid=hrojGp&target_type=post",
        "name": "Prem Rana",
        "views": "25 views",
        "link": "https://analytical.quora.com/Can-I-become-a-data-scientist-after-BCA-If-no-what-should-I-do",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/gradadmissions",
        "author": "u/___V-E-N-0-M___",
        "question": "UBC | Master of Science in Computer Science 2023 Fall - Admission Results",
        "upvotes": "5",
        "comment": "16",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/gradadmissions/comments/121ket7/ubc_master_of_science_in_computer_science_2023/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What are the best colleges for an MCA in Pune?",
        "answer": "Computers have taken our world by storm. Our every action is now dependent on computer Technology. With the era of the 4th revolution, an expertise in the field of computers can give the head start you need in your career. MCA, an acronym for Master of Computer Applications is a computer science PG program for those who are interested in this field. This course can span from 2-3 years and it will give you that essential knowledge and degree that is well sought after by various MNC's. This master’s program is designed to equip its students with a good theoretical knowledge in the field and provide ample scope in developing their practical approach to Computers.\n\nPune is one such city in India which is a popular education hub of India. There are various colleges in Pune offering MCA degree courses for the students. Students must choose a college after comparing all essential factors so that they can achieve their desired objectives.\n\nThe most renowned colleges for MCA in Pune are:\n\n● Symbiosis Institute of Computer Studies and Research (SICSR),Pune\n\n● Fergusson College (Autonomous), Pune\n\n● Vishwakarma Institute of Technology (VIT), Pune\n\n● (PCCOE)Pimpri Chinchwad College Of Engineering, Pune\n\n● Ness Wadia College of Commerce, Pune\n\n● Maharashtra Institute Technolgy, Kothrud (MIT), Pune.\n\n● Bharati Vidyapeeth Deemed University (IMED), Pune\n\n● D. Y. Patil Institute of Master of Computer Applications and Management, Akurdi\n\n● Sinhgad Institute of management(SIOM), Pune.\n\n● Indira College of Engineering and Management, Pune\n\n● Modern College of Arts, Science & Commerce, Pune\n\n● Garware College Of Commerce, Pune\n\n● Pratibha Institute of Business Management (PIBM), Pune.\n\nI Hope the information was informative:)\n\nALL THE BEST!",
        "name": "Rajesh Kumar Singh",
        "views": "847 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-college-for-an-online-MCA-in-Bangalore",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/China",
        "author": "u/Achilles370",
        "question": "A little help on choosing countries for studies.",
        "upvotes": "2",
        "comment": "7",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/China/comments/pkx1ms/a_little_help_on_choosing_countries_for_studies/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Stutter",
        "author": "u/oliverneut",
        "question": "What are some IT jobs where you dont have to. Talk much . What are options available .need guidance from experience people",
        "upvotes": "8",
        "comment": "7",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Stutter/comments/qv09n1/what_are_some_it_jobs_where_you_dont_have_to_talk/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/Less-Change-7466",
        "author": "u/digiomg",
        "question": "Why Student Should Pursue MCA to Speed Up Their Career",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/Less-Change-7466/comments/ywndaa/why_student_should_pursue_mca_to_speed_up_their/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What are the career opportunities or placements available at present for students who have been admitted into the integrated MCA program at Lovely Professional University?",
        "answer": "Hello reader,\n\nI hope you are doing well,\n\nLovely Professional University (LPU) offers an integrated MCA program to prepare students for successful careers in the field of computer applications. The program is designed to provide students with the necessary skills and knowledge to pursue a successful career in the technology sector. The integrated MCA program at LPU provides a plethora of career opportunities for its students.\n\nThe curriculum of the program enables students to gain theoretical and practical knowledge in the domains of computer applications, programming, software engineering, and other related fields. The program helps students to gain the skills to develop, implement and maintain computer applications.\n\nThe integrated MCA program at LPU also offers placements to its students. The university has a dedicated placement cell that helps students in their job search. The placement cell assists the students in preparing for the placement tests, interviews, and other related processes. The university also provides internships to its students. The internships provide an opportunity for the students to gain hands-on experience and to gain insights into the work environment. The internships also help students to develop connections with potential employers.\n\nThe integrated MCA program at LPU also provides students with the opportunity to pursue higher studies. The university offers a wide range of courses in the field of computer applications and software engineering. The courses offered by the university provide an in-depth understanding of the concepts and technologies involved in the field.\n\nThe integrated MCA program at LPU also provides students with the opportunity to work in the industry. The program provides students with the necessary skills and knowledge to pursue a career in the technology sector. The students can find employment opportunities in different sectors such as IT, software development, software engineering, web development, and other related fields.\n\nOverall, the integrated MCA program at LPU provides students with a wide range of career opportunities and placements. The program helps students to gain the necessary skills and knowledge to pursue a successful career in the field of computer applications and software engineering. The university also provides internships, higher studies, and employment opportunities to its students.\n\nI hope it was helpful to you!\n\nThank you:)",
        "name": "Vidushi Sharma",
        "views": "52 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-scope-of-an-MCA-graduate-in-the-UPSC-examination",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is the fee structure of a BCA in LPU, or is LPU good for a BCA?",
        "answer": "Hello reader,\n\nI hope you are doing well,\n\nwell, since one of my roommates is from the BCA course so could provide you with the information related to the same.\n\nThe fee structure of a BCA at Lovely Professional University (LPU) is quite affordable, considering the quality of education and facilities that the university provides. It is one of the leading universities in India, with a good reputation in terms of its academic programs. For the Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) program, the total fee is around INR 1.5 lakhs. This fee is divided into four installments. The first installment has to be paid at the time of admission and the remaining three have to be paid at the start of each semester. The fee also includes tuition fees, examination fees, library fees, and other miscellaneous charges.\n\nThe university also provides various scholarships for meritorious students and those from economically weaker sections of society. This helps them to pursue their studies without any financial burden. LPU is indeed a great choice for pursuing a BCA degree. It has highly qualified and experienced faculty members who are dedicated to providing quality education to students. The university offers various modern amenities such as a well-equipped library, fully-equipped laboratories, a sports complex, etc. It also provides a holistic learning environment with modern teaching methods, seminars, and workshops.\n\nThe university also provides various internships, industry visits, and learning opportunities which help the students to gain hands-on experience and develop a good understanding of the subject. Overall, LPU is a great choice for pursuing a BCA degree. It provides quality education, modern facilities, and a great learning environment. The fee structure is also quite affordable and the university provides scholarships for deserving students.\n\nI hope it helps!\n\nThank you:)",
        "name": "Vidushi Sharma",
        "views": "61 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-fee-structure-of-a-BCA-in-LPU-or-is-LPU-good-for-a-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which college has low fees and good placements in Delhi NCR for an MCA course?",
        "answer": "Are you looking for a suitable college for doing an MCA in Delhi NCR? We’re here for you!\n\nHere’s a list of top colleges offering an MCA degree in Delhi NCR:\n\n1. World College of Technology and Management (WCTM), Gurugram\n\n2. Amity University, Noida\n\n3. Manav Rachna International Institute of Research and Studies (MRIIRS), Faridabad\n\n4. KR Mangalam University of Information and Technology, Gurgaon\n\n5. G.D.Goenka University\n\n6. Galgotias University, Greater Noida\n\nOut of all these listed colleges, which college fulfils all the parameters? Which college has an affordable fee structure alongside a good placement record?\n\nWell, my answer to this question is very clear- I’d recommend the World College of Technology and Management (WCTM), Gurugram.\n\nThe World College of Technology and Management provides its students with a world class infrastructure, wide range of extra-curricular opportunities, teaching environment under the able guidance of experienced faculties, and everything in between. And all of it, comes with a very affordable fee structure. The very important aspect of choosing a ‘perfect’ college for yourself undoubtedly depends upon the placement record of the particular college because what matters in the end is- what job opportunity does the college offer? So, here at WCTM, this checkbox is also ticked! The World College of Technology and Management, Gurugram has an excellent placement record of outgoing batch by 100 plus companies ORACLE, IBM, HCL, L&T, WIPRO, DELHI-METRO, and many more.\n\nTherefore, WCTM has everything you’re looking for- affordable fee structure, commendable exposure, international tie-ups, industrial training, experienced faculty, impeccable placement records etc.\n\nFor more information visit this link- Best engineering college in Gurgaon | Best engineering college in Delhi NCR | WCTM",
        "name": "Dharmender Kumar",
        "views": "542 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-much-salary-is-offered-in-placements-of-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Which career is better, a BCA or a B.Tech?",
        "answer": "Both BCA (Bachelor of Computer Applications) and B.Tech (Bachelor of Technology) are popular undergraduate programs in the field of computer science and technology. However, the choice between the two largely depends on your career aspirations and interests.\n\nBCA is a three-year undergraduate degree program that focuses on the application of computer technology in business, commerce, and other industries. The program emphasizes on software development, programming languages, database management, and computer networking. BCA graduates can pursue careers as software developers, database administrators, system analysts, or web designers, among others.\n\nOn the other hand, B.Tech is a four-year undergraduate degree program that offers a comprehensive education in engineering and technology. B.Tech graduates specialize in a particular area of engineering, such as computer science, electrical, mechanical, or civil engineering. The program emphasizes on problem-solving, design, and innovation, and prepares graduates for careers as engineers, scientists, researchers, or consultants.\n\nIn general, B.Tech graduates tend to have a wider range of career opportunities and higher earning potential than BCA graduates, due to their specialized skills and knowledge in engineering and technology. However, BCA can also be a good choice for students who are interested in computer applications and programming, and want to start their careers in the IT industry.\n\nUltimately, the choice between BCA and B.Tech depends on your individual interests, career goals, and academic strengths. You should research and compare the curricula, career prospects, and opportunities for further education before making a decision.",
        "name": "Aarti Lohakare",
        "views": "25 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-career-is-better-a-BCA-or-a-B-Tech",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is the fee structure for a BCA at Mount Carmel College?",
        "answer": "Mount Carmel College, Bangalore, is a renowned institution offering a variety of undergraduate and postgraduate courses, including the Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) program. The BCA program at Mount Carmel College is a three-year degree course that provides students with a comprehensive understanding of computer applications and equips them with the necessary skills required for the industry.\n\nThe fee structure for the BCA program at Mount Carmel College, Bangalore, may vary depending on the category of admission. The two categories of admission are government quota and management quota. The government quota fee for the BCA program at Mount Carmel College for the academic year 2021-22 was around Rs. 35,000 per year. The management quota fee for the same program was around Rs. 1,50,000 per year.\n\nIt is important to note that the fee structure may change from year to year. Therefore, students must confirm the latest fee structure from the institution or their official website.\n\nMount Carmel College, Bangalore, provides a world-class infrastructure to its students, which includes well-equipped computer labs, state-of-the-art classrooms, libraries, and sports facilities. The institution also provides a supportive and conducive environment for students, which includes academic and career counseling, extracurricular activities, and mentorship programs.\n\nMoreover, Mount Carmel College, Bangalore, provides various scholarship and financial assistance programs to deserving students. The institution offers merit-based scholarships, sports scholarships, and other financial aid programs to support students who face financial constraints. The scholarship and financial assistance programs at Mount Carmel College are designed to help deserving students pursue their education without financial constraints.\n\nIn addition, the BCA program at Mount Carmel College, Bangalore, is designed to provide students with a holistic understanding of computer applications. The program's curriculum is designed to provide students with a strong foundation in computer science and programming languages such as Java, C++, and Python. The program also includes hands-on training, industrial visits, and internships to provide students with practical exposure and industry experience.\n\nMount Carmel College, Bangalore, has a strong placement cell that works closely with the industry to provide students with placement opportunities in various reputed companies. The placement cell conducts various activities, including mock interviews, group discussions, and career counseling sessions, to prepare students for the placement process. The institution has a track record of successful placements, with students being placed in various reputed companies, including Google, Amazon, Deloitte, KPMG, and many more.\n\nIn conclusion, the BCA program at Mount Carmel College, Bangalore, is an excellent choice for students aspiring to pursue a career in computer applications. The program's fee structure is affordable, and the institution provides world-class infrastructure, supportive environment, and scholarship and financial assistance programs to deserving students. Moreover, the program's curriculum, hands-on training, and internships provide students with a strong foundation in computer applications and the necessary skills required for the industry. Finally, the institution's robust placement cell provides students with ample opportunities to kick-start their careers in the industry.",
        "name": "Pooja Hegde",
        "views": "377 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-fee-structure-for-a-BCA-at-Mount-Carmel-College",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What is the reason you are not rich?",
        "answer": "Hi, I am Nitin Prakash Singh, and there are multiple reasons that make me poor.\n\nI am the elder son in the family that came with multiple responsibilities and I belong to a middle-class family, My father is also elder than his brother. when I completed my 12th I don’t have money to take admission in any technical course and at that time I don’t have that much knowledge, I used to think that education is the only thing that makes me rich.\n\nSo after 12th, I took admitted to B.sc(Physics) and start preparing for government jobs and waste my golden 4 years because after all of my hard work, I was not clear any govt exam, and my family don’t have money for any technical course like (B.tech or BCA or BBA or any other course for private college). and want to do B.tech but my family did not support me because of money and then after 2017 I decided to do MCA on the advice of one of my relatives.\n\nI took a loan of 4 lacs and complete my MCA after my MCA I got placed in an IT services base company(Fluper Mobo Agency) in Noida as an iOS developer and in starting of my career I got a 10000 rs in-hand salary, and for the first 6 months used to work free, company did not give us salary even they did not provide us stipend. and in march 2020 corona comes to India and again for 3 months company did not get work from me and I am on the bench for that period of time. after that in July 2020, I get a job in a different company in Noida where I start earning 18000. that was my first salary and a good job, after one year I leave that company and start working in Chetu India.\n\nI don’t have a home in the village so I took a 1000000 Home loan I have explained I am the elder in the family so I have many responsibilities for the family all my brother idealizes me. I have to take care of all of them, I have to gift them they think I earn very well and am very happy but in reality, I pay 65% of my salary in EMI every month. and I send 10000 every month to my mother.\n\nThese all are the reason I am not rich.\n\nThanks",
        "name": "Nitin Prakash Singh",
        "views": "44.4K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-reason-you-are-not-rich",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the benefits of pursuing an MCA from SRM Amravati?",
        "answer": "Hello Aspirant,\n\nMCA or Master of Computer Applications is a postgraduate program that provides advanced training in computer science and its applications. Pursuing an MCA from SRM University, Amaravati can offer several benefits, including:\n\nIndustry-relevant curriculum: The MCA program at SRM University, Amaravati is designed to provide students with a strong foundation in computer science concepts and practical skills that are relevant to the industry. The program is regularly updated to keep up with the latest trends and technologies in the field.\nPractical training: The MCA program at SRM University, Amaravati provides students with ample opportunities to gain practical experience through internships, projects, and industry collaborations. This can help students to develop the skills necessary to succeed in the industry.\nExperienced faculty: The faculty at SRM University, Amaravati, are experienced and knowledgeable in their fields, and are dedicated to providing students with a high-quality education. They provide individual attention to students and help them to develop critical thinking, problem-solving, and communication skills.\nExcellent infrastructure: SRM University, Amaravati has state-of-the-art infrastructure, including well-equipped labs, libraries, and other facilities that are necessary for a comprehensive education in computer science.\nCareer opportunities: An MCA degree from SRM University, Amaravati can open up a wide range of career opportunities in areas such as software development, data science, cybersecurity, and project management, among others.\nNetworking opportunities: The MCA program at SRM University, Amaravati provides students with ample opportunities to network with industry professionals, alumni, and other students. This can help students to build valuable connections that can help them to advance their careers.\n\nOverall, pursuing an MCA from SRM University, Amaravati can provide students with a comprehensive education in computer science and valuable practical experience that can help them to succeed in the industry.\n\nIf it is advisable and informative\n\nplz follow , upvote and share.\n\nThanks",
        "name": "Career Initiative",
        "views": "60 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-benefits-of-pursuing-an-MCA-from-SRM-Amravati",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is the opinion of students who have completed the Master of Computer Applications (MCA) course at Lovely Professional University in Rajkot, India?",
        "answer": "Hello reader,\n\nI hope you are doing well,\n\nSince one of my seniors is currently doing MCA from LPU, so could provide you with an insight about the same.\n\nLovely Professional University takes a holistic approach to education to develop students' individual and intellectual potential. Its commitment to nurturing bright minds and creating an exceptional living and learning environment allows students to reach their full potential. Life at LPU is one to look forward to.\n\nThe concept of nourishing individual minds outside of lecture halls through extracurricular and multicultural environments provides all students with a rich learning experience. LPU provides a beautiful campus life—a campus life that you have all imagined.\n\nPlacements-\n\nLPU has a dedicated placement cell that assists students in securing job offers from various organizations. According to the university's website, 200+ companies visited LPU for MCA placements, including big names like Amazon, Google, Microsoft, Infosys, TCS, Cognizant, and Capgemini. The highest package offered to an MCA student was Rs. 29 LPA, while the average package was around Rs. 4-5 LPA. LPU claims a placement record of over 90% for MCA students.\n\nFaculty: LPU's MCA faculty comprises experienced academicians and industry professionals with expertise in their respective fields. As per the university's website, the faculty members hold doctorates from reputed institutions and have published research papers in national and international journals. They also conduct workshops, seminars, and training programs to enhance the student's skills.\n\nCurriculum: LPU's MCA course is designed to provide students with a strong foundation in computer science and software development. The curriculum covers subjects like programming languages, algorithms, data structures, database management, web development, and software engineering. Additionally, LPU offers elective courses in emerging areas like cloud computing, data analytics, artificial intelligence, and blockchain technology. The course also includes a six-month industry internship to provide students with practical exposure to the software industry.\n\nOverall, the feedback of students who have completed the Master of Computer Applications (MCA) course at Lovely Professional University (LPU) appears to be positive. The university's strong placement record, experienced faculty, and industry-oriented curriculum have helped students secure job offers from reputed organizations.\n\nI hope I was able to help you!\n\nThank you:)",
        "name": "Vidushi Sharma",
        "views": "29 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-opinion-of-students-who-have-completed-the-Master-of-Computer-Applications-MCA-course-at-Lovely-Professional-University-in-Rajkot-India",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Which college is best for MCA / MSc IT with affordable fees?",
        "answer": "Hello there,\n\nHere are some top colleges for MCA/MSc IT with affordable fees:\n\nVellore Institute of Technology (VIT)\nManipal Academy of Higher Education (MAHE)\nSymbiosis Institute of Computer Studies and Research (SICSR)\nAmity University\nChrist University\nJain University\nDelhi University\nUniversity of Mumbai\nPune University\nBangalore University\nPSG College of Technology\nSRM Institute of Science and Technology\nChandigarh University\n\nHope it helps, for more details regarding college and admission feel free to contact 📲6205238449(Call/WhatsApp)\n\nThank you❤",
        "name": "Anjali Mishra",
        "views": "44 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-college-is-best-for-MCA-MSc-IT-with-affordable-fees",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/invertisbareilly",
        "author": "u/getadmision",
        "question": "Know more about the BCA course at Invertis University",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/invertisbareilly/comments/x3xc3y/know_more_about_the_bca_course_at_invertis/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/PhysicsStudents",
        "author": "u/___V-E-N-0-M___",
        "question": "Is it worth it to take up a bachelor's degree in physics if I already have a bachelor's in math and computer science?",
        "upvotes": "24",
        "comment": "17",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/PhysicsStudents/comments/12bu4zh/is_it_worth_it_to_take_up_a_bachelors_degree_in/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are some good private colleges for an MCA near Delhi NCR?",
        "answer": "Hi Bhavya Raheja, Good Morning!\n\nAs you know there are many good colleges for MCA near Delhi NCR.\n\nBut I suggest you 2 or 3 private colleges for MCA near Delhi NCR.\n\nFirst of all, I suggest SGT University’s SGT Institute of Engineering & Technology\n\nThis is the best MCA College in Delhi NCR.\n\nYou can also opt for Amity University and others.\n\nThanks & Regards",
        "name": "Nagendra Yadav",
        "views": "36 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-good-private-colleges-for-an-MCA-near-Delhi-NCR",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/cscareerquestions",
        "author": "u/itsthabadmon",
        "question": "I have a B.S. in Computer Science and graduated last year. Since getting laid off in December I have sent out around 700+ applications through job boards. Only one employer bothered to move forward with me before deciding against hiring me. Is the market really this bad or is it me?",
        "upvotes": "209",
        "comment": "125",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/cscareerquestions/comments/11s6wkl/i_have_a_bs_in_computer_science_and_graduated/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is the cost of a management quota seat in RV College of Engineering?",
        "answer": "RVCE, a top institution in Karnataka, has a high cut-off rank for various engineering programs. However, students can still secure a spot through the management quota.\n\nB.E. Engineering Admission in RVCE, Bangalore:\n\nEach year, an entrance exam is held for merit-based admission at RVCE. COMEDK and Karnataka CET are the only entrance exams whose scores are accepted by RVCE for seat allocation.\n\nKarnataka CET or K-CET Entrance Exams:\n\nThe Karnataka Common Entrance Test is a state-level entrance examination for B.E. engineering admissions. In RV College, 45% of the total seats are reserved for Karnataka state students. The Karnataka Exams Authority (KEA) conducts the KCET entrance test. The cut-off rank for RVCE through the K-CET exam varies for all B.E. programs, with an annual tuition fee of INR 90,000.\n\nCOMED-K Entrance Exams:\n\nThe Consortium of Medical, Engineering, and Dental Colleges of Karnataka (COMEDK) is conducted for B.E. admission in Karnataka unaided private engineering colleges. RVCE reserves 30% of the total seats for all state students, including Karnataka students. COMED-K conducts an online entrance test for merit seat admission in RV College of Engineering. The cut-off rank for RVCE through the COMEDK exam varies for different programs, with an annual tuition fee of INR 2 lakhs.\n\nM.Tech Admission in RVCE, Bangalore:\n\nThe Karnataka PGCET entrance exam is conducted for M.Tech program admission at RVCE. The exam is held for PG course admission in Karnataka colleges and is conducted by the Karnataka Examinations Authority (KEA). Students from all over India can register for the PGCET entrance exams.\n\nMCA Admission in RVCE, Bangalore:\n\nKMAT and PGCET exam scores are accepted for MCA admission at RV College. The Karnataka Management Aptitude Test (KMAT) is held for MBA and MCA admission in Karnataka colleges. Students from all over India can apply for the KMAT entrance test.\n\nAdmission in RV College of Engineering through Management Quota:\n\nRVCE offers management quota for direct admission in B.E., M.Tech, and MCA programs. With 25% reserved seats, students can gain admission in RVCE under the management quota by paying higher tuition fees. Many students and parents are willing to pay for admission under the management quota.\n\nEligibility Criteria for RV College of Engineering Management Quota Admission:\n\nRVCE offers management quota admission to students with good academic scores in class 10th, 11th, 12th, or graduation. This ensures that all students complete the course on time and secure campus placements. Eligibility criteria for B.E., M.Tech, and MCA direct admissions are based on minimum marks in relevant subjects and entrance exams.\n\nRVCE Management Quota Admission Process:\n\nDocument Verification: Students must provide essential documents for verification.\nFee Payment: Students must pay the first-year tuition fee and development fee to reserve a seat under the management quota.\nAdmission Allotment Letter: This letter will be issued once the entrance exam scorecard is provided.\n\nRV College of Engineering Management Quota Fee:\n\nAdmission in RV College of Engineering starts in January and continues until all management quota seats are filled. To secure a management quota admission at RV College of Engineering, it's crucial to book a seat as early as possible. Otherwise, you may miss the opportunity if seats get filled.\n\nIn addition to the annual tuition fee, a one-time development fee must be paid, which varies depending on the chosen branch.\n\nRVCE Management quota fees for the 2022 batch are as follows:\n\nCourses : Tuition fee per annum\n\nComputer Science & Engineering : 10 Lakh\n\nInformation Science Engineering : 7 Lakh\n\nMechanical Engineering : 6 Lakh\n\nElectronics & Communication Engineering : 5 Lakh\n\nAerospace Engineering : 5 Lakh\n\nCivil Engineering : 4.5 Lakh\n\nElectrical & Electronics Engineering : 4 Lakh\n\nIndustrial Engineering & Management : 3.5 Lakh\n\nElectronics & Instrumentation Engineering\n\n3 Lakh\n\nChemical Engineering : 3 Lakh\n\nBiotechnology : 3 Lakh\n\nElectronics & Telecommunication Engineering : 3 Lakh\n\nMTech/MCA : 2.5 Lakh",
        "name": "Kailash M",
        "views": "227 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-cost-of-a-management-quota-seat-in-RV-College-of-Engineering",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What are the better opportunities after doing MCA?",
        "answer": "Master of Computer Applications (MCA) is a postgraduate degree in computer science that prepares students for a career in the field of computer technology. After completing an MCA degree, there are several career opportunities available, such as:\n\nSoftware Developer: MCA graduates can work as software developers, designing, developing, and testing software applications for a variety of industries.\nData Analyst: MCA graduates can work as data analysts, extracting insights from large data sets and using that information to inform business decisions.\nBusiness Analyst: MCA graduates can work as business analysts, using their technical skills to understand business processes and systems, and recommending solutions to improve efficiency and performance.\nSystem Analyst: MCA graduates can work as systems analysts, designing and implementing computer systems to meet the needs of businesses and organizations.\nDatabase Administrator: MCA graduates can work as database administrators, managing and maintaining large databases, ensuring they are optimized for performance and security.\nNetwork Administrator: MCA graduates can work as network administrators, designing, implementing, and maintaining computer networks for businesses and organizations.\nCloud Engineer: MCA graduates can work as cloud engineers, designing, implementing, and managing cloud-based systems and infrastructure.\nCyber Security : MCA graduates can work as cyber security professionals, protecting organizations from cyber attacks, protecting sensitive data and ensuring the security of computer networks.\nArtificial Intelligence & Machine Learning: MCA graduates can work as AI/ML engineers, developing and implementing AI and machine learning algorithms to solve real-world problems.\nDigital Marketing: MCA graduates can work in Digital marketing, developing and implementing digital marketing strategies for businesses and organizations.\n\nIt's important to note that the job opportunities for MCA graduates may depend on the specific skills and experiences they have, as well as the job market in their region.",
        "name": "Sagar Gandhi",
        "views": "120 views",
        "link": "https://cahelpinghand.quora.com/Has-CA-New-Scheme-of-Education-and-Training-proposed-by-ICAI-already-implemented-or-yet-to-be-implemented",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Can a merchant cash advance UCC be used to finance a business purchase?",
        "answer": "A merchant cash advance (MCA) UCC filing is a type of financing that provides a lump sum payment to a business in exchange for a percentage of future credit card sales. Typically, this type of financing is used to cover short-term cash flow needs or to fund business expansion. However, it may be possible to use an MCA UCC to finance a business purchase, depending on the specific terms of the financing agreement.\n\nIf the MCA UCC provides enough funds to cover the cost of the business purchase and the terms of the financing agreement allow for the funds to be used in this way, then it may be possible to use the financing for this purpose. However, it is important to carefully review the terms of the financing agreement and to ensure that the business purchase is a viable investment before proceeding with this type of financing. Additionally, it may be advisable to consult with a financial professional or attorney to ensure that this type of financing is the most appropriate option for your specific business needs.",
        "name": "Indian Citizen",
        "views": "15 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Can-a-merchant-cash-advance-UCC-be-used-to-finance-a-business-purchase",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Did people in Medieval Europe care about all the wars going on? What were the concerns of an average farmer from Italy and France, for example, on a day-to-day basis?",
        "answer": "Direct clashes between both sides were very rare. Most of the war would have been the looting and ravaging of the other's territory as in burning down villages, crops, destroying vineyards, killing or taking prisoner peasants, rape and theft etc. As in attacking each other's territory and people rather than attacking each other. They wanted to destroy the other side while not risking battle. The idea of sparing civilians is a fairly modern idea. In past ages, the entire male population might be killed, and the rest sold into slavery. Caesar did it to the Gauls when a tribe rebelled. Caesar says himself that he sold a million people into slavery and killed over a million. Armies were not that large. The largest that the entire Roman military ever got to was 160 000 soldiers in total. Genghis Khans armies were also about 160 000 in total, and they wiped out so many people that the carbon dioxide in the atmosphere decreased the equivalent of all the USA vehicle emissions for a year. Everyone in Central Asia spoke Indo-European languages and looked European. They all now speak Turkic languages and look Asian. Genghis Khans slave soldiers were all Turkic or Tatar as we call them. The history of the dukes of Normandy and their battles with France 1000 - 1300 especially Henry 1 of England in his Norman campaigns to stop France and Anjou harassing his civilians go into detail on this subject, harassing civilians to get the other side to negotiate",
        "name": "Neil McA.",
        "views": "87 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Did-people-in-Medieval-Europe-care-about-all-the-wars-going-on-What-were-the-concerns-of-an-average-farmer-from-Italy-and-France-for-example-on-a-day-to-day-basis",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/FrutigerAero",
        "author": "u/watermelonraj",
        "question": "Windows Live Mesh was a free internet-based file synchronization application, designed to allow files and folders between two or more computers be in sync",
        "upvotes": "79",
        "comment": "5",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/FrutigerAero/comments/11s49vf/windows_live_mesh_was_a_free_internetbased_file/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/Fair_Sense_2444",
        "author": "u/Fair_Sense_2444",
        "question": "Just finished a demo reel for a computer graphics master's program application",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/Fair_Sense_2444/comments/10rm2su/just_finished_a_demo_reel_for_a_computer_graphics/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/gradadmissions",
        "question": "Low GPA in bachelors, decent in Master's. Want to do another master's (electronics / electrical) in another country. Any universities which accept low GPA students in Europe?",
        "upvotes": "3",
        "comment": "0",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/gradadmissions/comments/k8dlu5/low_gpa_in_bachelors_decent_in_masters_want_to_do/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What if South Africa had a majority white population (both English and Afrikaners) before 1910?",
        "answer": "It would now be exactly the same as Australia, New Zealand or Canada or the US or any northern European country. If Africa had never existed, it would make zero difference to the level of development etc of the rest of the world",
        "name": "Neil McA.",
        "views": "117 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-if-South-Africa-had-a-majority-white-population-both-English-and-Afrikaners-before-1910",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/admissionguru1",
        "author": "u/DifficultAccess4651",
        "question": "BCA: Bachelor of Computer Application",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/admissionguru1/comments/zaemvo/bca_bachelor_of_computer_application/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What is the eligibility criteria for MCA?",
        "answer": "The eligibility criteria for MCA is a Bachelor's degree in any discipline with mathematics at 10+2 level or equivalent.",
        "name": "Karen Solvig",
        "views": "349 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-eligibility-criteria-for-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Futurology",
        "author": "u/Sariel007",
        "question": "This mirror reverses how light travels in time. There are already applications in wireless, radar, and optical-computing.",
        "upvotes": "685",
        "comment": "77",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Futurology/comments/120j5ro/this_mirror_reverses_how_light_travels_in_time/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/baltimore",
        "author": "u/digiomg",
        "question": "Does anyone know of computer science internships in baltimore that are still taking applications for summer of 2023. I am an undergraduate sophomore who is looking for any opportunity to gain practical experience.",
        "upvotes": "7",
        "comment": "11",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/baltimore/comments/12bn63q/does_anyone_know_of_computer_science_internships/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is MCA?",
        "answer": "MCA stands for Master of Computer Applications. It is a postgraduate degree program that focuses on providing students with advanced knowledge and skills in the field of computer applications. The program typically covers topics such as software development, programming languages, database management, computer networks, and web development.\n\nMCA is a three-year program that is designed to equip students with both theoretical and practical knowledge, along with hands-on experience through internships and projects. The program is suitable for students who have completed their undergraduate degree in computer science, information technology, or a related field.\n\nUpon completing an MCA degree, students can pursue various career paths such as software developer, database administrator, web developer, system analyst, project manager, and more. With the growing demand for technology and digitalization, the MCA degree has become increasingly popular and sought-after in the job market.",
        "name": "Aniket Sharma",
        "views": "15 views",
        "link": "https://collegeforum.quora.com/What-is-MCA-1",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Is it worth Doing MCA from distance education Lpu?",
        "answer": "Hello there, Doing MCA from distance education mode can be a good option for those who are unable to attend regular classes due to work or other commitments. Lovely Professional University (LPU) offers a distance education program for MCA that is designed to provide students with a comprehensive education in computer science and applications, including software development, database management, and networking.\n\nAdvantages of doing MCA from distance education LPU:\n\nFlexibility: One of the main advantages of distance education is its flexibility. Students can study at their own pace and convenience, without having to worry about attending regular classes.\nCost-effective: Distance education is generally more affordable than regular full-time courses, as it eliminates the cost of on-campus accommodation, commuting, and other expenses.\nCareer advancement: Doing MCA through distance education can help students enhance their knowledge and skills in computer science and applications, which can lead to career advancement and better job opportunities.\n\nHope this clears the doubt!!",
        "name": "Sankalp Shrivastava",
        "views": "31 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-worth-Doing-MCA-from-distance-education-Lpu",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Anu",
        "author": "u/bcaklekun",
        "question": "ANU Master of Computing (Advanced) Application",
        "upvotes": "4",
        "comment": "1",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Anu/comments/xz1vmq/anu_master_of_computing_advanced_application/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/Edubuild",
        "author": "u/Harry_Superman",
        "question": "Online Bachelor of Computer Application | BCA Degree in Vadodara",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/Edubuild/comments/126lxb9/online_bachelor_of_computer_application_bca/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which are the top institutes offering MCA and BCA courses in Delhi NCR?",
        "answer": "Delhi NCR is a home to many private institutes offering a Bachelors as well as a Masters in computer Applications. Are you looking forward to a career as an IT expert?\n\nWell, pursuing your degree from a top college will offer a cutting-edge curricula and pedagogy, top-notch infrastructure and facilities, and chances for you to complete foreign internships.\n\nSome of the top colleges in Delhi NCR for pursuing a BCA/MCA degree are:\n\nWorld College of Technology and Management (WCTM), Gurugram\nInstitute of Management studies (IMS), Noida\nLingaya’s Vidyapeeth, Haryana\nManav Rachna International Institute of Research and Studies (MRIIRS), Faridabad\nAmity University, Noida\nKR Mangalam University, Gurgaon\nInstitute of Professional Excellence and Management (IPEM), Ghaziabad\n\nBCA is one of the most sought-after technical courses because of the growing demand for IT experts both in India and internationally. There is also a lot of demand for MCA graduates due to their technical and analytical skills, which helps them excel in the IT field.\n\nWell, the World College of Technology and Management is the one that checks off all the boxes for being the best college. All the recommendations and pointers I put forward come from an experience of three years at WCTM. Yes, I’m a third year BCA student at WCTM, Gurugram.\n\nThe exposure at this college is commendable. Being an BCA student, there’s a constant need for industrial experience and well as technical guidance under experienced professionals, which WCTM provides. The internships and first-hand experience I’ve had here, has apparently improved me as a professional individual.\n\nHere at WCTM, you don’t just get to learn theories, but practice, experiment, perform during internships and inculcate your skills to excel in the professional world.\n\nFor more information, head over to this link- Best engineering college in Gurgaon | Best engineering college in Delhi NCR | WCTM",
        "name": "Ashok Deshmukh",
        "views": "284 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-top-institutes-offering-MCA-and-BCA-courses-in-Delhi-NCR",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Indian_Academia",
        "author": "u/eksing",
        "question": "Can I go for a master's in computer applications when I have a bachelor in arts?",
        "upvotes": "12",
        "comment": "3",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Indian_Academia/comments/vo7qbh/can_i_go_for_a_masters_in_computer_applications/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Is a BCA better than a DCA?",
        "answer": "The biggest difference is BCA is a full-time UG course and DCA is simply a diploma course. Even for the job, prospective BCA students will have more advantages compared to DCA.\n\nIf your goal is only to get a job in the computer industry then you can do DCA but if you want a designation with a big amount of salary then you should do BCA from the best colleges.\n\nSandip University in Nashik is the best college in India for BCA Program. they have a beautiful college campus and the best part is they give 100% job placement.",
        "name": "Pankaj Gaikwad",
        "views": "126 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-a-BCA-better-than-a-DCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is the future scope of BCA?",
        "answer": "Hello there,\n\nAfter completing your BCA, you are eligible for various entry-level jobs in the IT sector. You can also go for higher studies and pursue an MCA, which will open even more doors to success for you. The BCA degree is an efficient enabler that sets you up for a bright career in terms of jobs.\n\nIf you need any kind of assistance regarding admission feel free to contact through Whatsapp. (Link is in bio)\n\nHappy Learning……….",
        "name": "Suraj Late",
        "views": "72 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-future-scope-of-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Career",
        "author": "u/DifficultAccess4651",
        "question": "Switching Careers to IT security at 34",
        "upvotes": "3",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Career/comments/y648di/switching_careers_to_it_security_at_34/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the requirements for joining the Master of Computer Applications (MCA) program at the Udaipur campus of the Central University of Rajasthan (CTU)? What will be the job prospects for graduates of the MCA program at CTU Udaipur?",
        "answer": "To be eligible for the MCA program at the Udaipur campus of the Central University of Rajasthan (CTU), candidates must have a bachelor's degree in any discipline with Mathematics as one of the subjects at the 10+2 level or at the graduate level. Additionally, they must have secured at least 50% marks in their qualifying exam (45% for SC/ST candidates).\n\nThe admission to the MCA program at CTU is based on the candidate's performance in the Rajasthan MCA Admission Test (RMCAAT) conducted by the Rajasthan Technical University (RTU), Kota.\n\nAs for job prospects, graduates of the MCA program at CTU Udaipur can expect to have a wide range of career opportunities in the field of information technology. They can work as software developers, system analysts, database administrators, web developers, network engineers, and IT consultants, among others. Additionally, they can also pursue higher studies in the field of computer applications or related fields. The average starting salary for MCA graduates in India is around Rs. 3-5 lakhs per annum, but this can vary depending on the company, location, and job profile.",
        "name": "Krishna Sahoo",
        "views": "24 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-requirements-for-joining-the-Master-of-Computer-Applications-MCA-program-at-the-Udaipur-campus-of-the-Central-University-of-Rajasthan-CTU-What-will-be-the-job-prospects-for-graduates-of-the-MCA-program",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What are the top MCA colleges in Bangalore?",
        "answer": "Professional Computer Science MCA is one of the most sought-after graduate courses in India. The demand for MCA courses has seen an upsurge in recent years in India, an MCA graduate has several job opportunities that pay a better salary.\n\nThere are many specializations available related to the student's field of interest which might influence their final choice. However, your bright future depends on how you are going to pick your specialization with MCA from which college.\n\nWith my experience, here is a list of MCA colleges that provides quality education and comprehensive personality development.\n\n· Christ University, Bangalore\n\n· Krupanidhi Degree College, Bangalore\n\n· The Oxford College of Science, Bangalore\n\n· Mount Carmel College, Bangalore\n\n· MS Ramaiah Institute of Technology, Bangalore\n\n· BMS Institute of Technology and Management, Bangalore\n\nKrupanidhi Degree College, Bangalore\n is the best, as it offers a quality education at an affordable price. Even after being a private institution, Krupanidhi’s fee is a little low in comparison to other private colleges and institutions in Bangalore. Their goal is to build future leaders of India by providing a holistic learning environment.",
        "name": "Sheetal Desai",
        "views": "1.4K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-universities-in-the-USA-does-SBI-provide-foreign-education-loans-I-am-not-able-to-find-a-list-online",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "twitter",
        "name": "Amol Mathur",
        "handle": "@Shaitaaaaan",
        "timestamp": "Nov 6, 2009",
        "like": "",
        "replies": "",
        "retweets": "",
        "text": "Replying to \n@iWanderluster",
        "link": "https://twitter.com/Shaitaaaaan/status/5478566711",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/Tejas9311",
        "question": "Bachelor of Computer Application Online",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/Tejas9311/comments/wffl0i/bachelor_of_computer_application_online/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Is it possible to become a data scientist after a BCA in data analytics, or should I go with BCA data science?",
        "answer": "Yes, it is possible to become a data scientist after obtaining a BCA in data analytics. However, you may need to pursue additional training or education to gain specialized skills required for a career in data science. Some ways to acquire these skills include:\n\nPursuing a master's degree in data science or a related field\nCompleting online courses or certifications in data science\nParticipating in data science bootcamps or hackathons\nGaining practical experience through internships or data science projects.\n\nPursuing a BCA in data science may be a better option if you are specifically interested in a career in data science. BCA in data science programs provide a more comprehensive education in data science and related fields, including programming, statistics, machine learning, and data visualization.",
        "name": "Dakota Schey",
        "views": "14 views",
        "link": "https://cimpalscience.quora.com/Is-it-possible-to-become-a-data-scientist-after-a-BCA-in-data-analytics-or-should-I-go-with-BCA-data-science",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Which is better for MCA, IIIT Hyderabad or BITS Pilani?",
        "answer": "Both IIIT Hyderabad and BITS Pilani are renowned institutions for MCA programs in India, and both have their own unique strengths.\n\nIIIT Hyderabad is known for its strong focus on research and innovation, and its MCA program is designed to provide students with a strong foundation in computer science and information technology, as well as hands-on experience in research and development. The faculty at IIIT Hyderabad is highly qualified and experienced in their respective fields, and the institute has state-of-the-art facilities for research and education.\n\nOn the other hand, BITS Pilani is also a top-ranked institution in India, with a strong reputation for its MCA program. The curriculum at BITS Pilani is designed to provide students with a comprehensive understanding of computer science and applications, and the program emphasizes practical knowledge and skills. The institute has a strong focus on industry collaborations and partnerships, which provides students with excellent opportunities for internships and placements.\n\nUltimately, the choice between IIIT Hyderabad and BITS Pilani for MCA will depend on your personal preferences and career goals. You should consider factors such as the curriculum, faculty, facilities, research opportunities, industry collaborations, and placement records of both institutions before making a decision. It is also important to visit the campuses and talk to current students and faculty members to get a better understanding of the culture and learning environment at each institution.",
        "name": "MN Sathi",
        "views": "22 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-better-for-MCA-IIIT-Hyderabad-or-BITS-Pilani",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is future after MCA?",
        "answer": "The future after MCA (Master of Computer Applications) is quite promising, as the field of computer applications is constantly evolving and there is a high demand for skilled professionals in this field. Here are some of the potential career paths after completing an MCA degree:\n\nSoftware Developer: MCA graduates can work as software developers, designing and developing software applications for various industries.\nWeb Developer: MCA graduates can also work as web developers, creating and maintaining websites and web applications.\nData Analyst: With their knowledge of data structures and database management, MCA graduates can also work as data analysts, helping organizations to analyze and interpret large amounts of data.\nSystems Analyst: MCA graduates can also work as systems analysts, analyzing organizational requirements and designing and implementing computer systems to meet those requirements.\nNetwork Administrator: MCA graduates can also work as network administrators, managing and maintaining computer networks for organizations.\nCybersecurity Analyst: With the increasing threat of cyber attacks, MCA graduates can also work as cybersecurity analysts, ensuring the security and privacy of organizational data and systems.\nIT Consultant: MCA graduates can also work as IT consultants, providing expert advice and guidance to organizations on their IT strategy, infrastructure, and applications.\n\nOverall, MCA graduates have a wide range of career opportunities in various industries such as IT, finance, healthcare, and government. With the increasing digitization of business processes and the growing importance of data-driven decision making, the future of MCA graduates is bright and promising.",
        "name": "Ujjwal Matoliya",
        "views": "72 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-future-after-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "I'm a BSc computer science final year student. Should I do MCA from Pune or prepare for placements in Hyderabad?",
        "answer": "In my opinion u should prepare for placements as u can have mca in private colleges as well.\n\nYou will go for job in TCS , Infosys or any MNC if you have any offer . You can also go for any small company job as compare to get admission in MCA .\n\nAfter 2 years of MCA you have to again search for Job but after 2 years of job in IT you will be 2 years ahead than that of those guys who are MCA fresher.\n\nThank you",
        "name": "Mohd Tariq",
        "views": "1.3K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-colleges-to-do-an-MCA-from-Delhi-NCR-Gurugram-or-Faridabad",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/Puzzleheaded-Fox1868",
        "author": "u/Professional-Bad1121",
        "question": "BCA Full Form: Eligibility, Salary, Job Scope, Entrance Exam, Admission 2023, Subjects, Career, Colleges",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/Puzzleheaded-Fox1868/comments/xufhgg/bca_full_form_eligibility_salary_job_scope/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/gradadmissions",
        "author": "u/sddrdz",
        "question": "Research papers vs journals from a well-reputed publication - which is more impressive in terms of your Master's application in Computer Science?",
        "upvotes": "3",
        "comment": "2",
        "timestamp": "Past hours",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/gradadmissions/comments/u8oqgt/research_papers_vs_journals_from_a_wellreputed/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/delhi",
        "author": "u/Harsh00077",
        "question": "IGNOU University",
        "upvotes": "3",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/delhi/comments/10142g0/ignou_university/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/admissionguru1",
        "author": "u/Aiteke",
        "question": "MCA:Master of Computer Applications",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/admissionguru1/comments/zbamae/mcamaster_of_computer_applications/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which is the best college for an online MCA in Bangalore?",
        "answer": "Hello Vinaya,\n\nThere are several colleges in Bangalore that offer online MCA programs. Some of the top colleges that offer online MCA programs in Bangalore include:\n\nChrist University: Christ University is one of the most reputed universities in Bangalore and offers an online MCA program.\nJain University: Jain University is another well-known university in Bangalore that offers an online MCA program.\nPES University: PES University is known for its strong emphasis on research and offers an online MCA program.\nBangalore University: Bangalore University is one of the oldest and most reputable universities in the country and offers an online MCA program.\nAcharya Institute of Technology:Acharya Institute of Technology offers online MCA program.\n\nIt's important to note that the best college for an online MCA program would depend on factors such as your career goals, prior education and experience, and personal preferences. It is advisable to check the accreditation of the institute, the curriculum, faculty qualifications and student reviews before enrolling.\n\nIf it is advisable and informative\n\nplz upvote and share.\n\nThanks",
        "name": "Career Initiative",
        "views": "152 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/I-have-done-a-BSc-in-computer-science-and-I-got-selected-at-Capgemini-and-I-have-accepted-the-offer-I-want-to-do-an-MCA-Should-I-do-a-distance-MCA-an-online-MCA-or-a-regular-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/EducationinIndia",
        "author": "u/getadmision",
        "question": "Bachelor of Computer Applications: How You Grow With This Degree",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/EducationinIndia/comments/zrf6gr/bachelor_of_computer_applications_how_you_grow/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Which are the best colleges to pursue a BCA in North India?",
        "answer": "In the era of digital India, where most of the work is executed through computers, a course like BCA from a top private BCA institute in Delhi NCR will help you find a better career in the field of computer applications. You need to look for infrastructure, facilities, study program and placement policy of the college.\n\nYou will spend your 3 years in the course, so it is obvious that all the minute details should be taken care of with the help of the top private BCA institute in Delhi NCR.\n\nThe department of Computer Science at the World College of Technology and Management envisions imparting practical learning in software development and to train the students to develop soft skills with global standards. Further, enhance their knowledge in the field of Computer Science.\n\nWe provide the best of the infrastructure, faculty that teaches the basics of computer applications and software developments. We have also successfully placed our students in the top-most companies of the world.\n\nWorld College of Technology and Management checks all the boxes for being the best BCA college in Gurgaon.\n\nWe ensure that when our students walk out with good jobs in top companies, they excel in their chosen field and successfully rise in their careers.\n\nThe department owns air-conditioned computer labs connected with servers, online UPS and printers. It also has state of the art computer systems configured with Intel i3, i5 and i7 processors and we even have Gurugram's first ever Apple iOS lab for students.\n\nApart from the different language processors, multimedia packages, MSDN packages and graphic packages. Visual tools and DTP packages are also available. The department has a 100 Mbps leased line internet facility and all the nodes are deployed for students to browse the internet.",
        "name": "Hardik Vashisht",
        "views": "19 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-best-colleges-to-pursue-a-BCA-in-North-India",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/dypimca",
        "author": "u/Adventurous-Band5267",
        "question": "\" D. Y. PATIL INSTITUTE OF MASTER OF COMPUTER APPLICATIONS AND MANAGEMENT-Vision & Mission\"",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/dypimca/comments/zt91lt/d_y_patil_institute_of_master_of_computer/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/C_Programming",
        "author": "u/asbnoida",
        "question": "C programming absolute beginner",
        "upvotes": "24",
        "comment": "25",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/C_Programming/comments/vsfihq/c_programming_absolute_beginner/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/gradadmissions",
        "author": "u/gabseo",
        "question": "[Ph.D. Application] Minimum TOEFL subscore for Machine Learning Department (MLD) in School of Computer Science (SCS)",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/gradadmissions/comments/125mip2/phd_application_minimum_toefl_subscore_for/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What are the top BCA colleges in North India?",
        "answer": "Hi Friends!\n\nIn the era of digital India, where most of the work is executed through computers, a course like BCA from a top private BCA institute in Delhi NCR will help you find a better career in the field of computer applications. You need to look for infrastructure, facilities, study program and placement policy of the college.\n\nYou will spend your 3 years in the course, so it is obvious that all the minute details should be taken care of with the help of the top private BCA institute in Delhi NCR.\n\nThe department of Computer Science at the World College of Technology and Management envisions imparting practical learning in software development and to train the students to develop soft skills with global standards. Further, enhance their knowledge in the field of Computer Science.\n\nWe provide the best of the infrastructure, faculty that teaches the basics of computer applications and software developments. We have also successfully placed our students in the top-most companies of the world.\n\nWorld College of Technology and Management checks all the boxes for being the best BCA college in Gurgaon.\n\nWe ensure that when our students walk out with good jobs in top companies, they excel in their chosen field and successfully rise in their careers.\n\nThe department owns air-conditioned computer labs connected with servers, online UPS and printers. It also has state of the art computer systems configured with Intel i3, i5 and i7 processors and we even have Gurugram's first ever Apple iOS lab for students.\n\nApart from the different language processors, multimedia packages, MSDN packages and graphic packages. Visual tools and DTP packages are also available. The department has a 100 Mbps leased line internet facility and all the nodes are deployed for students to browse the internet. https://www.wctmgurgaon.com",
        "name": "Ashish Kumar",
        "views": "1K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-top-BCA-colleges-in-North-India",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "I'm 30 years old and completely waste my life in preparing for a government job exam but couldn't get anything. What should I can do now? I'm an MCA pass-out in 2016.",
        "answer": "Hey brother, don’t be discouraged by the age. You can still achieve a lot of things in life, you have more then 30 years to live in this world, just start something new, a new carrier path, a business, learn new skills etc to get employed, and also stop comparing yourself with others, it will only demotivate you. Currently i am in the same situation as you, last month i celebrated my 29th borthday (well technically not celebrated, because lack of money…hahaha). I dropped out in college in 2012, started college again in 2016, i also have completed MCA last year, could not get any job in TCS, Wipro..etc because of long education gap, most of my college friend got selected, I am currently living in Hyderabad ameerpet, and doing course on cyber security to start a carrier in it, giving a lot of interviews, i am hopeful that within few months i will get a job.\n\nSince you have a MCA degree, i also suggest you to start your carrier in IT, there are lot of courses like DevOps, Java development, python, data-science etc. Within 6 to 8 month of training you will get a job in these fields. So don’t give up and don’t loose hope in because life is short. Just take care of your health (mental and physical) and work hard towards your bright future. Cheers mate… have a good day",
        "name": "Ajay Isr",
        "views": "4.2K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-colleges-are-best-for-an-MCA-in-Delhi-NCR-decent-fee",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is the admission process for MCA at SVNIT?",
        "answer": "Hello Aspirant,\n\nThe admission process for Master of Computer Applications (MCA) at Sardar Vallabhbhai National Institute of Technology (SVNIT) is as follows:\n\nEligibility Criteria: The candidate must have a Bachelor's degree in any discipline with Mathematics as a subject at the 10+2 level or at the Bachelor's level. The candidate must have secured at least 60% marks or 6.5 CGPA (55% marks or 6.0 CGPA for SC/ST candidates).\nEntrance Exam: The candidate must appear for the NIMCET (National Institute of Technology MCA Common Entrance Test) conducted by NITs. The NIMCET exam is a national-level entrance exam for MCA admissions at NITs.\nOnline Application: The candidate must visit the official website of SVNIT and fill the online application form for MCA admission. The candidate must fill in personal and academic details, upload scanned copies of documents, and pay the application fee.\nCounselling: The eligible candidates are shortlisted based on their NIMCET score and called for counselling. The counselling process involves document verification, choice filling, and seat allocation.\nSeat Allotment: The seats are allotted based on the candidate's NIMCET score, choice filling, and category rank. The candidate must pay the admission fee and report to the institute for further admission formalities.\nFinal Admission: The candidate must complete the admission formalities, submit the necessary documents, and pay the academic fee to confirm their admission.\n\nIt is important to note that the admission process and eligibility criteria may vary from year to year. Therefore, candidates are advised to check the official website of SVNIT for the latest updates and information.\n\nIf it is advisable and informative\n\nplz follow , upvote and share.\n\nThanks",
        "name": "Career Initiative",
        "views": "56 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-admission-process-for-MCA-at-SVNIT",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Is ONLEI Technologies Institute the best or not for summer internship training?",
        "answer": "ONLEI Technologies is the best Institute for summer internship training .\n\nSummer Internship Training according to College and University Curriculum . Students from all courses such as B. Tech, M .Tech, BCA , MCA, Polytechnic, Diploma, Management and so on have the opportunity to register for the internship.\n\nONLEI Technologies announces Summer Training to all the engineering and management students.\n\nResearch Based Summer Training to Leverage Your Career Prospects . If you are an engineering student or pursuing graduate or post-graduate level IT degree then you know that getting summer training is crucial, because it is the best way to acquire practical knowledge in your field.\n\nVisit their Website :\n\nONLEI Technologies - Best Online Training Company\nONLEI Technologies is Best Online Training Company for Python Training , Machine Learning Training , Data Science Training , Digital Marketing Training , Summer\nhttps://onleitechnologies.com/",
        "name": "Aditi A",
        "views": "2.5K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Can-we-study-for-an-MCA-in-IIM",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What are the best MCA colleges in Kerala?",
        "answer": "FISAT\n\nFederal Institute of Science And Technology Mookanoor, Angamaly.\n\nUniversity- KTU\n\nExcellent teaching and guidance\n\nEco friendly Campus\n\nPlacement cells",
        "name": "LiniMariya",
        "views": "1.2K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-bands-or-artists-have-closed-out-a-decade-by-releasing-one-of-their-best-albums",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/sanjanasbm",
        "author": "u/sanjanasbm",
        "question": "master of computer application colleges in mumbai | MCA College",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/sanjanasbm/comments/w8j00r/master_of_computer_application_colleges_in_mumbai/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is the BCA admission process at Amity University, Mumbai?",
        "answer": "To apply for BCA you have to visit: https://www.amity.edu/apply-now.aspx?CampusId=wkO/Ia5mSSk=\n\nfill the form using necessary credentials. And if you are eligible you will receive the call from Amity University Mumbai with further instructions.",
        "name": "AJEEL KARATTIL",
        "views": "6 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-BCA-admission-process-at-Amity-University-Mumbai",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Are there any specific documents that are required to obtain a CIN number, and what is the process for submitting these documents?",
        "answer": "To obtain a CIN (Corporate Identification Number) in India, you need to file an application with the Ministry of Corporate Affairs along with certain documents, including:\n\nMemorandum of Association and Articles of Association\nIdentity proof of directors\nAddress proof of directors\nProof of registered office\nDigital Signature Certificate\n\nTo submit these documents, you need to create an account on the MCA website, obtain a DSC for at least one director, and file the e-form SPICe along with the documents. After paying the prescribed fee, wait for the application to be processed by the MCA, and once approved, the CIN number will be issued.",
        "name": "Why Tap",
        "views": "6 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Are-there-any-specific-documents-that-are-required-to-obtain-a-CIN-number-and-what-is-the-process-for-submitting-these-documents",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "twitter",
        "name": "chalocampus",
        "handle": "@chalocampus",
        "timestamp": "Jun 12, 2009",
        "text": "TMU MORADABAD BCA ADMISSION 2009: Bachelor Degree(BCA)2009 Admissions in Computer Application at Teerthanker Mah.. http://tinyurl.com/nzk2hz",
        "link": "https://twitter.com/chalocampus/status/2129018257",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is full admission process in Christ University Bangalore for BCA?",
        "answer": "The admission process for BCA at Christ University Bangalore involves the following steps:\n\nApplication: Candidates need to apply online on the Christ University website and submit the application form along with the required documents and application fee.\nEntrance Test: The next step is to appear for the Christ University Entrance Test (CUET), which is a computer-based test that assesses a candidate's aptitude, reasoning, and quantitative abilities. The exam also includes questions on general knowledge and current affairs.\nMicro Presentation: Candidates who clear the CUET are then required to give a Micro Presentation (MP). The MP is a 90-second presentation on a given topic, and it is designed to test a candidate's communication and presentation skills.\nPersonal Interview: The final stage of the admission process is the Personal Interview (PI). Shortlisted candidates are called for an interview with the admission committee, which evaluates the candidate's overall profile, academic performance, and extracurricular activities. The PI also assesses a candidate's suitability for the BCA program at Christ University.\nAcademic Performance: The university also considers a candidate's academic performance while shortlisting candidates for admission. The minimum eligibility criteria for admission to the BCA program at Christ University is a pass in 10+2 from a recognized board with Mathematics or Computer Science as a subject.\n\nOverall, the admission process for BCA at Christ University is comprehensive and rigorous, designed to identify candidates with strong academic potential and a passion for technology. Candidates who perform well in the CUET, MP, and PI, and have a strong academic background, are likely to be offered admission to the BCA program at Christ University.",
        "name": "Neshu Chauhan",
        "views": "487 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-full-admission-process-in-Christ-University-Bangalore-for-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/asbnoida",
        "author": "u/digiomg",
        "question": "Know These Most Important Skills If You are a BCA Aspirant!",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/asbnoida/comments/usaxxb/know_these_most_important_skills_if_you_are_a_bca/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Which college is best for the BCA in Delhi?",
        "answer": "Hello Aspirant,\n\nDelhi is home to several reputed colleges offering the Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) program. Here are some of the best colleges for BCA in Delhi:\n\n1. Indira Gandhi National Open University (IGNOU): IGNOU is a well-known university in India offering distance learning courses, and its BCA program is highly popular among students. The program is designed to provide students with a strong foundation in computer applications and includes subjects such as programming languages, computer networks, web technologies, and database management.\n2. Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University (GGSIPU): GGSIPU is a government-affiliated university in Delhi offering a wide range of undergraduate and postgraduate courses, including BCA. The program is designed to provide students with a strong foundation in computer science and includes subjects such as programming languages, software engineering, and database management.\n3. Jagan Institute of Management Studies (JIMS): JIMS is a well-known management institute in Delhi offering a three-year BCA program. The program is designed to provide students with a strong foundation in computer applications and includes subjects such as programming languages, software engineering, and database management. The institute has a strong industry connect and provides students with ample opportunities for internships and placements.\n4. Maharaja Surajmal Institute (MSI): MSI is a private college in Delhi offering a three-year BCA program. The program is designed to provide students with a strong foundation in computer applications and includes subjects such as programming languages, software engineering, and database management. The college has a strong fa...\n\nBecome a subscriber\nUnlock this answer by subscribing to Career Initiative's Space\nFrom $4.17/mo",
        "name": "Career Initiative",
        "views": "109 views",
        "link": "https://careerinitiativesspace.quora.com/Which-college-is-best-for-the-BCA-in-Delhi",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/tiipsindia",
        "author": "u/adityaa_io",
        "question": "Leading BCA College in Greater Noida for Students",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/tiipsindia/comments/10g05fs/leading_bca_college_in_greater_noida_for_students/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the career options after earning a Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA)?",
        "answer": "After earning a Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA), graduates have various career options available to them. Here are some of the most popular career paths for BCA graduates:\n\nSoftware Developer - BCA graduates can work as software developers, building and maintaining software applications for various industries.\nWeb Developer - BCA graduates can work as web developers, creating and maintaining websites and web-based applications.\nDatabase Administrator - BCA graduates can work as database administrators, managing and maintaining databases for organizations.\nSystem Administrator - BCA graduates can work as system administrators, responsible for maintaining and troubleshooting computer systems and networks.\nTechnical Writer - BCA graduates can work as technical writers, creating documentation for software applications and other technical products.\nData Analyst - BCA graduates can work as data analysts, analyzing and interpreting data to provide insights and recommendations for businesses.\nIT Consultant - BCA graduates can work as IT consultants, providing advice and support to organizations on how to use technology to achieve their business objectives.\n\nOverall, the career options available to BCA graduates are diverse and expanding as the field of computer applications continues to evolve.",
        "name": "Ujjwal Matoliya",
        "views": "16 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-options-after-earning-a-Bachelor-of-Computer-Applications-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is the best placement MCA university in India?",
        "answer": "Leading Campus Placement Institution: Chandigarh University\n\nMCA FROM CHANDIGARH UNIVERSITY\n\nThe distance MCA from Chandigarh University is a highly acknowledged technical degree. It seeks to enhance the abilities required for employment in programming and computing. The Institute for Open & Remote Education at Chandigarh University strives to offer its online students helpful e-mentoring, interesting e-content, job placement assistance, and more.\n\nThree years are spent on the course.\n\nThe MCA\n\nThe course aims to strengthen pupils' computer application skills and software development abilities. Students will be better equipped to succeed in the corporate IT sector because to this preparation. MCA courses have a structured curriculum that spans five semesters and are more concentrated on applying topics like IT Skills, Programming Languages, and other similar ideas.\n\nThe MCA programme places a major emphasis on providing students with both a solid theoretical framework and extensive practical experience in the linked fields. It aims to offer fresh, business-focused instruction in applied computer science. Its goal is to create skilled workers who can successfully satisfy the demands of the information technology sector.",
        "name": "Kapish Goyal",
        "views": "7 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-placement-MCA-university-in-India",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/bcaklekun",
        "author": "u/bcaklekun",
        "question": "KLE BEST BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATION COLLEGE IN BANGALORE",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/bcaklekun/comments/11z8kqk/kle_best_bachelor_of_computer_application_college/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Few Abnormal signal intensity areas are seen in watershed region of ACA/MCA & MCA/PCA on left side appearing hypointense on TI and hyperintense on T2w images showing significant diffusion restriction on DWI / ADC mapping. Can someone explain this?",
        "answer": "Ask the physician who requested the scan. No radiologist or neurologist I know would answer this question without knowing more history of the patient, without seeing the images, and if not licensed to practice medicine in the state where the patient lives.",
        "name": "Steven Horii",
        "views": "52 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Few-Abnormal-signal-intensity-areas-are-seen-in-watershed-region-of-ACA-MCA-MCA-PCA-on-left-side-appearing-hypointense-on-TI-and-hyperintense-on-T2w-images-showing-significant-diffusion-restriction-on-DWI-ADC",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/invertis_",
        "author": "u/invertisbareilly",
        "question": "Everything you need to know about the BCA course",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/invertis_/comments/x8rxnw/everything_you_need_to_know_about_the_bca_course/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Which is the best MCA College in terms of Curriculam in India?",
        "answer": "in this era of Information Technology the value of MCA degree has been increased manifold because MCA degree not only unlocks avenues of glittering career but also strengthens technical skills of students for various technologies focused on the conceptual framework. The programme is designed to prepare neat-handed professionals in the sphere of Information Technology. The programme lays stress on the latest programming language and tools to develop cutting-edge software applications.\n\nThis is the most lucrative advantage of MCA degree. Whether you are a fresher or experienced in your field, if your skills match the demand of the industry, then you can demand salary according to your wish. Tech giant companies like IBM, Google, Amazon, Facebook offer lucrative Pay-Packet to talented candidates.\n\nSome engineers also prefer doing MCA after their graduation as it offers better placement opportunities.After MCA, many candidates joined as Software Developer/Programmer/Engineer, IT Desk Troubleshooting, IT system Analyst, Software Application Designer, Software Consultant, Web Designer and Developer, Technical Writer, Systems Developer, Quality Assurance and Software Testing.\n\nIf I talk about Lovely professional University, it offers MCA and MCA Hons with Data science which is in huge demand on today market.\n\nLPU offers MCA and MCA Hons with Data Science in tie with Transorg Analytics. So, I would like to share why you must choose MCA Hons with data science, LPU provides-\n\n1.Innovative Industry –oriented courses and Professional Certifications\n\n2. Seed Money To encourage and support students in entrepreneurship and research activities, various types of seed money funding’s are granted.\n\n3. Industry - Live Projects\n\n4 Industry- Attachment/ Internship\n\n5. Competitions/ Bootcamps/ Codefests\n\nIn addition to this, about the placements, the highest package for 2021–22 session is Rs32 lacs per annum in MCA programmes with 98% of placements records.\n\nHope this information could help you!",
        "name": "Hardik Vashisht",
        "views": "13 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-MCA-College-in-terms-of-Curriculam-in-India",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Indians_StudyAbroad",
        "author": "u/KoalaOk3336",
        "question": "Want to pursue MsC Cybersecurity in Ireland. What is the situation currently?",
        "upvotes": "3",
        "comment": "1",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Indians_StudyAbroad/comments/120j689/want_to_pursue_msc_cybersecurity_in_ireland_what/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which college is best for MCA / MSc IT with affordable fees?",
        "answer": "Hello there,\n\nHere are some top colleges for MCA/MSc IT with affordable fees:\n\nVellore Institute of Technology (VIT)\nManipal Academy of Higher Education (MAHE)\nSymbiosis Institute of Computer Studies and Research (SICSR)\nAmity University\nChrist University\nJain University\nDelhi University\nUniversity of Mumbai\nPune University\nBangalore University\nPSG College of Technology\nSRM Institute of Science and Technology\nChandigarh University\n\nHope it helps, for more details regarding college and admission feel free to contact 📲6205238449(Call/WhatsApp)\n\nThank you❤",
        "name": "Anjali Mishra",
        "views": "44 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-degree-is-better-BTech-or-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/UCI",
        "author": "u/Cybedra",
        "question": "“Bachelor in Information and Computer Sciences/Undeclared”? (Chose CS on application)",
        "upvotes": "4",
        "comment": "2",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/UCI/comments/11vcvpk/bachelor_in_information_and_computer/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are the benefits of completing an MBA or an MCA before taking up a CPA course?",
        "answer": "Completing an MBA or an MCA before taking up a CPA course can provide a range of benefits such as:\n\nStrong foundation: An MBA or MCA program can provide a strong foundation in business, finance, accounting, and management concepts that can be useful in the CPA course.\nComplimentary knowledge: MBA or MCA programs can provide complimentary knowledge and skills to the CPA course, making the candidate more well-rounded and versatile.\nCareer options: With an MBA or MCA degree in hand, candidates may have more career options available to them than with just a CPA qualification.\nNetworking opportunities: MBA or MCA programs offer excellent networking opportunities that can help candidates in their professional career.\nSalary potential: An MBA or MCA degree can increase a candidate's salary potential and earning power, even when combined with a CPA qualification.\n\nHowever, it is important to note that an MBA or MCA degree is not a requirement for taking up a CPA course, and candidates can still become successful CPAs without one. The decision to pursue an MBA or MCA before taking up a CPA course should be based on the individual's career goals and aspirations.",
        "name": "College Sakha",
        "views": "13 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-benefits-of-completing-an-MBA-or-an-MCA-before-taking-up-a-CPA-course",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is the scope of MCA in India?",
        "answer": "Master of Computer Applications (MCA) is a postgraduate program that offers advanced knowledge and skills in computer science and applications. MCA graduates have a strong foundation in programming languages, software development, database management, and system administration, making them suitable for various job roles in the IT industry. The scope of MCA in India is vast, with numerous opportunities for MCA graduates in various sectors.\n\nHere are some of the job roles that MCA graduates can pursue in India:\n\nSoftware Developer: MCA graduates can work as software developers, where they design, develop, and maintain software applications for organizations. They can work in various domains such as web development, mobile application development, and enterprise application development.\nSystem Administrator: MCA graduates can work as system administrators, where they manage and maintain the IT infrastructure of an organization. They can manage servers, databases, networks, and security systems to ensure the smooth functioning of IT operations.\nDatabase Administrator: MCA graduates can work as database administrators, where they manage and maintain the databases of an organization. They can design, implement, and maintain databases to ensure data security, integrity, and availability.\nIT Consultant: MCA graduates can work as IT consultants, where they provide advisory services to organizations on various IT-related issues. They can help organizations in system design, technology selection, and IT strategy development.\nData Analyst: MCA graduates can work as data analysts, where they analyze and interpret data to provide insights and recommendations to organizations. They can use various tools and techniques to analyze data and develop reports and dashboards for decision-making.\nCybersecurity Analyst: MCA graduates can work as cybersecurity analysts, where they identify, assess, and mitigate cybersecurity risks in an organization. They can use various tools and techniques to identify vulnerabilities and develop strategies to secure the IT infrastructure.\nProject Manager: MCA graduates can work as project managers, where they plan, execute, and monitor IT projects in an organization. They can manage teams, budgets, and timelines to ensure the successful completion of IT projects.\n\nThe scope of MCA in India is not limited to the IT industry. MCA graduates can also pursue careers in other sectors such as finance, healthcare, and education, where technology plays a crucial role. Here are some of the sectors where MCA graduates can find job opportunities in India:\n\nBanking and Finance: MCA graduates can work in the banking and finance sector, where they can develop software applications for banking operations, manage databases, and provide IT consulting services.\nHealthcare: MCA graduates can work in the healthcare sector, where they can develop software applications for patient management, electronic health records, and medical billing.\nEducation: MCA graduates can work in the education sector, where they can develop e-learning applications, manage learning management systems, and provide IT consulting services to educational institutions.\nGovernment: MCA graduates can work in the government sector, where they can work on various IT projects such as e-governance, digitalization, and cybersecurity.\nEntrepreneurship: MCA graduates can also start their businesses and offer IT services such as software development, system administration, and IT consulting.\n\nThe scope of MCA in India is also growing due to the increasing demand for IT professionals in various sectors. The IT industry in India is expected to grow at a CAGR of 9.2% from 2020 to 2025, according to a report by NASSCOM. This growth is driven by various factors such as the adoption of new technologies, digitalization, and the increasing demand for IT services.",
        "name": "Aniket Sharma",
        "views": "21 views",
        "link": "https://collegeforum.quora.com/What-is-the-scope-of-MCA-in-India",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Is it okay if I do a BCA from a local college and do an MCA in a reputed college because of financial reasons?",
        "answer": "Yes, it's absolutely fine. Since you are not focussing over the placements after your BCA, so knowledge is more important over here. After BCA, you should choose your college wisely for MCA as it is going to have a big impact on your corporate career and overall profile as well.",
        "name": "Atul Pandey",
        "views": "257 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-okay-if-I-do-a-BCA-from-a-local-college-and-do-an-MCA-in-a-reputed-college-because-of-financial-reasons",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/Adventurous-Band5267",
        "author": "u/theweirdindiangirl",
        "question": "MCA full form: Subjects, Career, Top Colleges in India, Entrance Exam, Admission Process, Salary, Job Scope.",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/Adventurous-Band5267/comments/whn6ym/mca_full_form_subjects_career_top_colleges_in/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "twitter",
        "name": "Demon Hunter",
        "handle": "@rockstar_narang",
        "timestamp": "Oct 6, 2009",
        "text": "Replying to \n@CyberEddieGr",
        "link": "https://twitter.com/rockstar_narang/status/4652489235",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Okay this might sound ridiculous to many and honestly it still sounds ridiculous to me too. I am seventeen. So the first thing you must be wondering, why is a 17th year old here. It might be answered by suspicions like \"maybe they r curious who knows\". i am curious fine enough but i wont say i am for sure, but can i admit that might be in a twin flame connection. I am already aware of what a twin flame is, with all its pros and cons attached. I experienced it as a person myself. I know it sounds ridiculous and it is honestly kinda childish due to the fact that I havent experienced a life yet. I havent, lets be honest. i know that due to that thinking i gave up considering it a twinflame connection all together. there r many different types of connections in the spirtiual realm. Maybe its one of those, but there are things i cant just ignore now. This is way too intense(again how intense things can a 17 yr old experience) but its intense enough for me, i can say. So i wanna know, is it possible for me to actually have a twinflame right now or have an awakening for one right now for like i wasnt into twinflames and soulmate related things before this had happened to me. I will always come as far as to say that i didnt believe in it. And thats what my thinking was when he came around too. I wont say that it was like i hated it or anything on that level just that i wasnt worrying about one and if there was one i wasnt exactly concerned for them. Since i was having enough things to work upon as a person and as i mentioned, am too young to worry about those during that days for i was already coming out of an awakening period. But once he came around, its a total uno reverse situation on my head so i wont even try getting started on that. But is it possible for it to actually occur for me?",
        "answer": "Yes,twinflames meet any time irrespective of their age. I met my twinflame at age 10, not at all aware of these connections. But we felt an immense care and love at that age itself. Age doesn’t matter. Age is just a thing in matrx world and divine connections are beyond that.",
        "name": "Abc Bca",
        "views": "735 views",
        "link": "https://onthetwinflamejourney.quora.com/Okay-this-might-sound-ridiculous-to-many-and-honestly-it-still-sounds-ridiculous-to-me-too-I-am-seventeen-So-the-first",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which mca books to refer to crack NIMCET?",
        "answer": "There are few books you can consider : Self scorer, Rd sharma objective , MCA full package of arihant\n\nthese books will help you from going basic to advance",
        "name": "Abhijeet Saxena",
        "views": "596 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-is-the-placement-in-Christ-University-for-the-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is MCA?",
        "answer": "MCA stands for Master of Computer Applications. It is a postgraduate degree program that focuses on providing students with advanced knowledge and skills in the field of computer applications. The program typically covers topics such as software development, programming languages, database management, computer networks, and web development.\n\nMCA is a three-year program that is designed to equip students with both theoretical and practical knowledge, along with hands-on experience through internships and projects. The program is suitable for students who have completed their undergraduate degree in computer science, information technology, or a related field.\n\nUpon completing an MCA degree, students can pursue various career paths such as software developer, database administrator, web developer, system analyst, project manager, and more. With the growing demand for technology and digitalization, the MCA degree has become increasingly popular and sought-after in the job market.",
        "name": "Aniket Sharma",
        "views": "15 views",
        "link": "https://collegeforum.quora.com/What-is-MCA-1",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/IntltoUSA",
        "author": "u/dandelion66",
        "question": "Indian trying to find Universities in the US",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "6",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/IntltoUSA/comments/10is8gy/indian_trying_to_find_universities_in_the_us/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are the distance education courses offered by Lovely Professional University, Delhi?",
        "answer": "Hello reader,\n\nI hope you are doing well,\n\nLovely Professional University (LPU) is a private university located in Jalandhar, Punjab, India. It offers various distance education courses in different fields of study. Some of the courses offered by LPU in distance mode are:\n\nMBA - The distance MBA program offered by LPU is a two-year program that covers various aspects of management, including marketing, finance, human resources, and operations management.\nBBA - The distance BBA program offered by LPU is a three-year program that provides a foundation in business and management principles.\nMCA - The distance MCA program offered by LPU is a two-year program that provides a comprehensive understanding of computer applications and software development.\nBCA - The distance BCA program offered by LPU is a three-year program that provides a foundation in computer science and application development.\nB.Com - The distance B.Com program offered by LPU is a three-year program that covers various aspects of commerce, including accounting, taxation, and finance.\nPGDCA - The distance PGDCA program offered by LPU is a one-year program that provides a comprehensive understanding of computer applications and software development.\n\nLPU also offers various diploma and certificate courses in different fields of study. The distance education courses offered by LPU are designed to provide quality education to students who cannot attend regular classes due to various reasons.\n\nI hope the information shared by ne was helpful to you!\n\nThank you:)",
        "name": "Vidushi Sharma",
        "views": "39 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-distance-education-courses-offered-by-Lovely-Professional-University-Delhi",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/PhD",
        "author": "u/Valuable-Fishing281",
        "question": "I studied Linguistics in college (I have a master degree) and now I want to apply for a PhD program. Can I choose computational linguistics as my area of research? Will the University accept my application if I did?",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "12",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/PhD/comments/vkm3ll/i_studied_linguistics_in_college_i_have_a_master/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/todayilearned",
        "author": "u/CuriousDepartureOne",
        "question": "TIL John von Newmann was a child prodigy who could divide 8-digit numbers in his head by age 6. By age 8, he was fluent in Ancient Greek, had mastered calculus and would amuse his parents' friends by reciting book pages after just glancing at them. He also developed the modern computer architecture.",
        "upvotes": "13.9k",
        "comment": "471",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/zeutdf/til_john_von_newmann_was_a_child_prodigy_who/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Is there any scope in BCA and MCA?",
        "answer": "Yes, there is a lot of scope in both BCA (Bachelor of Computer Applications) and MCA (Master of Computer Applications) degrees. The IT industry is constantly evolving and growing, and there is a high demand for skilled professionals in the field of computer applications.\n\nHere are some of the career options and job opportunities available for BCA and MCA graduates:\n\nSoftware Developer: BCA and MCA graduates can work as software developers and develop software applications for different industries.\nWeb Developer: BCA and MCA graduates can work as web developers and design, develop and maintain websites and web applications.\nDatabase Administrator: BCA and MCA graduates can work as database administrators and manage, design, and maintain databases for various organizations.\nNetwork Administrator: BCA and MCA graduates can work as network administrators and manage and maintain computer networks for organizations.\nSystem Analyst: BCA and MCA graduates can work as system analysts and analyze business requirements and recommend technology solutions to meet the requirements.\nIT Consultant: BCA and MCA graduates can work as IT consultants and provide consulting services to organizations on various aspects of IT.\nProject Manager: BCA and MCA graduates can work as project managers and manage IT projects for organizations.\nData Analyst: BCA and MCA graduates can work as data analysts and analyze and interpret data to provide insights to organizations.\n\nIn addition, BCA and MCA graduates can also start their own software development companies or become freelancers and work on projects independently.\n\nOverall, there is a lot of scope and job opportunities in both BCA and MCA degrees, and the demand for skilled professionals in the field of computer applications is expected to grow in the future.",
        "name": "Dipak Singh",
        "views": "15 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-there-any-scope-in-BCA-and-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/Broad-Worldliness7",
        "author": "u/Broad-Worldliness7",
        "question": "What to Expect After Completing an Online BCA Degree",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/Broad-Worldliness7/comments/ywlh06/what_to_expect_after_completing_an_online_bca/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "I completed diploma in mechanical engineering and distance BA degree. Am I eligible to study distance MCA course?",
        "answer": "In general, eligibility requirements for a distance MCA course may vary depending on the institution offering the course. However, in most cases, a candidate must have a Bachelor's degree in Computer Applications or a related field, such as Information Technology or Computer Science, to be eligible for a distance MCA course.\n\nWhile having a diploma in mechanical engineering and a distance BA degree may not be directly related to computer applications, some institutions may consider these qualifications as eligible for admission to a distance MCA course if the candidate has a sufficient background in mathematics, statistics, and computer programming. Therefore, it is best to check with the specific institution offering the course to determine their eligibility criteria and requirements.",
        "name": "Eduxprts",
        "views": "15 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/I-completed-diploma-in-mechanical-engineering-and-distance-BA-degree-Am-I-eligible-to-study-distance-MCA-course",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/AskComputerScience",
        "author": "u/vivans720",
        "question": "Can i become a data scientist?",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/AskComputerScience/comments/12beujn/can_i_become_a_data_scientist/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is the eligibility for an MCA in SRM?",
        "answer": "Hello Aspirant,\n\nTo be eligible for an MCA (Master of Computer Applications) program at SRM Institute of Science and Technology, the candidate should meet the following criteria:\n\nThe candidate should have a Bachelor's degree in Computer Applications (BCA) or a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science Engineering (B.E./B.Tech CSE) or any equivalent degree from a recognized university with a minimum of 50% marks in aggregate.\nThe candidate should have studied Mathematics as a subject in their 10+2 level or in graduation.\nThe candidate should have a valid score in the entrance exam conducted by the university or any other national level exam like NIMCET or TANCET.\n\nIt's important to note that eligibility criteria may vary depending on the university and the specific MCA program offered. Therefore, it's recommended to check the official website of SRM Institute of Science and Technology or contact the admissions office for detailed and up-to-date information.\n\nIf it is advisable and informative\n\nplz follow , upvote and share.\n\nThanks",
        "name": "Career Initiative",
        "views": "121 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-eligibility-for-an-MCA-in-SRM",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Indian_Academia",
        "author": "u/Flash_Discard",
        "question": "Guys how hard is Master’s of Computer Applications(MCA)?",
        "upvotes": "11",
        "comment": "3",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Indian_Academia/comments/xx1q5q/guys_how_hard_is_masters_of_computer/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/snowrunner",
        "author": "u/dypimca",
        "question": "ZiKZ 566A in Wisconsin: jack of all trades, master of none. What do you think would be the best application for it?",
        "upvotes": "39",
        "comment": "20",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/snowrunner/comments/11g9e3o/zikz_566a_in_wisconsin_jack_of_all_trades_master/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Is a BCA tough for an arts student?",
        "answer": "I want to tell you, with proper guidance nothing is tough we only need a good college with good exposure. My friends are pursing this course at Lovely professional University. For students interested in pursuing a professional degree, the Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) is a rewarding alternative. The course lasts three years, with each year divided into two semesters. As computers have become a necessity in today's world, the demand for this course is growing by the day. I want to recommend you a college with better exposure which is also leading in these days. Lovely professional University. After completing the course from this university, students will have a thorough understanding of how to create computer programmes that meet the needs of users utilising a variety of programming languages such as C, C++, Python, Java, and others. With solid academic understanding of computer applications, an entry-level computer applications software engineer can readily find work in big IT businesses.\n\nIt is a type of course in which the student is taught all there is to know about computers. He or she learns about a variety of programming languages, including C, C++, Java, and Python. Networking, Multimedia, Business Communication, DBMS and Internet Programming, and Cyber Law are among the disciplines he or she will study.",
        "name": "Ayush Raj",
        "views": "5.2K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-a-BCA-tough-for-an-arts-student",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/cgcadmission2023",
        "author": "u/cgcadmission2023",
        "question": "Career Scope in BCA",
        "upvotes": "2",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/cgcadmission2023/comments/11rpaii/career_scope_in_bca/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which is the best college to do an MCA in Delhi, India?",
        "answer": "Hi Friends,\n\nMasters in computer applications is a professional post-graduation course in Computer Applications. This course trains the students to prepare for a flourishing IT career. It consists of various programs, application software, computer architecture, operating systems and many more.\n\nWell, having a BCA degree will definitely secure you a job, but furthermore, having an MCA degree would refine your skills and provide you with an added exposure. An MCA degree from a top private institute with ensure rewarding job opportunities at your doorstep.\n\nAre you confused about what to do after BCA? Are you unable to decide the best college for yourself for doing an MCA from Delhi, NCR?\n\nI would recommend you the World College of Technology and Management (WCTM), Gurugram. MCA degree from WCTM will help students who want to delve deeper into the world of technology and computers.\n\nChoosing the top MCA College in Delhi NCR will not only get you a post-graduation degree but also open up new doors of opportunity in the government and private sector. This two-year degree will be a complete professional making for an IT sector in India and abroad.\n\n● The faculty at the World College of Technology and Management is amongst the most experienced professionals in their respective fields.\n\n● The exposure at WCTM is something which will help in the holistic development of its students.\n\n● Life at WCTM also comes with a lot of amazing fests and celebrity meets. These make up some college memories that you will cherish forever.\n\n● WCTM also comes with very affordable fee structure and hostel facilities too.\n\nTo know more about the college, check the link-\n\nhttps://www.google.com/url?sa=t&rct=j&q=&esrc=s&source=web&cd=&ved=2ahUKEwjFrPbNj8T7AhUb0XMBHUieASgQFnoECBwQAQ&url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.wctmgurgaon.com%2F&usg=AOvVaw0TSkJZpwv07IiQRthKMYrR\nhttps://www.google.com/url?sa=t&rct=j&q=&esrc=s&source=web&cd=&ved=2ahUKEwjFrPbNj8T7AhUb0XMBHUieASgQFnoECBwQAQ&url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.wctmgurgaon.com%2F&usg=AOvVaw0TSkJZpwv07IiQRthKMYrR",
        "name": "Monisha R",
        "views": "2.5K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-college-to-do-an-MCA-in-Delhi-India",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Which is the best course, a BCA or a BBA?",
        "answer": "It depends on your interests and career goals.\n\nBCA (Bachelor of Computer Applications) is a technical course that focuses on computer science and programming skills. It is an undergraduate degree program in the field of computer applications. The course is designed to provide students with a strong foundation in computer science and programming concepts, and practical skills to develop software applications and information systems.\n\nBBA (Bachelor of Business Administration) is a business management course that covers topics such as finance, marketing, human resources, and operations management. It is an undergraduate degree program in the field of business administration. The course is designed to provide students with a strong foundation in business management concepts, principles, and practices.\n\nHere are many colleges and universities that offer BCA programs. It is important to research and choose a college that fits your specific needs and interests. Here are some well-known colleges in India that offer BCA programs:\n\nMedhavi Skills University, Sikkim\nChrist University, Bangalore\nSymbiosis Institute of Computer Studies and Research, Pune\nLoyola College, Chennai\nDepartment of Computer Science, Delhi University\n\nThere are many universities and colleges that offer BBA programs. It is important to research and choose a university that fits your specific needs and interests. Here are some well-known universities in India that offer BBA programs:\n\nIndian Institute of Management (IIM), Indore\nIndian Institute of Technology (IIT), Delhi\nMedhavi Skills University, Sikkim\nChrist University, Bangalore\nSymbiosis International University, Pune\n\nIt is important to note that the \"best\" university for you depends on your individual needs, interests, and career goals. It is recommended that you research the programs offered by each university, faculty qualifications, infrastructure, placement opportunities, and student support services before making a decision.\n\nBCA (Bachelor of Computer Applications), it covers topics such as software development, database management, web design, and computer networks. BCA graduates can work as software developers, web developers, system administrators, and IT managers.\n\nThe BCA program typically takes 3 years to complete and covers subjects such as programming languages, computer networks, database management, web development, software engineering, and computer architecture. Students are also given opportunities to work on real-world projects to gain practical experience in software development.\n\nAfter completing a BCA program, students can pursue careers in software development, web development, system administration, IT management, and other related fields. They can also opt for higher education, such as a Master of Computer Applications (MCA) or other related postgraduate programs.\n\nBBA (Bachelor of Business Administration), graduates can work as business analysts, marketing executives, human resources managers, and project managers. The BBA program typically takes 3 years to complete and covers subjects such as finance, accounting, economics, marketing, human resource management, operations management, and organizational behavior. Students are also given opportunities to work on real-world projects and internships to gain practical experience in the business world.\n\nAfter completing a BBA program, students can pursue careers in business management, finance, marketing, human resources, and other related fields. They can also opt for higher education, such as a Master of Business Administration (MBA) or other related postgraduate programs.\n\nIf you are interested in a career in computer science and programming, then BCA would be the better option for you. However, if you are interested in business management and want to work in areas such as finance, marketing, and human resources, then BBA would be the better option for you. Ultimately, the best course for you would be the one that aligns with your interests, strengths, and career goals.",
        "name": "Amanaya Bhatt",
        "views": "101 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-course-a-BCA-or-a-BBA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/jobs",
        "author": "u/Affectionate-Main999",
        "question": "What can be done after BCA(Bachelor in. computer application)",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "1",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/jobs/comments/uukuol/what_can_be_done_after_bcabachelor_in_computer/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "How is SGT University for B Tech in mechanical Engineering?",
        "answer": "SGT University is best for B Tech in Mecanical Engineering in Gurgaon & Haryana.\n\nThis university provides best facilities to the engineering students. SGT is fully equiped with High technology labs.\n\nDEPARTMENTS @ FACULTY OF ENGINEERING & TECHNOLOGY\n\nThere are 4 departments in Engineering at SGT University.\n\nDepartment of Civil Engineering\n\nDepartment of Computer Science\n\nDepartment of Mechanical Engineering\n\nDepartment of Electrical Engineering\n\nThey provide many courses in the field of Engineering.\n\nB tech in civil engineering\n\nB tech in compture science\n\nB tech in mechanical engineering\n\nB tech in electronics engineering\n\nBCA in artificial intellegence\n\nBCA in cloud computing\n\nm tech in civil engineering\n\nm tech in compture science\n\nm tech in mechanical engineering\n\nm tech in electronics engineering\n\nSGT University also provides phd in engineering courses.",
        "name": "Nagendra Yadav",
        "views": "16 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-is-SGT-University-for-B-Tech-in-mechanical-Engineering",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "I have no work experience in the IT sector, I’m just pursuing my MCA from a B-category college. My age is 41 now. Can I get a job in IT sector after completion of MCA?",
        "answer": "So my question is --- do you have technical skills? if Yes, then you will definitely get a job in IT but if No then also there are so many jobs where you don't need so much technical skills. Like (You can learn software testing).",
        "name": "Brother's Photography",
        "views": "1.8K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/I-want-to-become-a-software-developer-but-I-am-not-from-engineering-background-is-it-possible-for-me",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Morocco",
        "author": "u/theanxiousnerd",
        "question": "1337 + online Bachelor in computer science",
        "upvotes": "11",
        "comment": "61",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Morocco/comments/1231t8v/1337_online_bachelor_in_computer_science/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Which are the good colleges for a BCA?",
        "answer": "LPU is reputed to have the largest co-location network. The LPU School of Computer Application is ranked among the top four institutes of computer application in North India by NASSCOM.\n\nThe program is designed to develop programming skills to create efficient software with optimized resources to develop /website/cloud/mobile applications. Eligibility for the course is a Pass with 50% of the total marks at 10+2 (with English) or equivalent.\n\nIndustry certifications, MOOCs, hackathons/events, competitive events alongside the Curriculum, workshops, invited talks, educational trips, live projects, incubation projects, community projects, projects with NGOs, etc. are an integral part of the curriculum.\n\nCourse highlights include Projects, Contemporary Curriculum, Interdisciplinary Minors, Industry Visits, Holistic Development, Professional Development, Software Skills, Industry Immersion,\n\nStudents have instant access to the latest tech labs such as iMac, SAP, etc. The BCA course at LPU is designed to develop programming skills to create resource-efficient and optimized software to develop website, cloud and mobile applications. Students are prepared for topics such as programming languages, hardware and software, computer networks, World Wide Web, database management, logic, multimedia, etc. Offer 19 .25 and the average package is 3.1LPA.\n\nBCA graduates have a good reach in jobs like web developer, web designer, network administrator, web administrator, systems, computer programmer, Software Developers, Software Testers, etc. depending on the skills you acquire during your BCA. Various companies, organizations and multinationals offer BCA candidates the positions listed above.",
        "name": "Ria Agnihotri",
        "views": "42 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-good-colleges-for-a-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "How is the placement in Christ University for the MCA?",
        "answer": "The average package is between 5-7 lacs. In 2017, Amazon offered the highest package of 16 lacs, while many companies offered the lowest package of 4.5 lacs. As a result, if you are an average student, you will have plenty of opportunities to demonstrate your’s worth.\n\nChrist University MCA has 146 seats in total, and classes are held in the department itself. When compared to the rest of other Bangalore colleges provides it.\n\nAxis Bank, Deloitte, ICICI, Infosys, LG Electronics, Nestle, Shopclues, Tata Power, and TCS are among the hiring firms.",
        "name": "Ashu Mantri",
        "views": "4.2K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-online-MCA-from-Jain-university-is-worth-it",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/antiwork",
        "author": "u/georgetelegraph72",
        "question": "computer programming job application",
        "upvotes": "17.2k",
        "comment": "376",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/antiwork/comments/zsl806/computer_programming_job_application/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/tcbusinessschool",
        "author": "u/Harild123",
        "question": "Career Opportunities Following 12th Grade In It",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/tcbusinessschool/comments/tue0mb/career_opportunities_following_12th_grade_in_it/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/codingbootcamp",
        "author": "u/blackapple56",
        "question": "I'll graduate Codesmith this summer. I'm considering enrolling in a Computer Science Bachelor's program. Will that hurt my resume?",
        "upvotes": "6",
        "comment": "16",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/codingbootcamp/comments/12c4y65/ill_graduate_codesmith_this_summer_im_considering/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "If Uganda has the most gold in the nation miner, why is the country not one of the top richest countries?",
        "answer": "From your question I can see that you do not have any understanding of economics. I dont think I can give you a short answer except to say that printing money doesnt make you rich . Money is only of value in terms of what it can buy. The goods you can buy are what gives the money value. Likewise a country is only rich in terms of what it produces. Its workers get paid based on the amount of value they produce. By the way Uganda is not the top gold producer. Likewise a person can only be paid the amount of value that he produces. Ugandan workers do not produce much value. Japanese workers do produce a lot of value so they get higher wages.\n\nBelow is a link to a fairly short book that will give you a better understanding of economics and help you to answer questions like this yourself in future\n\nBasic Economics: A Common Sense Guide to the Economy\nBasic Economics: A Common Sense Guide to the Economy eBook : Sowell, Thomas: Amazon.co.uk: Kindle Store\nhttps://www.amazon.co.uk/Basic-Economics-Thomas-Sowell-ebook/dp/B06XCH5NGZ/",
        "name": "Neil McA.",
        "views": "698 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-average-salary-of-an-MCA-graduate-in-India-What-are-some-companies-that-hire-them-with-high-salaries",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "How can I register for LLP?",
        "answer": "To register for an LLP (Limited Liability Partnership) in India, you will need to follow these steps:\n\nObtain a Digital Signature Certificate (DSC) and a Designated Partner Identification Number (DPIN): All designated partners of the LLP must have a DSC and DPIN, which can be obtained by submitting an online application on the Ministry of Corporate Affairs (MCA) website.\nReserve a name for your LLP: You can check the availability of your desired LLP name on the MCA website and reserve it by filing the LLP name reservation form online.\nPrepare the LLP agreement: The LLP agreement outlines the rights, duties, and obligations of the partners and the LLP. It can be prepared by a chartered accountant, company secretary, or lawyer.\nFile the incorporation form: After obtaining the DSC and DPIN, and preparing the LLP agreement, you can file the incorporation form online on the MCA website.\nPayment of fees: You will need to pay the prescribed fees at the time of filing the incorporation form.\nObtain the Certificate of Incorporation: After the incorporation form is approved, you will receive a Certificate of Incorporation from the Registrar of Companies, which confirms the creation of your LLP.\n\nIt is recommended that you engage the services of a professional, such as a chartered accountant or company secretary, to ensure that the registration process is completed correctly and in a timely manner.",
        "name": "Mr. Informat",
        "views": "52 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-register-for-LLP",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Can I replace my car battery with a lithium battery?",
        "answer": "I better jump in here before more wrong information is posted. I design Li-ion battery packs for cars, motorcycles, golf carts, buses, trucks, boats, airplanes, etc. for many years, and I work with an excellent packer in China who builds these Li-ion packs for hundreds of applications by the container loads each week. So, we have lots of practical experience.\n\nFor many years, there have been drop-in replacements of Li-ion batteries for the 12V car battery. The BMS (battery management system) is programmed to accept the voltage and current from the car’s existing alternator charging system, making sure the Li-ion cells do not get over-charged or over-discharged. There are six different Li-ion formulations in the Li-ion family of rechargeable chemistries (LMO, LCO, NCA, NMC, LFP, LTO). Tesla started with the NCA, then to NMC, and now LFP in China market.\n\nThe LFP (LiFePO4) is the most popular chemistry for automotive applications being one of the thermally safest formulas in the Li-ion family. LFP has around 3 times the energy per pound or kg than lead-acid batteries. So, around 1/3 to 1/2 the weight of a flooded or AGM battery. It is also smaller, but the same size or group dimensions are maintained to ensure it looks and fits like a 1:1 drop-in replacement.\n\nThere are other Li-ion chemistries that have greater energy per lb or higher power output. For example, I recently designed a marine engine starting battery capable of 1,500 MCA, but my final design was able to output 3,000 MCA. The size was less than 1/3 the size and the weight was less than 1/4 that of an AGM equivalent battery. My Li-ion packs can operate at -30°C (-22°F), and still retain more than 70% of their max capacity. At that temperature, AGM will be lower than 40% of its max capacity. So, the Li-ion battery will have many more cranks left by the time the AGM batteries throw their towel in.\n\nSo, yes, you can replace your lead-acid car battery with a Li-ion battery. It will last at least 3-4 times longer, so the total ownership cost will be much less than a lead acid battery. Amazon will give you a rough idea of the costs.\n\nAddendum\n\nThere are many good comments below, and also some are from less experienced folks; which is good, because this is the main reason I bother posting on a forum like this - to pass on actual facts and hands-on experiences for people to avoid potentially dangerous issues. More answers have been posted since my answer above. Be careful with some, Li-ion batteries have more energy per unit weight and per unit volume than lead-acid batteries (e.g. flooded, AGM, GEL), also more expensive. Li-ion chemistries need more control to maximize benefits and longevity. It is not a good replacement for all situations (e.g. extremely hot or cold climates) unless additional care is applied. One of the big reasons why Tesla EVs can go more than 500,000 to a million miles on the original battery pack is their active thermal management system provides the ideal temperature setting for the cells during charging and discharging, even when parked.\n\nOne commenter lectured me for not just saying yes or no to the question, and that I bragged about myself excessively and dragged on in the answer. Like gasoline, Li-ion batteries can be dangerous if not handled or treated with a little respect. Most people, especially me, cannot read minds and learn about new technology thoroughly without some hands-on experience. So, I’m trying to share what I’ve learned in the past 15–20 years on Li-ion chemistries so you would avoid dangerous mistakes.\n\nI agree with many that for common car starting applications in mild climates the SLA, AGM, or GEL lead-acid battery works fine and is less expensive than Li-ion batteries. However, for applications where you don’t want to be stranded out in the ocean, or 2–3X weight savings will make a big difference for an application, then Li-ion would be more applicable. Li-ion prices will continue to drop as production quantity increases. There will be other newer chemistries on the horizon that will be even better and safer than Li-ion, but not for many years yet. I’m demonstrating the dragging-on part here, so I’ll stop and look forward to your questions.\n\nAddendum 2\n\nIn my initial answer, I was trying not to get into too many technical details, trying not to be too wordy. Since some of you seem to have a more technical interest in this subject, let me display a few graphs to give you a better visual summary at the risk of “dragging on” in my answer.\n\nThe table below shows you a lead-acid battery’s voltage as related to its SOC:\n\nThe chart below shows the less you discharge a lead-acid battery in-depth, the longer the life. So, if you just start your car a couple of times a day in mild weather, and if the battery is a good quality one, then you can expect more than 5–8 years of service.\n\nAlthough this graph below shows 48V batteries, the basic principle still applies. The area below each curve is a rough representation of the energy capacity of that particular chemistry. This is the reason why the LFP battery will always last longer than lead-acid batteries of the same Ah rating. Also, LFP will maintain a higher voltage for a longer period of time to ensure your electrical devices will operate properly or efficiently for a longer period of time.\n\nLFP batteries retain more energy than lead-acid batteries at all temperatures but are especially critical at the lower temperature range. 1C means discharging at the Ah rating. For example, a 100Ah battery can discharge 100A for 1 hour at the rated voltage (12V for ICE car batteries). So, for a 100Ah battery to crank an engine at 600A, then that’s a 6C discharge rate. The same rationale applies to charging. Charging a 100Ah battery at 200A would be a 2C charging rate, or charging at 50A would be a C/2 charging rate. By the way, to maximize LFP service life, always charge at C/2 or less. So, 1C charging means a 1-hr charge at 100A and a C/2 charge will take around 2-hrs at 50A for a 100Ah battery. For Li-ion batteries in general, the lower the charging rate, the better their longevity. You can also charge at a lower current while at the charging voltage (13.8 - 14.4V for LFP) to minimize stresses to the electrodes and electrolyte (and less dendrite growth). Most consumers do not have a 14.4V 100A charger at home, less than 100A will be fine. If you have a 12V 50Ah LFP battery, then be sure to charge at 25A or less for longevity (13.8–14.4V), above 32°F (0°C).\n\nAddendum 3\n\nI couldn’t add a couple of graphs to reply to a question in the comments below about new chemistries that are better than Li-ion in certain applications, so I’m going to post them here opening up for more criticisms of being too wordy.\n\nThe graph below shows how this new rechargeable chemistry (NiZn) will be better than NMH in capacity. The area below each curve represents that chemistry’s energy capacity. The greater the area, the more energy.\n\nThe graph below shows how NiZn performs in different areas compared to Li-ion and lead-acid batteries.\n\nIf you’re worried that nickel may be running out or being controlled by countries not friendly to the U.S., hopefully, this chart will relieve some of that anxiety.\n\nCalculate and Compare the TCO of your Lithium-Ion vs. VRLA Batteries\nWe’ve seen lithium-ion battery adoption grow at a rapid rate over the last couple of years. In fact, Bloomberg New Energy Finance report forecasts that 40% of data center battery backup will be lithium-ion by the year 2025. Among hyperscale data centers, this forecast is even greater at 55%. We know valve regulated lead acid (VRLA) is a less expensive battery solution on day one, so what’s driving this rapid growth for lithium-ion? Lithium-ion Capex Costs Continue to Decline There have been significant improvements with chemistries and technologies of lithium-ion batteries that have made them appealing for UPS applications. The Electrical Voltage (EV) industry is largely to thank for these advances. As adoption grows and the technology continues to mature, costs per kWh are declining. They still have a higher capex than VRLA batteries, but only by a factor of 1.5x to 2x today. So still, we asked what’s the main reason for lithium-ion adoption? TCO savings. The Data Center Science Center created a calculator to demonstrate this finding. A TCO Calculator Comparing Lithium-ion and VRLA Batteries We developed a TradeOff Tool calculator to help understand the impact of choosing lithium-ion vs. VRLA energy storage for a 3-phase static UPS. This TCO in the tool includes the following costs: Capex : The initial cost premium of the batteries. Lithium-ion generally has a higher cost. Note, a battery management system (BMS) is included in the standard lithium-ion solution, whereas with VRLA, you’d need to add another 20% to the VRLA cost for a BMS. So, comparing both solutions with BMS already narrows the capex cost gap. Energy : Typical battery fixed losses from steady state trickle charging are 0.1% for lithium-ion and 0.2% for VRLA, which translates to 50% energy savings. Note, we didn’t include the cost of transient losses incurred during a power outage that require battery discharging and subsequent charging. Battery replacements : VRLA batteries have a service life in the range of 3-6 years, whereas lithium-ion batteries can have a service life in the range of 10-15 years. In a 10-year TCO analysis, this generally means 2 battery replacements for VRLA batteries vs. zero for li-ion. Maintenance : Preventive maintenance of VRLA UPS batteries differs from lithium-ion UPS batteries. All battery maintenance should include regular visual inspections and an annual torque check. However, VRLA battery maintenance requires periodic internal resistance checks of every battery jar, whereas, lithium-ion batteries do not. This is because lithium-ion batteries come with a battery management system (BMS) that provides continuous monitoring of the state of health and state of charge. Also, VRLA battery maintenance is typically performed more frequently – two times per year if the VRLA batteries include a battery monitoring system or four times per year if they don’t; whereas lithium-ion batteries are generally maintained annually. Based on this, our calculator assumes\nhttps://www.thegreengrid.org/ja/newsroom/blog/calculate-and-compare-tco-your-lithium-ion-vs-vrla-batteries\n\nAddendum 4 (Jumpers)\n\nI just found out something about Li-ion car jumpers this week that’s a little confusing. Since it’s related to starting ICEs, I thought I’d share this with you in this thread. There are many of these palm-size or small portable Li-ion car jumpers that might advertise “2000A” or more, please be aware that’s not the cranking current such as CCA or MCA. It’s the peak current that we call it a current spike when you first turn on a power source that’s not well regulated or attenuated.\n\nThey are using a Li-ion chemistry that can release a great deal of energy on demand. This current spike only lasts a very short time in the beginning and drops down to the current needed to crank the engine. They use small Li-ion cells to be as compact as possible, so the electric load on these cells is very high.\n\nAn ICE that’s tuned up will start on the first crank within 1–second. However, old gasoline engines or diesels in the cold might be more challenging. If this little jumper is new and fully charged, then it should be able heat up the glow plugs and get a few cranks in. Just wanted to warn you about their labeling practices. In the winter time, it’d be better if you kept this jumper inside a warm place, and not leave it out in the car or truck overnight in the cold. It’s energy capacity could go down from 20–40%, depending upon the temperature and chemistry of the Li-ion cells. Only recharge this jumper after it warms up inside to get the highest charge.\n\nIf you left this jumper in the vehicle, and it’s below freezing, then you need to disconnect it from the weak battery as soon as the engine starts to prevent the vehicle’s charger sending energy back into the Li-ion cells. Only the LTO chemistry can be charged below 0°C (down to -40°C).",
        "name": "Karl Young",
        "views": "1.2M views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-MCA-colleges-in-Kerala",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/getadmision",
        "author": "u/Instance-Top",
        "question": "What is BCA and why has it becomes more important in today’s Lifestyle?",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/getadmision/comments/x357gr/what_is_bca_and_why_has_it_becomes_more_important/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is the difference in salary between someone with a Master's in Computer Applications (MCA) and someone with a Bachelor's in Computer Science (B.Sc)?",
        "answer": "Salary will not be much in both the cases unless you are skilled in some domain (like Cloud , Java etc.) or working in a big company.But doing Masters (MSc or MCA) will increase your eligibility to apply for jobs. Most companies or govt jobs prefer B.Tech or MCA or MSC. (Not only BCA guy) So do Masters (MCA or MSc)",
        "name": "Anpanp",
        "views": "12 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-in-salary-between-someone-with-a-Masters-in-Computer-Applications-MCA-and-someone-with-a-Bachelors-in-Computer-Science-B-Sc",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Which college is best for MCA / MSc IT with affordable fees?",
        "answer": "Hello there,\n\nHere are some top colleges for MCA/MSc IT with affordable fees:\n\nVellore Institute of Technology (VIT)\nManipal Academy of Higher Education (MAHE)\nSymbiosis Institute of Computer Studies and Research (SICSR)\nAmity University\nChrist University\nJain University\nDelhi University\nUniversity of Mumbai\nPune University\nBangalore University\nPSG College of Technology\nSRM Institute of Science and Technology\nChandigarh University\n\nHope it helps, for more details regarding college and admission feel free to contact 📲6205238449(Call/WhatsApp)\n\nThank you❤",
        "name": "Anjali Mishra",
        "views": "44 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-college-is-best-for-MCA-MSc-IT-with-affordable-fees",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What is the best private MCA college in India?",
        "answer": "The abbreviation MCA refers to \"master of computer application,\" and it's where you learn about software development, contemporary programming languages, and tools for creating apps more quickly and effectively.\n\nCheck out the private MCA colleges in Delhi NCR:\n\nABES Engineering college\nInstitute of Management Studies - [IMS], Noida\nVivekananda Institute of Professional Studies - [VIPS], New Delhi\nSharda University - [SU], Greater Noida\nManav Rachna International Institute of Research and Studies - [MRIIRS], Faridabad\nJSS Academy of Technical Education - [JSSATE], Noida\nInstitute of Information Technology & Management - [IITM], New Delhi",
        "name": "Joyah Khan",
        "views": "418 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-best-private-colleges-for-an-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Which one is better, an MCA or an MSc in computer science?",
        "answer": "Both an MCA (Master of Computer Applications) and an MSc (Master of Science) in Computer Science are valuable degrees and can lead to exciting career opportunities in the field of computer science. However, the choice between the two ultimately depends on your personal goals and interests.\n\nAn MCA is a professional degree that typically focuses on practical skills related to computer applications and software development. It may be more suited to individuals who are interested in pursuing a career in software development or in positions that require strong technical skills.\n\nOn the other hand, an MSc in Computer Science is a more academic degree that focuses on the theoretical foundations of computer science. It may be more suited to individuals who are interested in pursuing research or academic positions in the field of computer science, or who are interested in pursuing a career in a specialized area such as artificial intelligence or machine learning.\n\nUltimately, both degrees can lead to successful careers in computer science, and the choice between the two will depend on your individual goals and interests. It's important to carefully consider the curriculum and focus of each program before making a decision.",
        "name": "Digital School",
        "views": "10 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-one-is-better-an-MCA-or-an-MSc-in-computer-science",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Is doing an MCA worth it for the year 2024?",
        "answer": "MCA is worthy or not it totally depends on you talent and knowledge in CS and how you're using MCA platform.",
        "name": "IIMT Group Of Colleges",
        "views": "233 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-eligibility-for-an-MCA-in-SRM",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the benefits of doing an MCA from Lovely Professional University? Is it worth it, or are there better colleges to do an MCA from in Punjab?",
        "answer": "Hello reader,\n\nI hope you are doing well,\n\nLovely Professional University (LPU) is a leading university in India and it offers world-class education to its students. The university offers a range of courses, including Masters in Computer Applications (MCA). This course is designed to enable students to develop strong foundations in the field of computer applications and to become highly skilled professionals.\n\nThe MCA program at LPU offers students a wide range of benefits. First and foremost, the course is designed to equip students with a comprehensive understanding of computer applications and their applications in the corporate world. Students are imparted the latest knowledge and skills, enabling them to be successful professionals in the IT industry.\n\nThe MCA program at LPU also allows students to gain practical experience through industrial visits and internships. This helps to bridge the gap between theoretical knowledge and practical application, which is essential for a successful career in the IT industry. The university also offers students the opportunity to take part in research projects, which helps to further enhance their knowledge and skills.\n\nIn addition, the MCA program at LPU provides students with the opportunity to network with industry experts, which can be invaluable for their careers. The university also provides students with the opportunity to gain specialized knowledge in the area of their choice. The MCA program at LPU also offers students the opportunity to pursue higher studies and take up postgraduate programs. This enables students to gain a more advanced understanding of the field and to further their career prospects.\n\nFinally, the MCA program at LPU also provides students with the option of pursuing a professional certification or diploma. This helps to enhance their professional skills and also provides them with the opportunity to develop their knowledge and skills further.\n\nOverall, the MCA program at LPU provides students with a comprehensive understanding of the field of computer applications and their applications in the corporate world. It also helps to equip students with the skills and knowledge they need to become successful professionals in the IT industry. Therefore, the MCA program at LPU is an ideal choice for students looking to pursue a career in the IT industry.\n\nI hope it helps!\n\nThank you:)",
        "name": "Vidushi Sharma",
        "views": "29 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-benefits-of-doing-an-MCA-from-Lovely-Professional-University-Is-it-worth-it-or-are-there-better-colleges-to-do-an-MCA-from-in-Punjab",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/learnmachinelearning",
        "author": "u/RauhanSheikh",
        "question": "I have a bachelor's in computer application and I want to do masters in AI/ML/DS. so, what are the best universities in Germany for that?",
        "upvotes": "3",
        "comment": "9",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/learnmachinelearning/comments/whechj/i_have_a_bachelors_in_computer_application_and_i/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Concordia",
        "question": "Application start date for Master of Applied Computer Science (MApCompSc) fall 2023?",
        "upvotes": "4",
        "comment": "1",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Concordia/comments/viqquw/application_start_date_for_master_of_applied/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is the meaning of the annotation on a B1/B2 visa?",
        "answer": "The function of an annotation is for BCA to communicate with CBP.\n\nThe consular officers (BCA) are all over the world and approve visas and have their file on you.\n\nThe immigration officers (CBP) are in airports all over the US and have their file on you.\n\nBut the two files don't crosstalk. CBP can't peek into your BCA file to see what your visa is all about.\n\nSo the consular officer's way of communicating to the immigration officer is the annotation.\n\nSometimes it's just procedural, like noting the i-20, which links to the school you said you were attending when you got the visa. If there's a change in school, that can be a sign of some kind of fraud or significant change that might affect whether the student should be given entry. (Or not, I'm not saying that any change will get you refused, just that it's the way to mark a change.)\n\nSometimes the annotation is personal and specific. Say the consular officer has a hunch about you, that you might be planning something not what you say. You say you are going for a conference, you are qualified, but you are just a little squirrelly. The CO is not allowed to deny you on a hunch, but really wants to let CBP know something might be up. So you might get annotated with your conference location and dates.\n\nSo let's say you are Ghanaian and you get a visa to go to a conference in Iowa, and you get annotated. If you show up in Texas (which has a lot of Ghanaian immigrants) two months before the conference, then you will probably have a lot of explaining to do once the immigration officer sees the annotation.\n\nAnd sometimes it's even to help you, like there's something bad in your file, the CO manually cleared you and tried to remove whatever bad thing is there, but it still lives on electronically. So it might be saying “you may find this issue but I've already checked it out.” Much more officially of course.\n\nThe CO can only state facts, not give opinions or directions, so it can sometimes be a bit “Shaka, when the walls fell.” You have to tease out the “meaning\" from the factual statement.",
        "name": "Gaku Sato",
        "views": "89 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-meaning-of-the-annotation-on-a-B1-B2-visa",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which colleges are best for an MCA in Delhi/NCR (decent fee)?",
        "answer": "Hi Everyone,\n\nMasters in computer Applications is not just a master’s degree. It is a professional training program that prepares you to build a sustainable career in the IT world.\n\nGetting an MCA degree from a top private institute will not only get you a better exposure but also help you grab great job opportunities.\n\nSome of the top colleges for doing an MCA in Delhi NCR are:\n\nWorld College of Technology and Management (WCTM), Gurugram\nInstitute of Management studies (IMS), Noida\nLingaya’s Vidyapeeth, Haryana\nManav Rachna International Institute of Research and Studies (MRIIRS), Faridabad\nRC Institute of Technology (RCIT), New Delhi\nKR Mangalam University, Gurgaon\nInstitute of Professional Excellence and Management (IPEM), Ghaziabad\n\nI would recommend you the World College of Technology and Management, Gurugram. From affordability to facilities, this institute checks off all the boxes to fit-in the best college for MCA.\n\nWhy WCTM?\n\n● Infrastructure- WCTM is in the heart of an 18acre land and provides world class infrastructure to its students.\n\n● Placement- The placement record at WCTM is impeccable. The college environment also enables the students to expose themselves to the professional world.\n\n● Affordability- As compared to other private institutions in Delhi NCR, World college of Technology and Management is the most affordable.\n\n● Faculty- The faculty at WCTM is a group of expert professionals in their field who guide you in the best way possible. The faculty is very helpful and supportive.\n\n● Exposure- Life at WCTM is more than books, semester exams, academics etc. The exposure at WCTM is unmatched- from college fests to professional trainings, and everything in between.\n\nTo know more about the college, you can click on the link below:https://www.wctmgurgaon.com",
        "name": "Ashish Kumar",
        "views": "727 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-happens-if-your-best-friend-says-I-love-you",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Can I get admission in LPU for an MCA hons. course after failing in the LPUNEST?",
        "answer": "Hello reader,\n\nI hope you are doing well,\n\nLovely Professional University (LPU) has its admission test known as the LPUNEST for various undergraduate and postgraduate programs, including the MCA hons. course. If a candidate fails to secure the minimum required marks in the LPUNEST, they may not be eligible for admission to the MCA hons. the course at LPU. However, there may be alternative admission procedures available that the candidate can explore.\n\nOne option is to try and secure admission through the management quota, which allows candidates to gain admission to a program based on their academic records or other qualifications. However, the availability of seats under the management quota and the eligibility criteria may vary from year to year and may be subject to change.\n\nAnother option is to explore other universities that offer similar programs and have different admission procedures. The candidate can research and apply to these universities to pursue their MCA hons. course.\n\nIn any case, it is important to note that failing to secure the required marks in the LPUNEST does not necessarily mean that the candidate is not capable of pursuing the MCA hons. course. They can try other options and work hard to achieve their goals.\n\nI hope it helps!\n\nThank you:)",
        "name": "Vidushi Sharma",
        "views": "24 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-get-admission-in-LPU-for-an-MCA-hons-course-after-failing-in-the-LPUNEST",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/JEENEETards",
        "author": "u/Present_Leading3977",
        "question": "Btech CSE (4 years ) VS Master's in computer application ( MCA)",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "5",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/JEENEETards/comments/wacawr/btech_cse_4_years_vs_masters_in_computer/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/saryuun12",
        "author": "u/saryuun12",
        "question": "Best College for BCA in Dehradun | Bachelor of Computer Application",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/saryuun12/comments/126e0my/best_college_for_bca_in_dehradun_bachelor_of/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Is BSc IT available at Parul University?",
        "answer": "No bsc it is not available at parul University\n\nBut it has BCA which is better than bsc\n it\n\nBca is also of 3 year i.e 6 sem\n\nFee for bca at parul University is around 55000 per year\n\nHope this helped\n\nThank you",
        "name": "Abhishek",
        "views": "14 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-BSc-IT-available-at-Parul-University",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Should I do a BBA or BCA before an MBA?",
        "answer": "The decision to pursue a BBA or BCA before an MBA largely depends on your personal interests, career goals, and academic background. However, if you're interested in management and business administration, pursuing a BBA before an MBA could be a good option.On the other hand, if you're interested in computer applications and want to work in the IT industry, pursuing a BCA before an MBA could be a good choice.\n\nAs for Geeta University, it offers both BBA and BCA programs, so you can choose the program that aligns with your interests and career goals. Additionally, Geeta University also offers an MBA program for those who have completed their undergraduate studies and want to further their education in business management.",
        "name": "Priyanshu GTH",
        "views": "17 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Should-I-do-a-BBA-or-BCA-before-an-MBA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Indians_StudyAbroad",
        "author": "u/ishit_sharma",
        "question": "Unable to choose which country to pursue my master's from",
        "upvotes": "6",
        "comment": "19",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Indians_StudyAbroad/comments/xwdwtk/unable_to_choose_which_country_to_pursue_my/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Where can I access Set 1 forms on MCA portal?",
        "answer": "Hover on ‘MCA services’, ‘Company e-Filing’ and then hover on the relevant module which is displayed in the below screenshot. Then click on the relevant form which the user desires to file.",
        "name": "MANOJ KUMAR SHARMA",
        "views": "13 views",
        "link": "https://manojkumarsharmaassociates.quora.com/Where-can-I-access-Set-1-forms-on-MCA-portal",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/MeetPeople",
        "author": "u/chaoticquantaa",
        "question": "22 M[Friendship][Relationship] India/Anywhere - An Infj and demi looking for someone to feel connect with as a whole",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/MeetPeople/comments/1115iiy/22_mfriendshiprelationship_indiaanywhere_an_infj/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Which is the best private college in Bhopal for MCA?",
        "answer": "There are several good private colleges in Bhopal that offer MCA (Master of Computer Applications) programs. Here are some of the top options:\n\nMaulana Azad National Institute of Technology (MANIT): MANIT is a government institute, but it offers an MCA program and is considered one of the best colleges for MCA in Bhopal.\nTechnocrats Institute of Technology (TIT): TIT is a private college in Bhopal that offers an MCA program. It is considered one of the top colleges in the city for MCA.\nOriental College of Technology (OCT): OCT is another private college in Bhopal that offers an MCA program. It has a good reputation for its quality of education and placement record.\nLNCT Group of Colleges: LNCT is a group of private colleges in Bhopal that offer an MCA program. It is known for its good infrastructure and experienced faculty.\nRadharaman Institute of Technology and Science (RITS): RITS is another private college in Bhopal that offers an MCA program. It has a good placement record and offers modern facilities to its students.\n\nIt's important to do your research and consider factors such as the college's reputation, faculty, infrastructure, and placement record before making a decision. You should also consider your personal preferences and goals when selecting a college",
        "name": "SuChal",
        "views": "51 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-private-college-in-Bhopal-for-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/saryuun12",
        "author": "u/mttd",
        "question": "Best College for BCA in Dehradun | Bachelor of Computer Application",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/saryuun12/comments/126e0my/best_college_for_bca_in_dehradun_bachelor_of/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What are the best colleges to do an MCA from Delhi NCR, Gurugram or Faridabad?",
        "answer": "Hi Everyone,\n\nMasters in Computer Applications is a professional PG degree in computer science. The main focus of this course is to prepare individuals for a flourishing career in Information Technology. Its very crucial to take this degree from a well-reputed college, and some of the prerequisites of the same will be talked about later.\n\nWell, some of the best colleges to do an MCA from Delhi NCR, Gurugram or Faridabad are:\n\nWorld College of Technology and Management (WCTM), Gurugram\nInstitute of Management studies (IMS), Noida\nLingaya’s Vidyapeeth, Haryana\nManav Rachna International Institute of Research and Studies (MRIIRS), Faridabad\nRC Institute of Technology (RCIT), New Delhi\nKR Mangalam University of Information and Technology, Gurgaon\nInstitute of Professional Excellence and Management (IPEM), Ghaziabad\nJSS Academy of Technical Education (JSSATE), Noida\nATM Global Business School, Faridabad\nGalgotias University, Greater Noida\n\nOut of all these great options for pursuing an MCA, I’d recommend you the World College of Technology and Management (WCTM), Gurugram. What gives this college a cut above the rest?\n\nWell, it fulfils all the pre-requisites that I started talking about in the beginning- college culture, reputation, ranking, infrastructure, placements, exposure, opportunities, experienced faculty, hostel facilities, and an amazing environment, to name a few.\n\nThere’s a lot to praise about, but I’d rather choose to focus on a few points, from the perspective of exposure to opportunities as well as career point of view.\n\nWCTM provides exemplary internship opportunities and professional IT training to its students, and this is a plus point for MCA students who are looking forward to build a career in the IT industry. Plus, the World College of Technology and Management, Gurugram has an excellent placement record of outgoing batch by 100 plus companies ORACLE, IBM, HCL, L&T, WIPRO, DELHI-METRO, and many more.\n\nFrom the exposure perspective, the college organises fests, seminars and events every now and then which is a great opportunity for students to network and communicate with great, eminent personalities too.\n\nFor more information visit this link- Best engineering college in Gurgaon | Best engineering college in Delhi NCR | WCTM",
        "name": "Raja Rajput",
        "views": "251 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-top-MCA-colleges-in-Bangalore",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What is the career scope after a BCA+MCA?",
        "answer": "After completing a BCA (Bachelor of Computer Applications) and MCA (Master of Computer Applications), there are many career options available in the field of Information Technology (IT). Here are some popular career paths for BCA+MCA graduates:\n\nSoftware Developer\nSoftware Tester\nNetwork Engineer\nDatabase Administrator\nNetwork Administrator\nInformation Security Analyst\nProject Manager\nThey can take government exams such as those for banks, LICs, etc.",
        "name": "Bubai Das",
        "views": "270 views",
        "link": "https://clcoding.quora.com/I-am-a-12th-student-and-aspire-to-drew-carrier-in-IT-field-Does-BCA-with-specialisations-a-better-carrier-degree-Does-i",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/ApplyingToCollege",
        "author": "u/caagxd",
        "question": "Transfer Applicant looking for public universities in California offering Electrical Engineering AND Computer Science Bachelors.",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "2",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/ApplyingToCollege/comments/w02o48/transfer_applicant_looking_for_public/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/gradadmissions",
        "author": "u/Thanos9876",
        "question": "Are master’s programs in engineering considered cash cows for universities even if they admit only 5-10% of applicants?",
        "upvotes": "3",
        "comment": "12",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/gradadmissions/comments/11xj6zf/are_masters_programs_in_engineering_considered/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/gradadmissions",
        "author": "u/orang-i",
        "question": "Indian looking for Grad Schools in USA",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "6",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/gradadmissions/comments/10j7s5w/indian_looking_for_grad_schools_in_usa/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/Puzzleheaded-Fox1868",
        "author": "u/Puzzleheaded-Fox1868",
        "question": "MCA Full Form: Eligibility, Salary, Job Scope, Entrance Exam, Admission Process, Subjects, Career, Top Colleges",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/Puzzleheaded-Fox1868/comments/xd0rmj/mca_full_form_eligibility_salary_job_scope/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Can students complete a master's degree through distance learning after completing a bachelor's degree in computer applications (BCA) from the Indira Gandhi National Open University (IGNOU)?",
        "answer": "After acquiring the Bachelor's Degree (BCA) at IGNOU, there is a further educational opportunity to go for an MCA at IGNOU or Master's Programme at any other University/Institute.",
        "name": "IIMT Group Of Colleges",
        "views": "3 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Can-students-complete-a-masters-degree-through-distance-learning-after-completing-a-bachelors-degree-in-computer-applications-BCA-from-the-Indira-Gandhi-National-Open-University-IGNOU",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/csMajors",
        "author": "u/akxsh_vv",
        "question": "How to become a Computer Science researcher?",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "7",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/csMajors/comments/10x6ess/how_to_become_a_computer_science_researcher/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is the highest salary you can earn with a BCA from GITAM University?",
        "answer": "However, the salary one can earn with a BCA degree from GITAM University may depend on several factors such as job role, industry, location, and individual skills and experience.\n\nGenerally, BCA graduates from GITAM University can expect to earn entry-level salaries ranging from around 2.5 to 6 lakhs per annum depending on the above factors. With more experience and skills, they can earn higher salaries and can also pursue higher studies such as MCA, MBA, or other relevant courses that can lead to better career opportunities and higher salaries.",
        "name": "Ameer TV",
        "views": "10 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-highest-salary-you-can-earn-with-a-BCA-from-GITAM-University",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What is better, an MCA or 2.2 LPA at Infosys for the role of Systems Associate?",
        "answer": "Go for MCA without a shadow of doubt . Beacuse this 2.2 lpa job will do nothing but destroy your career . Once you start getting some amount you will get your comfort zone and won't be that effective as before . Rather try for some exam or try to improve to skill ,but never join any service based companies for 2,3 laks . Because here you won't be getting any knowledge and even sometimes have to work on the different domain.\n\nEither I would advice you to join any start up because the learning graph will always be high there . And you get to a lot of exposure. Also you will be assigned a project from very start of your joining unless these services based companies which makes to sit a person in bench for 7,8 months with an ease.\n\nHope it helps",
        "name": "Avinav Singh Rajpoot",
        "views": "14.2K views",
        "link": "https://datastructures.quora.com/Im-a-BSc-computer-science-final-year-student-Should-I-do-MCA-from-Pune-or-prepare-for-placements-in-Hyderabad",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Can I get into NIT without the JEE?",
        "answer": "For B Tech courses , you cant join an NIT without JEE Main.\n\nFor other courses like M Tech, MCA, M Sc etc you dont have to appear for JEE but some other exam.\n\nFor M Tech you need to qualify GATE, for MCA need to pass NIMCET exam, and JAM score is required for M Sc courses (CCMN counselling).",
        "name": "K Singh",
        "views": "107 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-get-into-NIT-without-the-JEE",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which is the best Mca colleges in Delhi NCR?",
        "answer": "The best course for a particular student depends on their individual goals, interests, and needs. Some students may find that MCA is a good fit for them, while others may prefer a different course of study.\n\nIt is important for students to carefully consider their options and do their own research before deciding on a course of study. Some factors to consider when choosing a course of study include the content and structure of the program, the career prospects and job opportunities available to graduates, and the reputations and resources of the institutions offering the course.\n\nIn general, it is advisable for students to choose a course of study that aligns with their career goals and interests, and to select an institution that has a good reputation and offers a high-quality education.\n\nFrom my own experience the best private college in Delhi NCR is World College of Technology and Management, Gurugram.\n\nMy time at WCTM has been wonderful. WCTM has always been my top pick for all the criteria, be it the placement statistics, faculty members, infrastructure, internships, industrial training, extracurricular activities, or academics.\n\nThe B.Tech. CSE placement rate is perfect. Many businesses, including HCL Technology, Accenture, Nokia Solutions, Byjus, and Maintech Technologies, among others, have sent out recruiters.\n\nAt WCTM, a rigorous academic process has given students the expertise and specialised abilities they need to perform superbly in a variety of challenging scenarios with ease and confidence. The specialized student training branch at WCTM has been the one of the major factors behind my growth.\n\nThis department focuses on developing the soft skills such as communication skills, posture, etc. Every student would go through vigorous training to develop a presentable and professional personality.\n\nYou can visit the college website here: Best engineering college in Gurgaon | Best engineering college in Delhi NCR | WCTM",
        "name": "Somick Roy",
        "views": "396 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-doing-an-MCA-worth-it-for-the-year-2024",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "How can I engage with you as my personal and company legal advisor?",
        "answer": "Company Law is a different kettle of fish.\n\nIt needs expertise in many areas of Legal operations of companies and legal codes pertaining to SEBI, MCA and ROC\n\nI have never worked in company law and would be totally lost\n\nYou need someone who knows every section of the 2013 Code.\n\nPersonal Legal Advisor?\n\nSure.\n\nIf you have any legal problems (Criminal) and want advise on least cumbersome way to settle the issue, then mediation and arbitration is my speciality especially wrt State Police cases on 420 IPC Or 138 NI Act Or 406 IPC Or 409 IPC Or 498A (Chennai, Trichy, CBE or Bangalore only)\n\nIf you have insurance problems with Health Insurance claims, I handle that\n\nIf you want to import from China & Singapore and need to register a company or tie up with local companies there and establish an LC facility, I handle that\n\nIf you want to export to Russia and pay in AED / Yuan instead of Dollars and want to promote business in Russia, I handle that too\n\nIn any such case if you DM your issue, and if I can offer professional (paid) collaboration, then I will have one of the six people who work with me contact you (Again Bangalore, Chennai, Trichy and Coimbatore only)\n\nOtherwise I can offer you free advise and guide you to people who can help you (Like Real Estate Title Deeds etc)",
        "name": "Kanthaswamy Balasubramaniam",
        "views": "6.8K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-better-doing-MCA-or-MBA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/AskLE",
        "question": "What would look better on police application, bachelor’s degree or 4 years military?",
        "upvotes": "6",
        "comment": "47",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/AskLE/comments/129ncha/what_would_look_better_on_police_application/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "How was the Don Bosco College Panjim BCA tour to Manali?",
        "answer": "real-time information or news about recent events or tours. I am also unable to browse the internet on my own. However, typically, the experience of any tour largely depends on the planning, organization, and execution of the tour, the destination, weather conditions, group dynamics, and individual expectations. Factors such as itinerary, accommodation, transportation, activities, and food can also impact the experience of a tour. If you have more specific questions or details about the Don Bosco College Panjim BCA tour to Manali, you may need to reach out to the tour organizers or participants for more information.",
        "name": "Sajjad Hussain",
        "views": "14 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-was-the-Don-Bosco-College-Panjim-BCA-tour-to-Manali",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is the difference between borrowing channel allocation (BCA) and fixed channel allocation (FCA)?",
        "answer": "Borrowing channel allocation (BCA) and fixed channel allocation (FCA) are two different strategies for allocating channels in a cellular network.\n\nIn FCA, a fixed number of channels are assigned to each cell and they remain reserved for that cell only, even if they are not being used at the moment. This means that even if a cell has no active calls, the channels assigned to it cannot be used by other cells.\n\nIn BCA, a cell can borrow channels from its neighboring cells when the demand for channels exceeds its capacity. This enables more efficient use of the available channels and reduces the probability of call blocking. However, this also requires frequent communication between the base station and the neighboring cells to coordinate the borrowing and returning of channels.\n\nIn summary, the main difference between BCA and FCA is that BCA allows for more flexible and efficient use of channels by borrowing from neighboring cells, while FCA assigns a fixed number of channels to each cell regardless of demand.",
        "name": "Kirti Patil",
        "views": "8 views",
        "link": "https://kirtipatilsbestspace.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-borrowing-channel-allocation-BCA-and-fixed-channel-allocation-FCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Is online MCA from Jain university is worth it?",
        "answer": "Yes! Doing MCA from Jain University is worth it as it is one of the best colleges in Bangalore for management studies & I would suggest you join this college. It has good placements, and you can gain knowledge here. About 80% of the students got placed from the last 2 years. The highest salary package offered is 11.5 Lakhs.\n\nFor more you can also submit the Form & get connected with counsellor\n\nOnline Regular Degree Program\nOnline Regular Program by reputed Universities of India for BA, B.Com, BBA, BCA, MA, M.Com, MBA & MCA. Classes and Exams both would be conducted online. Get regular degree of reputed university by learning from home.\nhttps://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSfTpCSS3dHrXPAYGky8XxtrCdmz9SrsrZgzFR4NgIFGXhoWGA/viewform",
        "name": "Ayushi Singh",
        "views": "3.3K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/I-m-doing-b-sc-can-I-do-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What's the strangest thing you caught a flight attendant doing?",
        "answer": "One thing I noticed the only time I ever sat at the back next to the toilets(never again for obvious reasons) was the flight attendants went into the toilets numerous times after people had been (presumably to check it was OK) and they never washed their hands. Had they washed their hands they would have come out with slightly damp hands and wiped them on a towel or flushed the towel maybe or wiped them on their clothes. Either way I realized they were tidying up the toilets but not washing their hands. Then they go around handing out food.",
        "name": "Neil McA.",
        "views": "24K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-your-salary-Are-you-happy-with-it",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/softvisioncollege",
        "author": "u/sikhadawan",
        "question": "Best BCA Colleges in Indore (Bachelor of Computer Applications)",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/softvisioncollege/comments/126gsal/best_bca_colleges_in_indore_bachelor_of_computer/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Is the Venkatapathy manpower consultancy fake or real?",
        "answer": "Fraud-\n\ni got offer with unbelievable salary for Norway\n\nsame time I checked with employer they confirmed fraud.\n\nI asked mca registration number from vm consultant, he made within minutes and send but in government website mca list this company not there\n\nbrilliant fraud\n\nbe careful",
        "name": "Shiju Kumar",
        "views": "3.2K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-are-the-on-campus-placements-for-MCA-at-USICT-New-Delhi",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What is the difference between the F-22 and the F-35? Why is the F-22 more expensive?",
        "answer": "F-22 is the best air superiority and interceptor fighter while F-35 is the best multirole fighter.\n\ndifferences:\n\n1-F-22 is an twin engine fighter while F-35 just have one\n\n2-F-22 is an ATF (Advanced Tactical Fighter) while F-35 is an AMF (Advanced Multirole Fighter or MCA (Multirole Combat Fighter).\n\n3-F-22 is an air superiority fighter while F-35 is an multirole fighter.\n\n4-F-35 is slower that F-22 (F-35 top speed: Mach 1.6) (F-22 top speed: Mach 2.2)\n\n5- F-22 is more maneuverable than F-35.\n\nF-22A\n\nF-35B\n\nIf you want to compare F-35 with F-22, “F-35 is the younger brother of F-22”",
        "name": "Navid Tofighi",
        "views": "6.9K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-a-Masters-in-Computer-Science-MS-and-a-Master-of-Computer-Application-MCA-I-have-pursued-a-a-Bachelor-of-Computer-Application-BCA-this-year-which-degree-should-I-opt-for-now",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/WGU",
        "author": "u/asbnoida",
        "question": "Should I get a second Bachelors degree in Cloud Computing.",
        "upvotes": "28",
        "comment": "33",
        "timestamp": "Past hours",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/WGU/comments/11xypg3/should_i_get_a_second_bachelors_degree_in_cloud/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "How do I get into a good college for an MCA?",
        "answer": "To get into a good college for an MCA (Master of Computer Applications), you can follow these steps:\n\nResearch: Start by researching the top colleges that offer MCA programs in your country or region. Look for colleges that have a good reputation, experienced faculty, excellent facilities, and placement opportunities.\nEligibility: Check the eligibility criteria for admission to MCA programs in different colleges. Typically, candidates should have a bachelor's degree in Computer Science or a related field with a minimum percentage of marks specified by the college.\nEntrance exams: Many colleges require candidates to take an entrance exam to be eligible for admission to the MCA program. The most common entrance exams for MCA include NIMCET, MAH MCA CET, TANCET, etc. You can check the entrance exam requirements for different colleges and prepare accordingly.\nApplication process: Once you have identified the colleges and entrance exams you want to apply for, you need to submit your application. The application process may involve filling out an online or offline application form, uploading required documents such as transcripts, entrance exam scorecards, and other necessary documents, and paying the application fee.\nPreparation: Start preparing for the entrance exams well in advance. You can refer to textbooks, online resources, or join coaching classes to improve your chances of success.\nInterview: Some colleges may also conduct interviews as part of the selection process. Prepare for the interview by researching the college, practicing common interview questions, and presenting yourself professionally.\n\nIn summary, to get into a good college for an MCA, you need to research the top colleges, meet the eligibility criteria, prepare for entrance exams and interviews, and submit a strong application.",
        "name": "Sharma Shaan",
        "views": "2 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-get-into-a-good-college-for-an-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "My brother and I plan to start a clothing company in my mother’s name. What is the process for applying for a name?",
        "answer": "There is an online process which needs to be followed for name reservation of company i.e.\n\nCheck the availability of proposed company name on the MCA website\nThe Name of the Company should be unique. It should not be same, similar, identical, or resembling the name of the existing Company or LLP Registered. Phonetically similar names are also to be avoided.\nThe Name of the Company should strictly be in accordance with Rule 8 of The Companies Incorporation Rules, 2014.\nMake sure that there is no such trademark already registered with the same name.\nGo to Spice in MCA services and click on new application, proceed further with the application.\nSummary of the objects to be pursued by the company on its incorporation. Write as “THE MAIN OBJECT CLAUSE OF THE COMPANY IS ATTACHED HEREWITH”\nParticulars of the proposed or approved name (There are 2 options given for proposing Names for Name application of a Company) as per the preference to be given one should write names.\nChoose file: The last step for Name reservation of the Company is to browse the attachments to be done; if the name is not registered then only Main Object Clause of the proposed Company is required to be attached.",
        "name": "Dilip Bohra",
        "views": "106 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-colleges-for-an-MCA-in-Pune",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/ProWordPress",
        "author": "u/maincoderhoon",
        "question": "Where to find Full Time Job(Remote) ?",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "6",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/ProWordPress/comments/10fefuj/where_to_find_full_time_jobremote/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/MeetPeople",
        "author": "u/chaoticquantaa",
        "question": "22 M [Friendship][Relationship] India/Anywhere - An Infj and a demi guy seeking someone to connect with as a whole",
        "upvotes": "2",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/MeetPeople/comments/zzl5bq/22_m_friendshiprelationship_indiaanywhere_an_infj/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/tearsofthekingdom",
        "author": "u/bob4978135",
        "question": "A trademark application for the Master Sword logo was filed in Japan.",
        "upvotes": "35",
        "comment": "11",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/tearsofthekingdom/comments/11zd575/a_trademark_application_for_the_master_sword_logo/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/MSCS",
        "author": "u/One_Knowledge608",
        "question": "Is masters in Computer science at University of Chicago good?",
        "upvotes": "9",
        "comment": "31",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/MSCS/comments/128dtp5/is_masters_in_computer_science_at_university_of/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/careerguidance",
        "author": "u/These-Psychology-959",
        "question": "Switching Careers to IT security at 34?",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/careerguidance/comments/y64abr/switching_careers_to_it_security_at_34/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/jainuniversityseo",
        "author": "u/jainuniversityseo",
        "question": "Bachelor in computer application with Jain University",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/jainuniversityseo/comments/csejuy/bachelor_in_computer_application_with_jain/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Indians_StudyAbroad",
        "author": "u/Justaguy307",
        "question": "How to go to Germany for Masters. I want to go to Germany to pursue my masters from there. I am currently doing by bachelors from a private university in India and want to go this year to Germany. As i will get my degree in August 2023, and applications will begin in April, so what are all procedure",
        "upvotes": "11",
        "comment": "9",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Indians_StudyAbroad/comments/11r8agm/how_to_go_to_germany_for_masters_i_want_to_go_to/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/developersIndia",
        "author": "u/UnverifiedChaos-5017",
        "question": "Suggestion please, thanks",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "3",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/developersIndia/comments/zvo251/suggestion_please_thanks/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the better opportunities after doing MCA?",
        "answer": "After completing an MCA (Master of Computer Applications) degree, there are many career opportunities available in the field of information technology. Here are some potential job roles:\n\nSoftware Developer: As an MCA graduate, you can work as a software developer, creating, designing, and testing software applications.\nDatabase Administrator: You can work as a database administrator, responsible for managing and maintaining large databases used by companies and organizations.\nWeb Developer: As a web developer, you can create and design websites for clients, incorporating the latest technologies and design principles.\nNetwork Administrator: You can work as a network administrator, responsible for maintaining and managing computer networks for companies and organizations.\nIT Consultant: As an IT consultant, you can offer your expertise to clients on various technology-related issues and provide solutions to their problems.\nSystem Analyst: You can work as a system analyst, responsible for analyzing and improving computer systems and processes within a company or organization.\nData Scientist: As a data scientist, you can analyze complex data sets to help organizations make informed decisions.\n\nThese are just a few examples of the career opportunities available to MCA graduates. With the growing importance of technology in our daily lives, there is a high demand for professionals with a strong background in computer applications.",
        "name": "Eduxprts",
        "views": "6 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-better-opportunities-after-doing-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/jkluniversity",
        "author": "u/getadmision",
        "question": "Bachelor of computer Application | Explore J K Lakshmipat University Jaipur",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/jkluniversity/comments/yt11bd/bachelor_of_computer_application_explore_j_k/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Was Waterloo a British victory or shared with Prussia? Wasn't Wellington nearly defeated when saved by von Blucher?",
        "answer": "It was a Russian victory. They would have stood no chance against the experienced army that Napoleon invaded Russia with. Instead, they faced fairly raw recruits as that army was wiped out in Russia. Much like it was Russia who destroyed the Nazis in World War 2",
        "name": "Neil McA.",
        "views": "50 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Was-Waterloo-a-British-victory-or-shared-with-Prussia-Wasnt-Wellington-nearly-defeated-when-saved-by-von-Blucher",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/gamedev",
        "author": "u/DifficultAccess4651",
        "question": "Desperately looking for Career Advice ( Game dev/ web dev / AAA dreams)",
        "upvotes": "3",
        "comment": "11",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/gamedev/comments/y8df1u/desperately_looking_for_career_advice_game_dev/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/AskComputerScience",
        "author": "u/tiipsindia",
        "question": "Can i become a data scientist?",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/AskComputerScience/comments/12beujn/can_i_become_a_data_scientist/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/B_University",
        "author": "u/B_University",
        "question": "Master of Computer Application",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past hours",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/B_University/comments/yogbmr/master_of_computer_application/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Nepal",
        "author": "u/Expensive-Marzipan92",
        "question": "Bachelor in computer application(BCA)",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "8",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Nepal/comments/11zjra2/bachelor_in_computer_applicationbca/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What do you do when a dementia patient refuses to shower?",
        "answer": "**********DISCLAIMER… I AM UK BASED. THE FOLLOWING ANSWER ONLY APPLIES TO UK LAW. I HAVE NO IDEA ON ANY INTERNATIONAL LAW. PLEASE DO NOT HARASS STAFF AT CARE HOMES ABOUT THIS, WE ARE DOING OUR BESTS AND WORKING WITHIN THE LAW. **********\n\nWhat do you do when a dementia patient refuses to shower? That all depends.\n\nIn the UK, we have a Act of Parliament called the Mental Capacity Act (MCA) which outlines a person’s human rights and what actions an establishment can take to ensure the best of health for residents etc.\n\nOne of the key principles of the MCA is the right to make your own decisions (there is a reason I’m telling you this), and if are capable of making that decision.\n\nLet’s use Daisy for an example. Daisy is 24 years of age, she has autism and some slight learning difficulties however she lives totally independently in a supported living complex. Mum and dad have found out that Daisy would like to go to Scotland and climb Ben Nevis. They aren’t happy and want to stop her because they are afraid she’ll get lost and hurt herself. Can they do it?\n\nIn order to establish if they can, Daisy would need to have a Mental Capacity Assessment, which is pretty simple. She would be visited by a doctor or relevant medical professional, the manager of her complex and potentially a social worker (maybe just one of them, depending on how severe her needs are). She would be asked questions such as “Daisy, what would you need to go to Ben Nevis?”\n\nIf Daisy said something like “An ice cream, a pair of socks and a packet of crisps”, it would be unlikely she would be allowed to go. In this instance however she says “A map, a pair of boots and a mobile phone” along with a list of other things she thinks she needs. Please note if she says “my teddy” and sleeps with a teddy, that would not go against her as she needs the teddy to sleep.\n\nThey would then say “Daisy do you realise what could happen to you if you climb Ben Nevis?”\n\nAs long as Daisy can say “I might fall and hurt myself” she CANNOT BE STOPPED. She has the right to make that decision as she understands it is a dangerous thing to do. She can be told she will need a member of staff to accompany her, or to be booked in to group etc, but you cannot tell her she can’t go.\n\nNow, we’ll use Beryl. Beryl is 87, she has dementia. She no longer recognises her family, she knows she loves them but has no idea why. Beryl doesn’t want to take her tablets any more. If she doesn’t take her tablets, she’ll have a stroke and die. She is asked “What might happen to you if you don’t take these tablets.” Sadly, she doesn’t know.\n\nBeryl doesn’t have the capacity to make that decision.\n\nThe care staff take over and act in her best interests. It is in her best interest to take the medication, so they are given to her in different ways. Maybe on a nice tasty yoghurt (so long as the staff tell her it’s there) or maybe covertly (so long as they have medical consent to do that).\n\nNow, we move to the question of the shower. If the paitent can understand that they will become smelly and potentially get an infection, they cannot be forced to shower. If however they don’t know they can be treated in their best interests. It is in their best interests to be clean, so staff can shower them against their consent.\n\nYes. I have done this, and yes, we are very respectful when we do it.\n\nWe always ask them to co-operate and try to make it like a game “Look Mabel, a lovely warm bubbly bath! Let’s get you in it and you can play with the bubbles as long as you like!” or “Look William, a nice warm shower! Let’s see who can sing the loudest!”\n\nWe always try to respect theirs and their family’s wishes, no one really wants a male doing personal care on a female so we avoid that happening. Some families with certain religious beliefs etc might not want a female doing personal care on a male, in fact a lot of our struggles are “my wife wouldn’t like it!” In that case we try to meet them half way, so we escort them to the shower, then turn our backs while they shower (watching in the mirror to ensure they are safe all the time of course!).\n\nSometimes, they do become violent. It’s fear. They don’t understand why you’re doing it, but once they feel the warmth of the water, they tend to relax and let you do your job. I have had to restrain someone in a shower when they tried to attack a co-worker. It was minimal force (I held my forearm in front of her to block slaps and punches and held under her arms when she tried to kick to support her so she didn’t fall). When it becomes that hard, you shower people in twos.\n\nWe try to maintain dignity at all times.\n\nI promise you, your relative will not be in any danger at any time. We will make sure they are clean and healthy, and as happy as we can make them, for the rest of their lives.",
        "name": "Scaz",
        "views": "8.9K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-true-that-Mca-is-now-for-1year-for-BCA-graduate",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/tiipsindia",
        "author": "u/Manoyal003",
        "question": "Reputed BCA College in Greater Noida for Students",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/tiipsindia/comments/103xice/reputed_bca_college_in_greater_noida_for_students/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Do you think that in South cinema, they show the real Indian culture and tradition?",
        "answer": "There is nothing called South Indian Cinema, we have Tollywood, Kollywood, Sandalwood, and Mollywood. We have our own separate identities, do not mix up us. It is like saying Korean dramas, Japanese anime, and C-Dramas are the same.\n\nDo they show Indian culture?\n\nIndia is a diverse Country, the culture changes for every state and region, So, what exactly is Indian culture??\n\nIf you ask about Tollywood, yes it mostly concentrates on Telugu Culture and nativity, very rarely, they go beyond our Telugu nativity.\n\nTollywood movies like C/O Kancherapalem, Palasa, Jayamma Panchayathi, etc. show Kalingandhra's nativity and culture.\n\nTollywood movies like Rangastalam, Satamanambhavati, Mukunda, SVSC, Soggade Chinninayana, etc. depict Godavari districts of Coastal Andhra’s nativity and culture.\n\nTollywood movies like Mallesham, Balagam, Fida, Love Story, Daasi, Virata Parvam, Dasara, Skylab, Jathiratnalu, etc. show Telangana nativity and culture.\n\nTollywood movies like Ee nagaraniki Emaindi, Faluknuma Das, Pelli Choopulu, Life is Beautiful, Happy Days, etc. show Hyderabad city culture. (College & Friends oriented movies)\n\nTollywood movies like MCA had Warangal city and Medak of Telangana’s backdrop.\n\nMedak Town Backdrop:\n(Medak is my native place :))\n\nMedak Church\n\nThese are our architecture which is used to build Tile-roof Houses.\n\nAnd Warangal backdrop:\nBhadrakali Ammavari Temple, Warangal.\n\nLaknavaram Bridge, Warangal.\n\nVagdevi Engineering College, Warangal:\n\nWarangal Fort:\n\nTollywood movie Writer Padmabhushana depicts Vijayawada City of Andhra Pradesh’s Culture.\n\nTollywood movies as of now did not perfectly make a Rayalaseema backdrop movie, they always stereotype the region, If Tollywood makes a Rayalaseema Backdrop movie, then they show Factionalism only.\n\nAravinda Sametha:\n\nAntahpuram:\n\nMaryada Ramanna:\n\nTo date, in the post-2000 era, this is the best movie to show Rayalaseema's backdrop.\n\nRayalaseema Village Houses (Their architecture is very similar to North Karnataka Houses)\n\nBlack Soils of Kurnool:\n\nGandikota Canyon:\n\nComing to Sandalwood, they recently portrayed Coastal Karnataka Culutre through Kantara.\n\nNagamandala, Singaravva, Sangya Balya, Katheyada Kala depicts North Karnataka Culture.\n\nMovies like Aanebala show South Karnataka Culture.\n\nRagi Mudde:\n\nSouth Karnataka Houses:\n\nSouth Karnataka Vesara Temples:\n\nJatre in South KA:\n\nSandalwood’s Dweepa movie depicts the Kodava Culture of Karnataka.\n\nComing to Kollywood, It is the Mother of all these industries in showing its culture, No other Indian Industry can show its native culture like Kollywood.\n\nKollywood made many movies with Tamil Nadu village backdrop.\n\nWhen Kannadigas and Telugu people watch Tamil movies, we will not fail to say this dialogue “Veellu Hero-Heroines aa??” (What? They are Hero and Heroine?)\n\nLook at Adi Pinisetty in the above image. In real life, he looks like this 👇👇\n\nThis is Aishwarya Rajesh in a movie:\n\nIn real life:\n\nMollywood also depicts Kerala culture.\n\nIf you think only the culture in these South Indian states is Indian Culture then it is completely wrong, These cultures are just part of Indian Culture, you have Bihari, Gujju, Bengali, Maratha, Odia, Kashmiri, Manipuri, etc. cultures as well.\n\nFor example, Sairat a Marathi movie depicts Rural Maharashtra culture.\n\nAnother movie Jogwa introduces the Social evils of rural Maharashtra.\n\nWhen a Transgender dies, she is buried and her dead body is beaten with slippers.\n\nOk,\n\nThese days some are believing Indian Culture == Hindu Culture. So, they think Tollywood (South Movies according to them) respects Hindu culture while Bollywood disrespects Hindu culture.\n\nFor your kind information, there are many movies in Tollywood where Hindu gods are disrespected.\n\nMany Hindus were angry because of Lord Shiva’s getup was made fun of in the PK movie.\n\nBut in one of the Telugu movies, Hanuman getup was even beaten.\n\nLord Hanuman’s getup was made to beg Hero.\n\nHe was punched by Hero:\n\nAnd Goddess Kali’s getup was beheaded in the same movie:\n\nIn another movie a boy pelt stones on Ganesh’s idol for Ganesh Chaturthi.\n\nIn another movie, Ravana is glorified, They show like Ravana was not wrong.\n\nIn another of Rajamouli’s movies, Chitragupta and Yama are made fun of.\n\nChitragupta:\n\nYama:\n\nIn many movies, Krishna Getups are used for comedy.\n\nYeah, all these movies are produced in cute Tollywood only.\n\nSo, don’t judge any Industry by simply seeing one side, every coin has two sides.\n\nThanks!",
        "name": "Saket Reddy (సాకేత్ రెడ్డి )",
        "views": "15.1K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Do-you-think-that-in-South-cinema-they-show-the-real-Indian-culture-and-tradition",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Is there any online coaching facility for the MCA exam in the NIMCET?",
        "answer": "Dear Friends,\n\nAs per the 2023 March education survey report, Gate Indian Institute of Tutorials GATEIIT JP Nagar Bangalore is ranking on top of India for NIMCET MCA entrance examination.\n\nGateiit is known for it's high quality nimcet crash course and full courses with personal attention classes.\n\nBest teachers who all are nimcet toppers are teaching here with best efforts. Not only this they are also awarded coaching centre in India for their best performance.\n\nI hope you will like them.\n\nBest of luck for your upcoming 2024 nimcet exam preparation!",
        "name": "Sonali Ganguli",
        "views": "140 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-there-any-online-coaching-facility-for-the-MCA-exam-in-the-NIMCET",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Indian_Academia",
        "author": "u/invertisbareilly",
        "question": "Is BCA (bachelor of computer applications) a Professional or General degree",
        "upvotes": "10",
        "comment": "3",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Indian_Academia/comments/11d7pur/is_bca_bachelor_of_computer_applications_a/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/asbnoida",
        "author": "u/DifficultAccess4651",
        "question": "Best Career Options for BCA Graduates: What to Do Next",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/asbnoida/comments/ykyy6m/best_career_options_for_bca_graduates_what_to_do/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/wctmgurgaon23",
        "author": "u/wctmgurgaon23",
        "question": "Master of Computer Application (MCA): A Comprehensive Guide",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/wctmgurgaon23/comments/11ex4v1/master_of_computer_application_mca_a/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Can a 12th commerce student go for BCA?",
        "answer": "Yes, a commerce student can definitely join a Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) program after completing their 10+2 education. BCA is a popular undergraduate degree program that is open to students from different educational backgrounds, including commerce.\n\nBCA is a three-year degree program that covers various aspects of computer applications, including programming languages, software development, database management, and networking. However, the admission requirements for BCA may vary from institution to institution.\n\nSome colleges or universities may have specific eligibility criteria, such as a minimum percentage of marks in 10+2 or a specific combination of subjects. Therefore, it is always advisable to check the admission requirements of the institution you are interested in before applying for the BCA program.",
        "name": "Deepam Singh",
        "views": "20 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Can-a-12th-commerce-student-go-for-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the best institutes to study data science in chennai?",
        "answer": "You might be tired of this word, but this technology is very much trending nowadays. Every now and then, you might come across data science. The technology is gaining popularity and spreading like wildfire. Be it the top institutes, or e-learning platforms, each of them is providing training in this technology and many are showing interest as well. To get the most of data science, take up courses that have the option of domain specialisation.\n\nData science has many sub-fields in it, and you can choose any field of your choice as per your interest. But what you need to focus on is from which institute or online platform you want to gain knowledge or what kind of degree you would prefer. But if you are a resident of Chennai and looking for options around you, then a few universities are mentioned below.\n\nIndian Institute of Technology, Chennai\nProgram - Diploma in Data Science\nTerm - 8 months\nQualification - Candidate should have an undergraduate degree or at least two years of UG degree through any mode.\nAny working pros, freshers, or people seeking a job can apply for this program.\n\n2. SRM Institute of Science & Technology, Chennai\n\nThe institute is approved by UGC, accredited by NAAC with an A++ grade\nOffers MBA degree in data science, Business analytics\nBoth the degrees are for the term of two years.\n\n3. Vellore Institute of Technology, Chennai\n\nVIT is a renowned institute with UGC approval and is one of the deemed colleges of Chennai.\nThe offer M.Sc degree in data science\nThe course duration is for two years.\n\n4. Hindustan Institute of Science & Technology\n\nThe college is accredited by NAAC with grade A and is also UGC approved\nThey offer courses like MBA in business analytics, MCA in big data analytics and data science.\nThe term for all three courses is two years\n\n5. National Institute of Electronic and Information technology (NIELIT)\n\nThe institute is an autonomous college and is government-approved.\nThey offer a post-graduate diploma (PGD) in data science and analytics and an Advanced diploma in big data analytics.\nTo be eligible for this program you need to have a master's, BTech, MCA, BE, or any other equivalent degree.\n\nIf you do not prefer classroom study and want to learn data science online, there are quite a few options available. Online platforms offer certification or degree programs in this field. Also, individuals who work full-time might not find it feasible to enroll in programs in universities.\n\nSo what is to be done then?\n\nFor them, an alternative platform is available that allows them to get trained in fields of data science and that too with their specific domain.\n\nThis institute allows a working individual to take training and experience in any field of their choice.\n\nFollowing courses are offered by this institute for data science.\n\nAdvance Data science and AI Program with domain specialization\nFor managers: certification in AI, data science\n\nMore information about these programs is as follows.\n\nHands-on projects\nTo give students a view of a real-life situation, they are assigned projects to work on.\nProject experience is important as recruiters hire people with hands-on experience.\nIt provides real-time projects and capstones in every course.\nSome of the projects are BMW’s data science platform, Samsung’s health care app, etc.\nCertified programs\nIt will surely impress the hiring employers about the skills and experience you possess.\nYou will get a course completion certificate from IBM, a project completion certificate, and a micro-skills certificate\nDomain-specific coaching\nThe course of data science is designed for work professionals such that they can gain the same expertise related to their field.\nIt provides numerous specialization of domain electives like transportation, e-commerce, pharma, insurance, HR, tourism, hospitality, supply chain, manufacturing, social media, mechanical, marketing, automation, retail, telecommunication, energy, medical, oil, gas, and more.\nThe advantage is that when you apply for job roles linked to this field, you might be viewed as a valuable asset who has expertise in their domain with such skills.\n\nNot only this, it also provides hybrid sessions and project innovation labs: Students have access to both live project classes in more than seven cities and online project classes. Students can work at neighbouring project innovation labs, which are run by professionals in the business and are located in seven or more cities, including Delhi, Kolkata, Mumbai, Pune, Hyderabad, Chennai, and Bangalore. There, they will receive assistance from industry experts.\n\nA large selection of data science courses are available through Coursera, a well-known online learning environment. In a partnership with the University of Colorado Boulder, they provide a Master of Science in Data Science programme.\n\nFeatures\n\nBoth live and recorded classes will be offered to students.\nThe wide range of technologies and techniques that top data scientists utilise will be covered in this session for participants.\n\nWith these features the platform has some drawbacks too:\n\nThey don't offer domain specialised services.\nThey lack cutting-edge labs.\n\nIt is not possible for people who work jobs, attend classes in the universities full-time. They need something that fits with their schedule. These above insttutes has the option for that as well. If you really enjoy working with data and want to make a career in this field, go for the above options. As for the fresher student, look for other online e-learning centers.\n\nAll the best",
        "name": "Pravinth",
        "views": "451 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-institutes-to-study-data-science-in-chennai",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are the distance education courses offered by Lovely Professional University, Delhi?",
        "answer": "Hello reader,\n\nI hope you are doing well,\n\nLovely Professional University (LPU) is a private university located in Jalandhar, Punjab, India. It offers various distance education courses in different fields of study. Some of the courses offered by LPU in distance mode are:\n\nMBA - The distance MBA program offered by LPU is a two-year program that covers various aspects of management, including marketing, finance, human resources, and operations management.\nBBA - The distance BBA program offered by LPU is a three-year program that provides a foundation in business and management principles.\nMCA - The distance MCA program offered by LPU is a two-year program that provides a comprehensive understanding of computer applications and software development.\nBCA - The distance BCA program offered by LPU is a three-year program that provides a foundation in computer science and application development.\nB.Com - The distance B.Com program offered by LPU is a three-year program that covers various aspects of commerce, including accounting, taxation, and finance.\nPGDCA - The distance PGDCA program offered by LPU is a one-year program that provides a comprehensive understanding of computer applications and software development.\n\nLPU also offers various diploma and certificate courses in different fields of study. The distance education courses offered by LPU are designed to provide quality education to students who cannot attend regular classes due to various reasons.\n\nI hope the information shared by ne was helpful to you!\n\nThank you:)",
        "name": "Vidushi Sharma",
        "views": "39 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-distance-education-courses-offered-by-Lovely-Professional-University-Delhi",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Which job sector has more hiking, MCA or MBA?",
        "answer": "Very honestly, it depends on what college you attend. A second or third tier college will not give you great spikes. However, in a good college, say an IIM, an MBA student will get better hikes.\n\nFor a great hike, you will need a good CAT score. So I think it's better to focus on that. I started working on my basics from scratch by joining Physics Wallah's MBA course.\n\nIt also helped to network with alumni of my dream colleges on LinkedIn. It also depends on your skills of course. But as an MBA graduate, you will be managing computer science majors. In the tech or IT sector, an MBA grad will always earn more than an MCA graduate because of their position in the organization. So you must have some knowledge of the field. Especially, if you want to get hired in the tech sector.",
        "name": "R.suman",
        "views": "10 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-job-sector-has-more-hiking-MCA-or-MBA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "I want to become a software developer but I am not from engineering background is it possible for me?",
        "answer": "Sure. Generally people tend to do a MCA post graduation to get into Software.",
        "name": "Nabarun Mondal",
        "views": "1.2K views",
        "link": "https://agingwithanattitude.quora.com/Should-one-grow-old-gracefully-or-fight-it-all-the-way",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Can we study for an MCA in IIM?",
        "answer": "No, IIM provide different courses in management only. NIT's have the MCA course in the curriculum.\n\nUpvote of it seems helpful…",
        "name": "Infinity Education Services",
        "views": "401 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-better-opportunities-after-doing-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the negative effects of SEO on YouTube?",
        "answer": "There are several potential negative effects of search engine optimization (SEO) on YouTube:\n\nSpamming: Some content creators may use SEO tactics to manipulate search rankings and gain more views and subscribers, even if their content is low-quality or irrelevant. This can result in spamming of search results and make it harder for users to find the content they are looking for.\nOver-optimization: Over-optimizing video titles, tags, and descriptions with too many keywords can lead to a poor user experience. Viewers may be turned off by videos that appear to be stuffed with keywords and may perceive the content as low-quality or spammy.\nFocus on quantity over quality: Some creators may prioritize creating a large volume of videos with optimized titles and descriptions over creating high-quality content that engages and retains viewers. This can lead to a decrease in overall viewer satisfaction and engagement.\nUnfair competition: Creators with larger budgets or more resources may be able to invest more in SEO and gain an unfair advantage over smaller creators who cannot afford to invest in SEO.\nChanges to search algorithms: YouTube regularly updates its search algorithms to provide better results for users. Creators who rely heavily on SEO may be negatively impacted by these changes if their content is no longer deemed relevant or high-quality enough to rank well in search results.\n\nOverall, while SEO can be a useful tool for content creators on YouTube, it is important to balance it with a focus on creating high-quality content that engages and retains viewers.",
        "name": "Kveerakumar Mca",
        "views": "9 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-negative-effects-of-SEO-on-YouTube",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/tnvisa",
        "author": "u/getadmision",
        "question": "My bachelor is in science and master is in computer applications , I am working as cloud engineer from last 6-7 years, do you guys think I can get the TN status once I get the job in IT in US ?",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "2",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/tnvisa/comments/10sa6xc/my_bachelor_is_in_science_and_master_is_in/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Is the BCA degree worth doing?",
        "answer": "Hello everyone,\n\nI am a BCA graduate from Maharishi Markandeshwar University, Haryana. I am currently working as a website developer and earning lakhs today. So, it depends on you and the college you are pursuing this course. My college was having every facility and faculty also.\n\nI will give you all the details about BCA.\n\nAbout BCA\n\nA BCA course gives basic technical knowledge about software like website development, DBMS, C++ and Java etc. This course will help you to get into the IT field.\n\n(But I have to admit that the value of a BCA graduate is not equal to a B.tech computer science engineer because in B.tech CSE the study is in-depth. If you want some value like a Btech CSE you have to do MCA also.)\n\nCareer Opportunity\n\nThere is a boom in the IT sector in India. There are plenty of options to do a job in this sector. Every company today need an IT team to handle their website, app etc.\n\nThe BCA course is the best course to study if you want to become an IT expert.\n\nI will like to talk about my college also because it is a great college to study in India. The placement, crowd, faculties everything is great here.\n\nYou can type on google “mmu” and visit their website.",
        "name": "Sagar Aggarwal",
        "views": "1.5K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-the-BCA-degree-worth-doing",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which is the better course to study abroad after BCA?",
        "answer": "There is no one-size-fits-all answer to this question, as the best course of study abroad after BCA depends on your individual goals and interests.\n\nHowever, some popular options for studying abroad after BCA include pursuing a master's degree in business administration (MBA), studying computer science or engineering at a top university, or spending a semester or year abroad in a country with a different culture.\n\nWhichever route you choose, studying abroad after BCA can help you develop new skills and knowledge that will benefit you throughout your career.",
        "name": "John Irma",
        "views": "639 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-better-course-to-study-abroad-after-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/StudyInTheNetherlands",
        "author": "u/Adventurous-Band5267",
        "question": "Few questions about application for VU Amsterdam Computer science Master's degree",
        "upvotes": "7",
        "comment": "3",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/StudyInTheNetherlands/comments/ye0172/few_questions_about_application_for_vu_amsterdam/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Would Mensa notice if a person with an average IQ slipped into a meeting?",
        "answer": "Mensa is the top 2% which is one in every 50 people or one on every bus assuming a bus has 50 people on board. I was a local secretary for Mensa for 10 years and to be honest I didn't find them to be very high brow or profound. There were some arrogant and pretentious people but really just a mixed bag of very ordinary normal people trying to make new friends. It really is just a social club for people hoping to meet and make friends with lots of groups for shared interests from hiking to photography, music, board games and everything in between. Generally polite nice people and a person would have to be considerably lower in IQ to be a stand out and they would probably be polite and talk about what the person was talking about. I am also a senior fellow of ISPE which is a top 0.1% club and there it is also a social club more than anything and once again most conversations were day to day trivia but with far fewer members so less chances to meet lots of people in person.",
        "name": "Neil McA.",
        "views": "2.2K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-salary-for-MCA-holders",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/gamedev",
        "author": "u/Craft_Tech",
        "question": "Passed out from college after doing Bachelors in computer Science, Want to get into Game Dev Industry, Kinda lost",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "5",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/gamedev/comments/zma4xh/passed_out_from_college_after_doing_bachelors_in/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which is better, MCA or MSc Computer Science from a private college?",
        "answer": "MCA is best from private college.As it offers a greater amount of practical exposure to aspirants, while M.Sc offers more research scope for graduates.\n\n💖 Hope this helps you 💖",
        "name": "Miss᭄𝄞➳⃝ANNU᭄✿ɢɪʟʟ࿐",
        "views": "266 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-government-colleges-for-an-MCA-in-Delhi",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which is the best college in Chennai for MCA?",
        "answer": "SRM institute of science and technology is best as per 2022 ranking.",
        "name": "Amit Sharma",
        "views": "238 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-opportunities-or-placements-available-at-present-for-students-who-have-been-admitted-into-the-integrated-MCA-program-at-Lovely-Professional-University",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Can I take admission in LPU on September in an online BCA?",
        "answer": "Hello reader,\n\nI hope you are doing well,\n\nYes, you can take admitted to Lovely Professional University (LPU) in September in an online BCA course. LPU is one of the top universities in India and offers a wide range of courses and degrees in various fields. The university has an extensive online learning platform and offers students the opportunity to pursue their studies from the comfort of their own homes.\n\nThe online BCA course offered by LPU is one of the most sought-after courses and is highly respected in the industry. The course covers the fundamentals of computer applications, programming, database management, software engineering, web development, and business analytics. The course also provides critical skills in data analysis, communication, project management, and problem-solving. The curriculum is designed to equip students with the required skills and knowledge to become successful professionals in the Information Technology (IT) sector.\n\nThe online BCA course at LPU is highly flexible and students can choose to study at times and locations that best suit their lifestyle and needs. There are several payment options available and students can also avail of scholarships and other financial assistance. The duration of the course is three years and students can also opt for an additional year to complete their BCA degree.\n\nThe online BCA course from LPU also provides students with the opportunity to gain industry-relevant certifications such as Microsoft Certified Solutions Associate (MCSA) and Oracle Database Administrator (ODA). The university also provides job-oriented workshops and training programs to help students gain an edge in the IT industry.\n\nIn conclusion, the online BCA course from LPU is an ideal choice for those who wish to pursue a career in the IT sector. The course provides students with the necessary skills and knowledge to succeed in the industry and is highly respected by employers. The course is highly flexible and also provides students with the opportunity to earn industry-recognized certifications.\n\nI hope it helps!\n\nThank you:)",
        "name": "Vidushi Sharma",
        "views": "36 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-take-admission-in-LPU-on-September-in-an-online-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/digiomg",
        "author": "u/digiomg",
        "question": "MCA Top Colleges in India, Best College for Master of Computer Application (MCA)",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/digiomg/comments/u9ded5/mca_top_colleges_in_india_best_college_for_master/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/IWantOut",
        "author": "u/Broad-Worldliness7",
        "question": "[IWANTOUT] 20M India -> Australia",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "1",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/IWantOut/comments/11r1wbp/iwantout_20m_india_australia/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/saryuun12",
        "author": "u/saryuun12",
        "question": "Best BCA college in Dehradun| Bachelor of Computer Application",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/saryuun12/comments/12abxdc/best_bca_college_in_dehradun_bachelor_of_computer/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which are some best colleges in Delhi-NCR for BCA?",
        "answer": "List of Top BCA Colleges In Delhi NCR based on 2022 Ranking\n\n*WCTM (world college of technology and management) Gurugram.\n\n*IMS Noida, Noida. ...\n\n*Lingaya's Vidyapeeth, Faridabad. ...\n\n*VIPS, New Delhi. …\n\n*Sharda University, Greater Noida. ...\n\n*Noida International University, Greater Noida. ...\n\n*IPEM Ghaziabad, Ghaziabad. ...\n\n*FIMT, New Delhi.\n\nPersonally, I would say WCTM- World College Of Technology And Management, Gurugram is best.\n\nWCTM was ranked no 1 in Gurugram by Times of India survey 2022, in engineering, BBA and placements.\n\nEvery student is required to attend all lectures, tutorials, practical’s and other prescribed curricular and co-curricular activities. * Special care is taken to maintain all-round discipline in the College. Students must attend their classes regularly. According to the rules of the Institute students must have 75 % attendance or above in each subject for being eligible to appear in University examinations. Ragging is totally prohibited in WCTM.\n\nThe department of Computer Science at the World College of Technology and Management envisions imparting practical learning in software development and to train the students to develop soft skills with global standards. Further, enhance their knowledge in the field of Computer Science.\n\nWe provide the best of the infrastructure, faculty that teaches the basics of computer applications and software developments. We have also successfully placed our students in the top-most companies of the world.\n\nWorld College of Technology and Management checks all the boxes for being the best BCA college in Gurgaon.\n\nWe ensure that when our students walk out with good jobs in top companies, they excel in their chosen field and successfully rise in their careers. The department owns air-conditioned Apple Computer Labs connected with servers, online UPS and printers. It also has state of the art computer systems configured with Apple IOS, i3 12th generation, i5 and i7 processors with Windows-7 and Linux operating systems. Apart from the different language processors, multimedia packages, MSDN packages and graphic packages. Visual tools and DTP packages are also available. The department has a 100 Mbps leased line internet facility and all the nodes are deployed for students to browse the internet.\n\nVisit this link to learn more: Best engineering college in Gurgaon | Best engineering college in Delhi NCR | WCTM",
        "name": "Sanchit Yadav",
        "views": "1.2K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-some-best-colleges-in-Delhi-NCR-for-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "How good are the Impetus Gurukul’s MCA NIMCET video content lectures?",
        "answer": "Impetus Gurukul is one of the best online education portals which offers high-quality video content lectures for various courses.\n\nThe MCA NIMCET video content lectures offered by Impetus Gurukul are very good and have helped many students in clearing the examination.\n\nThe faculty members are highly experienced and knowledgeable and they make sure that all the concepts are explained in a clear and concise manner.\n\nOverall, I would recommend Impetus Gurukul to everyone who wants to learn from the best!",
        "name": "Ronald Debose",
        "views": "226 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-best-university-for-distance-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Is it worth it if a full stack developer course is running and start an MCA?",
        "answer": "Whether pursuing a full-stack developer course or an MCA degree is worth it depends on your individual goals and career aspirations.\n\nIf you're interested in becoming a software developer, a full-stack developer course could be a great option to gain practical skills and knowledge. If you want to broaden your knowledge of computer science and pursue higher-level positions in the IT industry, an MCA degree might be the way to go.\n\nUltimately, it's all about what you want to achieve in your career, so take some time to consider your interests and future goals before making a decision.\nBest of luck to you! :)",
        "name": "Asma Simreen",
        "views": "44 views",
        "link": "https://codelogically.quora.com/Is-it-worth-it-if-a-full-stack-developer-course-is-running-and-start-an-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What are some colleges in Delhi for doing a BCA?",
        "answer": "Bachelor of computer applications is considered one of the most opted courses after 12th standard. This three-year under-graduate degree course is opted by those who wish to delve into the world of technology and computer languages. BCA is one of the most popular options to get the career started in the field of IT.\n\nHere is list of top colleges/ universities offering Bachelor of Computer Application degree course in Delhi:\n\n1. World college of Technology and Management (WCTM)\n\n2. Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha university (GGSIPU)\n\n3. Vivekanand institute of professional studies\n\n4. Delhi Skill and entrepreneurship university (DSEU)\n\n5. Indra Gandhi National Open University New Delhi\n\n6. Baba sahib Ambedkar technical education society\n\n7. Institute of Information Technology and Management\n\nThere is no dearth of colleges offering BCA degree course in Delhi NCR, but I would suggest you World college of Technology and Management (WCTM) as the best option. What gives this institute a cut above the rest?\n\n1. Placement record- WCTM has an impeccable placement record.\n\n2. Experienced faculty- Most of the WCTM faculty members are experienced teachers from Indian B-schools.\n\n3. Pedagogy – WCTM offers an interactive-digital pedagogy for your three-year course\n\n4. 24x7 support- The WhatsApp support groups available for the students 24 x 7.\n\n5. Exposure- The college offers internships, workshops, seminars, and other morale boosting competitions every now and then.\n\n6. Infrastructure- WCTM has a world class, aesthetically designed infrastructure in an 18-acre lush green campus.\n\nConsidering the following factors, WCTM is amongst the best BCA colleges in Delhi NCR. Their systematic way of teaching, experienced faculty, extensive curriculum world class infrastructure, outstanding placement record, and salary package makes this institute to the top of the list.\n\nVisit this link for more information:\n\nBest engineering college in Gurgaon | Best engineering college in Delhi NCR | WCTM\nWCTM is one of the best engineering college in Gurgaon. We have adopted international teaching standards that make us the best engineering college in Delhi NCR.\nhttps://www.wctmgurgaon.com/",
        "name": "Aman Sachdeva",
        "views": "2.1K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-colleges-in-Delhi-for-doing-a-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Is a BCA a technical course?",
        "answer": "• Certainly, BCA is a technical course the duration of the course is 3 years and divided into 6 semesters. It comprises of the subjects like:\n\n• database\n\n• networking\n\n• data structure\n\n• core programming languages like ‘C’ and ‘java’\n\n• This course provides a lot of opportunities to the students who are interested in computer field and wants to work in the IT sector as programmer or software developer.\n\n• If you are the student of LPU then you can get the all the positive outcomes from this Programme; Domain Knowledge: How to analyse problems in different areas of information technology, interpret and present findings effectively using mathematical and communication skills.\n\nScope\n\nThere is a huge scope in the field of BCA. One can do job or can go for higher studies after the completion of course, Self-employment option is also available.\n\nTop Recruiters:\n\nA number of top recruiters look for the fresher degree holders for offering opportunity of work with. BCA is one of the demanding courses under the IT sector and LPU gives the best opportunity to work with reputed organization (MNC)\n\nMy younger brother did the BCA programme from Lovely Professional University in the year 2019 and got placed in an IT company with a good salary package\n\n“I hope this will help you”",
        "name": "Shilpa Sachdav",
        "views": "2.3K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-a-BCA-a-technical-course",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Is distance education for an MCA valid?",
        "answer": "The name of the degree doesn’t decide its worth, it is your passion and dedication that decides the worth of the degree. Masters of computer application (MCA) is an postgraduate degree course which is now available in both offline and online mode that opens doors for people who want to learn more about it. It is a course which offers knowledge and training in IT field and helps to learn different computer languages like java and c++. It teaches students about the IT world.\n\nThe online MCA program offers a number of specializations like data operations, data scientists and many more. This course is divided into four semesters, an online masters of computer application (MCA) degree makes you the ideal candidate for taking up potions in IT company.\n\nYou can also get a good placement in corporate, if you choose the right place to peruse your MCA degree. Even universities help you in this, to get a good package and a good position in job.\n\n‘Manav Rachna Centre for Distance and Online Education’ is one of the best universities to learn online Masters of computer application (MCA) because it provides the most amazing overall experience. In their online MCA course, the faculty of Manav Rachna provides real life case studies for better understanding, it is a great opportunity to earn while learning new skills and they provide industry exposure too which is a must nowadays.\n\nMCA\n - Online Programmes",
        "name": "Nishant Jawa",
        "views": "1.7K views",
        "link": "https://itjobscareers.quora.com/What-is-the-career-scope-after-a-BCA-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Can I take the IPU CET BCA if I had IP as an additional subject (6th subject)?",
        "answer": "So from 2023 IPU CET for UG courses comes under CUET so you have to give the CUET exam for taking admission in BCA in IPU.\n\nIt doesn’t matter is it your 6th or additional subject you are eligible for BCA in IP\n\nYou have to give the exam for the below subjects:\n\nEnglish - Section IA: Languages ii. Mathematics – Section II iii. Computer Science/ Information Practice ( Section II iv. General Test – Section III\n\nEligibility:\n\nPass in 12th Class of 10+2 of CBSE or equivalent with a minimum of 50% marks in aggregate* with pass in English (core or elective or functional). Mathematics or Computer Science / or any other subject related to Computer Science.",
        "name": "Aditya Aggarwal",
        "views": "27 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-take-the-IPU-CET-BCA-if-I-had-IP-as-an-additional-subject-6th-subject",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/gradadmissions",
        "author": "u/SJM_reddit",
        "question": "Universities offering computer science master's degrees in the USA without application fees",
        "upvotes": "2",
        "comment": "2",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/gradadmissions/comments/10h0cfo/universities_offering_computer_science_masters/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What is the scope of an MCA graduate in the UPSC examination?",
        "answer": "same as others.\n\nGood luck",
        "name": "Upendra Singh",
        "views": "480 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Are-degrees-like-BCA-and-MCA-recognised-in-the-UK-and-USA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/dataanalysis",
        "author": "u/WorkerChance",
        "question": "I am an international job applicant and just completed my Masters here in the US. I have an MSc in engineering management and a bachelors in Computer science. I know python, sql, tableau And advanced excel. Have applied to around 400 jobs by now, got rejected. I don’t know what to do. Please help.",
        "upvotes": "17",
        "comment": "22",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/dataanalysis/comments/omf0x8/i_am_an_international_job_applicant_and_just/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "I have completed a BCA. Am I eligible for NIC requirements?",
        "answer": "No, As per the notification BCA is not among eligible branches however you need to upgrade to one more level to MCA to become eligible.\n\nHere is the screenshot of required notification page.",
        "name": "Pawan Kumar",
        "views": "66 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/I-have-completed-a-BCA-Am-I-eligible-for-NIC-requirements",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/kolkata",
        "author": "u/the_scientist-7367",
        "question": "Admission in college",
        "upvotes": "4",
        "comment": "18",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/kolkata/comments/v120ur/admission_in_college/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Does NIT, IIT or bit provide BCA course?",
        "answer": "NIT, IIT, and BIT do not offer BCA courses.",
        "name": "April Grant",
        "views": "438 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Does-NIT-IIT-or-bit-provide-BCA-course",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What should I pursue, an MCA or MBA after a BCA?",
        "answer": "I am an MCA graduate from Maharishi Markandeshwar University, Haryana. I know about both the courses because I have also gone through this where I found which course to do, I will tell you every aspect of the advantages and disadvantages of pursuing this course.\n\nMBA\n\nAdvantages\n\nSalary is high at starting\nAs you are from a coding background, getting a job will be easier because IT is required everywhere.\nYou will get good exposure and you can get into IT again if you want because there is MBA in IT also.\n\nDisadvantages\n\nThe fees are very high\nThere is no guarantee that you will get a job or not.\n\nMCA\n\nAdvantages\n\nThe fees are less compared to MBA\nBooming industry\nYou will surely get a hike as your knowledge will increase when you work.\nLess competition when we compare it to MBA\nAfter getting at least 4 years of experience the MCA graduate gets a good salary package.\nTheir job is much safer because they get the same type of work in every company for example if the job profile is the same as a website developer.\nMore job opportunities\n\nDisadvantages\n\nThere is a time when you get bored of doing coding, especially when you get stuck.\nYou will not get a good amount of package in starting.\n\nAt last, I would share my experience when I was in college at Maharishi Markandeshwar University, Haryana (MMU) I was very satisfied with the facilities and faculty.",
        "name": "Sagar Aggarwal",
        "views": "460 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-good-is-Lovely-Professional-University-for-an-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "I have done my 12th with PCB and want to do a BCA. Will I be eligible to take the MCA entrance exam like the NIMCET or else without having maths in 12th?",
        "answer": "Yes, if you have mathematics/ statistics in graduation and have secured a 60% or 6.5 cgpa aggregate then definitely.",
        "name": "Rishav Bajaj",
        "views": "10 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/I-have-done-my-12th-with-PCB-and-want-to-do-a-BCA-Will-I-be-eligible-to-take-the-MCA-entrance-exam-like-the-NIMCET-or-else-without-having-maths-in-12th",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is the difference between a B.Sc and a BCA? Which is better for doing research after graduation?",
        "answer": "B.Sc is Bachelor's of science with the subject of your choice from science stream.\n\nBCA is Bachelor's of Computer Applications which have a certain set of subjects.\n\nBoth are good for research it depends on your choice in which area you want to do the research,in pure science or in computer application field.Both fields have wide scope for research.",
        "name": "Khushi Singh",
        "views": "11 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-a-B-Sc-and-a-BCA-Which-is-better-for-doing-research-after-graduation",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Which is the best MCA College in terms of Curriculam in India?",
        "answer": "in this era of Information Technology the value of MCA degree has been increased manifold because MCA degree not only unlocks avenues of glittering career but also strengthens technical skills of students for various technologies focused on the conceptual framework. The programme is designed to prepare neat-handed professionals in the sphere of Information Technology. The programme lays stress on the latest programming language and tools to develop cutting-edge software applications.\n\nThis is the most lucrative advantage of MCA degree. Whether you are a fresher or experienced in your field, if your skills match the demand of the industry, then you can demand salary according to your wish. Tech giant companies like IBM, Google, Amazon, Facebook offer lucrative Pay-Packet to talented candidates.\n\nSome engineers also prefer doing MCA after their graduation as it offers better placement opportunities.After MCA, many candidates joined as Software Developer/Programmer/Engineer, IT Desk Troubleshooting, IT system Analyst, Software Application Designer, Software Consultant, Web Designer and Developer, Technical Writer, Systems Developer, Quality Assurance and Software Testing.\n\nIf I talk about Lovely professional University, it offers MCA and MCA Hons with Data science which is in huge demand on today market.\n\nLPU offers MCA and MCA Hons with Data Science in tie with Transorg Analytics. So, I would like to share why you must choose MCA Hons with data science, LPU provides-\n\n1.Innovative Industry –oriented courses and Professional Certifications\n\n2. Seed Money To encourage and support students in entrepreneurship and research activities, various types of seed money funding’s are granted.\n\n3. Industry - Live Projects\n\n4 Industry- Attachment/ Internship\n\n5. Competitions/ Bootcamps/ Codefests\n\nIn addition to this, about the placements, the highest package for 2021–22 session is Rs32 lacs per annum in MCA programmes with 98% of placements records.\n\nHope this information could help you!",
        "name": "Hardik Vashisht",
        "views": "13 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-MCA-College-in-terms-of-Curriculam-in-India",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/movingtojapan",
        "author": "u/coldbottleoficebrew",
        "question": "is BCA course valid??",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "8",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/movingtojapan/comments/vpnbyo/is_bca_course_valid/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "How would you gauge social media's return on investment?",
        "answer": "The return on investment (ROI) of social media can be difficult to measure because social media platforms are often used for a variety of purposes, such as brand awareness, customer engagement, and driving website traffic. However, there are several metrics that can help gauge the ROI of social media, including:\n\nReach: The number of people who have seen your social media content.\nEngagement: The level of interaction your social media content receives, such as likes, comments, and shares\nConversions: The number of people who take a desired action as a result of your social media content, such as making a purchase or filling out a form.\nReferral traffic: the amount of traffic driven to your website from social media.\nRevenue: The amount of revenue generated as a result of your social media efforts\n\nTo gauge the ROI of social media, you will need to track these metrics over time and compare them to your investment in social media, including the cost of creating and publishing content, running ads, and managing social media accounts. By doing so, you can determine whether your social media efforts are generating a positive ROI and adjust your strategy as needed to optimize results.",
        "name": "Kveerakumar Mca",
        "views": "10 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-would-you-gauge-social-medias-return-on-investment",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is the eligibility for an MCA in SRM?",
        "answer": "Being an Educational Consultant, MCA (Master of Computer Applications) program at SRM Institute of Science and Technology, candidates must meet the following eligibility criteria:\n\nEducational qualification: Candidates must have a Bachelor's degree with a minimum of 50% marks in any discipline from a recognized university. Candidates who have studied Mathematics/Statistics/Computer Science/Computer Applications/Business Mathematics/Business Statistics as a subject in their 10+2 or undergraduate level are preferred.\nEntrance exam: Candidates must have a valid score in the SRM Joint Entrance Examination (SRMJEEE) for MCA or other national level entrance exams such as TANCET, NIMCET, or GATE.\nAge limit: There is no age limit for admission to the MCA program at SRM Institute of Science and Technology.\n\nHope it’s fine, feel free to contact 📲8292699093 (Call/WhatsApp) regarding colleges and admissions.\n\nThank you 😊",
        "name": "Sandesh Kumar",
        "views": "66 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-eligibility-for-an-MCA-in-SRM",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which degree is better: BTech or MCA?",
        "answer": "MCA is superior than B.Tech because, unlike B. Tech, which just awards a graduation certificate, it is actually a post-graduate degree program. In conclusion, MCA graduates have greater job prospects than B. Tech graduates. However, in the end, securing the correct placements also heavily depends on the competence and abilities of the applicant.\n\nWith more options available, selecting the best course for you is becoming a very difficult task for students. The curriculum and topics taught in both of these courses are quite similar, although MCA is a three-year post-graduate degree whereas B. Tech. CSE is a four-year undergraduate program. MCA has a strong emphasis on the creation of computer applications, whereas B. Tech is an engineering-based school with a focus on IT.\n\n(Hope This Answer Will Help You)",
        "name": "College Sakha",
        "views": "680 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Can-one-do-MCA-after-BA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Why is a BCA considered engineering in the IIM admission criteria?",
        "answer": "No, BCA is not considered engineering, but for some IIMs, they might come under the same stream or AC tier.",
        "name": "Sachin Chandra",
        "views": "155 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Why-is-a-BCA-considered-engineering-in-the-IIM-admission-criteria",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the career prospects for MBA after doing MCA?",
        "answer": "The combination of an MBA and MCA degree can offer several career opportunities in the fields of management and information technology. Some potential career paths for an individual with an MBA and MCA degree may include:\n\nIT Manager: As an IT manager, you would be responsible for managing technology infrastructure, developing and implementing technology solutions, and overseeing IT teams. With an MBA degree, you would have the skills necessary to manage the business aspects of technology, such as budgeting, planning, and project management.\nBusiness Analyst: Business analysts are responsible for identifying opportunities for improvement within an organization and recommending solutions. With an MCA and MBA degree, you would have the technical knowledge required to analyze IT systems and the business skills necessary to recommend solutions that align with organizational goals.\nEntrepreneurship: With an MBA and MCA degree, you could start your own business in the technology sector. Your technical knowledge, combined with your business skills, would help you develop a business plan, secure funding, and manage the operations of your business.\nTechnology Consultant: Technology consultants work with organizations to identify areas where technology can be used to improve business processes. With an MBA and MCA degree, you would have the technical knowledge to understand the technology needs of an organization and the business skills to provide recommendations for technology solutions.\n\nOverall, the combination of an MBA and MCA degree can offer a wide range of career opportunities in the technology and business sectors.",
        "name": "Ujjwal Matoliya",
        "views": "74 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-prospects-for-MBA-after-doing-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Which course is better for a student, an MTech or an MCA (from a good private college) after completing an MSc degree in Physics?",
        "answer": "A MTech from a good institution is better than MCA from a good institution, a MCA from a good institution is better than a MTech from a average institution",
        "name": "Sreenavin P",
        "views": "12 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-course-is-better-for-a-student-an-MTech-or-an-MCA-from-a-good-private-college-after-completing-an-MSc-degree-in-Physics",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "How is SGT University for BCA in artificial & machine Learning?",
        "answer": "SGT University is a well-known university in India that offers a BCA program with a specialization in Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning. The university has a dedicated School of Computer Science and Applications that offers this program.\n\nThe BCA program in Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning at SGT University is designed to equip students with the necessary knowledge and skills required to develop intelligent machines and systems. The program covers topics such as machine learning, data mining, computer vision, natural language processing, and deep learning.\n\nThe university has a team of experienced faculty members who are experts in the field of computer science and technology. The faculty members use modern teaching methods and technologies to ensure that students receive the best possible education.\n\nThe university also has a strong industry-academia interface, which means that students get the opportunity to work on industry projects and gain practical experience. Additionally, the university has tie-ups with several reputed companies, which helps students secure internships and job placements.\n\nOverall, SGT University is a good option for students who want to pursue a BCA program with a specialization in Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning.",
        "name": "Rana Mazumdar",
        "views": "32 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-is-SGT-University-for-BCA-in-artificial-machine-Learning",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/PE_Exam",
        "author": "u/Kakarot_J",
        "question": "Total Number of Professional Engineering References for an Applicant with an Accredited Master and Bachelor Degrees in Engineering",
        "upvotes": "3",
        "comment": "6",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/PE_Exam/comments/1281suj/total_number_of_professional_engineering/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are the career options after earning a Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA)?",
        "answer": "Top 10 Career Options After BCA\n\nTechnical Analyst. It is one of the most interesting job options after the BCA course. ...\nData Scientist. ...\nWeb Developer. ...\nDigital Marketer. ...\nSoftware Developer Trainee. ...\nBanking Sector. ...\nE-commerce Executive. ...\nEducator.",
        "name": "Ravi Kumar",
        "views": "30 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-options-after-earning-a-Bachelor-of-Computer-Applications-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which are the best private colleges for an MCA?",
        "answer": "Top private colleges for MCA are:-\n\nBIT Mesra,\n\nVIT Vellore,\n\nJain University,\n\nThapar University,\n\nChrist University",
        "name": "Shreya Sinha",
        "views": "602 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-replace-my-car-battery-with-a-lithium-battery",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Kerala",
        "author": "u/sickboi33",
        "question": "Is BCA(Bachelor's in Computer Application)a good course after 12th?",
        "upvotes": "8",
        "comment": "11",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Kerala/comments/enp3qg/is_bcabachelors_in_computer_applicationa_good/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/india",
        "author": "u/Even-Client-3868",
        "question": "Can i start my degree and enter IT sector now that i am 24?",
        "upvotes": "13",
        "comment": "5",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/india/comments/10rwadw/can_i_start_my_degree_and_enter_it_sector_now/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is ideal salary of MCA freshers in India? (Pune, Banglore)",
        "answer": "In 2023 — ideal will be 5 to 6 LPA",
        "name": "Nikhil Kizhakkedath",
        "views": "132 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-ideal-salary-of-MCA-freshers-in-India-Pune-Banglore",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "twitter",
        "name": "lakhan thakkar",
        "handle": "@lakhan_99",
        "timestamp": "Nov 1, 2009",
        "text": "persuing Bachelor in computer application",
        "link": "https://twitter.com/lakhan_99/status/5334654865",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/SJSU",
        "author": "u/Fun_Cry_5656",
        "question": "Did Undergrad at UC Davis. My Computer Science Bachelors GPA was 2.6 or something terrible but I have 7 years of work experience in the Data Science space. How hard will it be to get into the data Analytics program here?",
        "upvotes": "9",
        "comment": "11",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/SJSU/comments/12b47tj/did_undergrad_at_uc_davis_my_computer_science/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/indianmedschool",
        "author": "u/Taiyou04",
        "question": "I'm 26. Can I do an MBBS after an MSc in Neural/Cognitive Science and NIOS Sr Secondary Biology examination?",
        "upvotes": "34",
        "comment": "24",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/indianmedschool/comments/ydrjsb/im_26_can_i_do_an_mbbs_after_an_msc_in/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/india",
        "author": "u/marvelousdayz",
        "question": "China or India for Undergraduate Studies?",
        "upvotes": "12",
        "comment": "6",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/india/comments/pkwz8q/china_or_india_for_undergraduate_studies/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/gngroupinstitutes",
        "author": "u/curious_geek19",
        "question": "Top BCA Program in UP | GN Group Of Institutes",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/gngroupinstitutes/comments/wgtrc8/top_bca_program_in_up_gn_group_of_institutes/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/bcaklekun",
        "question": "KLE GOOD BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATION COLLEGE IN BANGALORE",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/bcaklekun/comments/124mgso/kle_good_bachelor_of_computer_application_college/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are some of the best government BCA colleges to take admission in 2023?",
        "answer": "IPU, JMI, JNU .",
        "name": "Shiv Shankar Mishra",
        "views": "12 views",
        "link": "https://aspaceforeverything1.quora.com/What-are-some-of-the-best-government-BCA-colleges-to-take-admission-in-2023",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are the benefits of pursuing a career in stock market or management consultancy after completing an MCA?",
        "answer": "Completing an MCA (Master of Computer Applications) degree can provide you with a strong foundation in computer science and technology, which can be applied in a variety of industries, including finance and management consulting. Pursuing a career in stock market or management consultancy after completing an MCA can offer several benefits, including:\n\nUtilizing your analytical and problem-solving skills: An MCA degree equips you with analytical and problem-solving skills that are valuable in the stock market and management consultancy fields. You can use these skills to analyze complex data and provide strategic recommendations to clients.\nHigh earning potential: Both the stock market and management consultancy industries offer high earning potential for those with the right skills and experience. As you gain experience and develop a reputation for expertise, you can command higher salaries and compensation packages.\nOpportunities for growth and advancement: The stock market and management consultancy industries offer ample opportunities for growth and advancement. As you gain experience and build your skills, you can take on more challenging projects and move up the ranks in your organization.\nExposure to diverse industries: Both industries provide exposure to diverse industries and clients, which can broaden your knowledge and skill set. This exposure can also provide you with the opportunity to network with industry leaders and build your professional reputation.\nChallenging and dynamic work: Both the stock market and management consultancy industries are dynamic and constantly evolving, providing you with challenging and engaging work. This can keep you motivated and engaged in your career.\n\nOverall, pursuing a career in the stock market or management consultancy after completing an MCA can offer many benefits and opportunities for growth, learning, and financial rewards. However, it's important to research the industries and companies carefully and determine whether they align with your personal goals and values",
        "name": "Nishna Waichale",
        "views": "26 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-benefits-of-pursuing-a-career-in-stock-market-or-management-consultancy-after-completing-an-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/IndianTeenagers",
        "author": "u/ribs-bangalore",
        "question": "BCA course.",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "3",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/IndianTeenagers/comments/wv1z8m/bca_course/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What's the eligibility criteria for an MCA and what are the best colleges in India?",
        "answer": "One should choose a career option very judiciously. Because several colleges offer many career courses, it sometimes becomes overwhelming to choose the best course. You can choose MCA if you are looking for the best career option. This stands for a master's degree in Computer Application which helps to explore the Technology world comprehensively. That is why students with an MCA degree from the best MCA College in Haryana always have higher opportunities in the technology world. This article will provide you with important details about the MCA course and facts related to it.\n\nMCA syllabus and Eligibility for Best colleges:\n\nGenerally, the best MCA colleges in Haryana offer specialization in computer technology like:\n\nSystem management\nInformation system\nManagement system\nSystem engineering\nNetworking internet\nSoftware application\nHardware Technology,\nComputer Architecture and Organization\nComputer programming\nDiscrete mathematical structure\nData structure\nBusiness management\nOperation research and Optimization\n\nThe MCA programme has a duration of three years and consists of six semesters. Academic and practical schedules are included in each semester.\n\nFor admission to the best MCA colleges in Haryana candidate should have the following degree:\n\nBachelor's degree in computer application or Science/BCA,\nThe applicant must have completed a BSc, BCom or B.A or B.A. degree in mathematics at the 10+2 level. Mathematics is a critical factor for MCA courses.\n\nIt depends on the University on what kind of eligibility criteria they are asking. The merit list is usually prepared after an entrance exam or on the basis of aggregate academic performance. Most of the time, best MCA colleges prefer entrance exams for MCA courses. MBA students of the Information Technology department can also join MCA courses. So if you are a student of any MBA college in Haryana, you definitely can do an MCA after it.\n\nDifference between MCA and PGDCA programs:\n\nComputer application specialization courses are of two types MCA and PGDCA. But there are some differences between these two courses. PGDCA means post-graduation diploma in computer application, and MCA means master of computer application. MCA is generally 3 Year course, and students, after graduation, can join the MCA program. A postgraduate diploma in computer application is 1-year course after graduation or a BBA. After a one-year PGDCA course, students can take admission directly to the 2nd year of the MCA program.\n\nBoth courses are available in the best MCA College in Haryana. Now the question is which course is more valuable, MCA or PGDCA. MCA is a 3-year professional program in computer technology, while PGDCA is a diploma course that provides fundamental knowledge on computer application. Therefore, students can select any of these degrees based on their career goals. But for a better opportunity in software and computer application, MCA is always best.\n\nStudents from the best BBA College in Haryana can also join in C.A. or PGDCA program after graduation. In that case, they must score 60% marks in graduation for eligibility. Students, after their BBA, can join the PGDCA program and be admitted to the 2nd year of MCA.\n\nOpportunity after MCA courses from the best colleges:\n\nMCA courses are always best for a student planning to get the opportunity in computer application. But students should seek admission to the best MCA Colleges in Haryana.\n\nThe best colleges always offer the perfect curriculum. They also offer proper practical and academic knowledge to the students which enable them to get good career opportunities. MCA students from top colleges always get better options than BCA or PGDCA courses. The greatest career options after obtaining an MCA are listed below.\n\nSoftware Developer\nHardware engineer\nDatabase Engineer\nCloud Architect\nIT architect\nSoftware consultant\nNetwork engineering\nSocial media manager\nEthical hacker\nQuality Assurance Analyst\nWeb Designer and developer\n\nTop opportunities in Computer Applications always come to the student of the best MCA College in Haryana. Students may get various job opportunities with a good salary scale in India and abroad. For example, a software developer and engineer's average salary is approximately 4 to 8 lakh INR per annum. The salary of database engineers and cloud architect ranges from Rs. 6 Lakh/per year and Rs. 4 lakh to 34.2 lakh per annum, respectively. You can therefore choose to pursue an MCA, which will give you a better possibility if you cannot gain admission to an MBA college in Haryana.\n\nTop MCA College in Haryana:\n\nIf you are looking for the best MCA College in Haryana, then TIMT is the best. This college is one of the best MCA colleges and offers the best MCA course. The offer the best teaching faculty with the most scientific syllabus to help the students to get better opportunities in the job market. This college is approved by AICTE and offers a certificate that is widely acceptable. Not only that, but it is also the best BBA College in Haryana.\n\nMCA always offers the best opportunity than other courses. The value of MCA courses are greater now than ever before because the entire world is dependent on technology. Sincere motivation and diligent work will get you into MCA if you plan to do so today. Any subject you are studying will always open up a fantastic earning possibility if you take an MCA degree. So, you should pick the best MCA course to give yourself the best chance for success.\n\nTilak Raj Chadha Institute of Management & Technology (TIMT) | Best MBA, MCA, BCA College in Haryana\nTIMT is one of best MBA, MCA, BCA College in Haryana, apply now. Top MBA colleges In Haryana has to know more about fee and admission fill personal details.\nhttps://www.timt.ac.in/",
        "name": "Subah",
        "views": "3 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Whats-the-eligibility-criteria-for-an-MCA-and-what-are-the-best-colleges-in-India",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/saryuun12",
        "author": "u/saryuun12",
        "question": "Best BCA college in Dehradun| Bachelor of Computer Application",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/saryuun12/comments/12cb9a5/best_bca_college_in_dehradun_bachelor_of_computer/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/bcaklekun",
        "author": "u/bcaklekun",
        "question": "KLE BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATION IN BANGALORE",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/bcaklekun/comments/11w8gxx/kle_bachelor_of_computer_application_in_bangalore/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/Topcollegeslnct",
        "author": "u/Topcollegeslnct",
        "question": "Master of Computer Application (MCA) - LNCT",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/Topcollegeslnct/comments/10woui7/master_of_computer_application_mca_lnct/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/TUe",
        "author": "u/tcbusinessschool",
        "question": "Number of applicants on the bachelor \"Computer Science and Engineering\"",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "6",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/TUe/comments/z6b5us/number_of_applicants_on_the_bachelor_computer/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/crawsecurityhub",
        "author": "u/vinodeducationist",
        "question": "What are the career opportunities in Cyber Security after graduation and master degree?",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/crawsecurityhub/comments/uk83r2/what_are_the_career_opportunities_in_cyber/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/MSCS",
        "author": "u/divaista",
        "question": "Is doing Masters in Computer Science worth it amidst current Market layoffs?",
        "upvotes": "22",
        "comment": "35",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/MSCS/comments/11ul5s2/is_doing_masters_in_computer_science_worth_it/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "I’m a class 12 (CBSE) commerce student with maths and computer science. Suppose if I fail in accounts and pass in the other 5 subjects, will I be able to get admission in colleges for a BBA or a BCA?",
        "answer": "If you gave your exams in 2023 (this year) then start studying in subjects which you think you could fail because board gives you an opportunity to give a compartment exam of that particular subject in which you failed, so if you got 25/100 in first exam but 60/100 in compartment then your compartment result will be accepted in college",
        "name": "Study",
        "views": "66 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/I-m-a-class-12-CBSE-commerce-student-with-maths-and-computer-science-Suppose-if-I-fail-in-accounts-and-pass-in-the-other-5-subjects-will-I-be-able-to-get-admission-in-colleges-for-a-BBA-or-a-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/learnprogramming",
        "author": "u/DifficultAccess4651",
        "question": "what language should i choose for data structure and algorithm c++ or java?",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "5",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/learnprogramming/comments/utqaf3/what_language_should_i_choose_for_data_structure/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which are the best colleges for MCA in India?",
        "answer": "There are many colleges that offer MCA courses in India.\n\nBut not all of these colleges are equally good.\n\nSome of the best colleges for MCA in India include the Indian Institutes of Technology (IITs), the National Institutes of Technology (NITs), and the Birla Institute of Technology and Science (BITS Pilani).\n\nThese colleges have excellent faculties, state-of-the-art facilities, and a great track record when it comes to producing successful MCA graduates.",
        "name": "Debra Mann",
        "views": "1.3K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-top-institutes-offering-MCA-and-BCA-courses-in-Delhi-NCR",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/UCI",
        "author": "u/Ironton245",
        "question": "“Bachelor in Information and Computer Sciences/Undeclared”? (Chose CS on application)",
        "upvotes": "4",
        "comment": "2",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/UCI/comments/11vcvpk/bachelor_in_information_and_computer/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/QuantumComputing",
        "author": "u/Taiyou04",
        "question": "Are there internship opportunities in quantum computing for which I do not have to be currently enrolled in a bachelor's/master's degree?",
        "upvotes": "4",
        "comment": "6",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/QuantumComputing/comments/10sepy7/are_there_internship_opportunities_in_quantum/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/gradadmissions",
        "author": "u/PrateekAwate",
        "question": "My application to UWO was sent from preliminary assessment to the Computer Science program for decision. What are my chances of getting in?",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "4",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/gradadmissions/comments/126v5ft/my_application_to_uwo_was_sent_from_preliminary/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Aalto",
        "author": "u/throwawayIELTS",
        "question": "Hey guys is SAT compulsory for bachelors in computer science won't they accept my application based on my transcripts and ielts?",
        "upvotes": "2",
        "comment": "6",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Aalto/comments/rxh2zw/hey_guys_is_sat_compulsory_for_bachelors_in/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/AskIndia",
        "author": "u/saryuun12",
        "question": "Due to finances after my 12th or intern, I joined an open university and took computer application as one of my core subjects. But I have this haunting feeling that I won't get a job in some big company due to my open university degree please can someone help me solve this dilemma",
        "upvotes": "3",
        "comment": "2",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/AskIndia/comments/11ttykm/due_to_finances_after_my_12th_or_intern_i_joined/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is the top college in Gaya?",
        "answer": "Chaitanya international Business College is best college for BBA BCA. Chaitanya International\n\nBusiness College, Gaya / Patna (Bihar) concentrates on individual talent and interest of a BBA / BCA student and tries to develop it. The faculty of Chaitanya Business College concentrates on the BBA / BCA student individually. The test and exams are conducted every week based on the BBA / BCA topics covered in that week. This helps the student to remember the topic easily. The college does not only concentrate on students aiming for management but also concentrates on students who aim for many other fields. College life skill course is fruitful for students career.",
        "name": "Anupam Raj",
        "views": "7 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-top-college-in-Gaya",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past hour",
        "question": "Can you guide me about the IT industry, programming languages, and career guidance? I am from non-IT and currently pursuing an MCA.",
        "answer": "I'd be happy to provide some guidance on the IT industry, programming languages, and career guidance.\n\nIT Industry: The IT industry is one of the fastest-growing industries in the world. It encompasses a wide range of areas, such as software development, IT support, cybersecurity, data analytics, and more. The demand for IT professionals is high, and the industry is constantly evolving with new technologies and trends.\n\nProgramming Languages: There are many programming languages in use today, and each has its own strengths and weaknesses. Some popular programming languages include:\n\nJava: Java is an object-oriented programming language that's widely used for building web applications, mobile apps, and games.\nPython: Python is a versatile language that's used for web development, data science, machine learning, and more.\nJavaScript: JavaScript is a scripting language that's used for building dynamic web applications.\nC++: C++ is a high-performance language that's used for building operating systems, compilers, and other low-level applications.\nRuby: Ruby is a dynamic, object-oriented language that's used for web development, game development, and more.\n\nCareer Guidance: Here are some tips for pursuing a career in IT:\n\nGain experience: Try to gain as much experience as possible through internships, entry-level jobs, or personal projects. This will help you build your skills and develop a portfolio of work.\nSpecialize: Consider specializing in a particular area of IT, such as web development, cybersecurity, or data analytics. This will make you more marketable and in-demand in the job market.\nNetwork: Attend industry events, join online communities, and connect with professionals in the field. Networking can help you learn about job opportunities and stay up-to-date on industry trends.\nStay up-to-date: The IT industry is constantly changing, so it's important to stay up-to-date on new technologies, tools, and techniques. Take online courses, read industry blogs, and attend conferences to stay informed.\nSoft skills: In addition to technical skills, employers also value soft skills such as communication, teamwork, and problem-solving. Work on developing these skills to make yourself a well-rounded IT professional.\n\nOverall, pursuing a career in IT can be a rewarding and fulfilling choice. With dedication, hard work, and a willingness to learn, you can build a successful career in this exciting industry.",
        "name": "Jebin Adt",
        "views": "3 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Can-you-guide-me-about-the-IT-industry-programming-languages-and-career-guidance-I-am-from-non-IT-and-currently-pursuing-an-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are the career opportunities for BCA graduates at BITS Pilani?",
        "answer": "BCA (Bachelor of Computer Applications) graduates from BITS Pilani, one of the top engineering colleges in India, have various career opportunities. Here are some of them:\n\nSoftware Developer: BCA graduates can work as software developers in various industries such as IT, e-commerce, and finance. They can develop, test, and maintain software applications using programming languages such as Java, Python, and C++.\nWeb Developer: BCA graduates can work as web developers, creating and maintaining websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and other web technologies. They can work as front-end developers, back-end developers, or full-stack developers.\nDatabase Administrator: BCA graduates can work as database administrators, responsible for maintaining and securing databases for organizations. They can design, implement, and maintain databases using SQL, Oracle, or other database management systems.\nNetwork Administrator: BCA graduates can work as network administrators, responsible for maintaining and securing computer networks for organizations. They can design, implement, and maintain network infrastructure using network protocols such as TCP/IP.\nIT Consultant: BCA graduates can work as IT consultants, BCA (Bachelor of Computer Applications) graduates from BITS Pilani, one of the top engineering colleges in India, have various career opportunities. Here are some of them:\nSoftware Developer: BCA graduates can work as software developers in various industries such as IT, e-commerce, and finance. They can develop, test, and maintain software applications using programming languages such as Java, Python, and C++.\nWeb Developer: BCA graduates can work as web developers, creating and maintaining websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and other web technologies. They can work as front-end developers, back-end developers, or full-stack developers.\nDatabase Administrator: BCA graduates can work as database administrators, responsible for maintaining and securing databases for organizations. They can design, implement, and maintain databases using SQL, Oracle, or other database management systems.\nNetwork Administrator: BCA graduates can work as network administrators, responsible for maintaining and securing computer networks for organizations. They can design, implement, and maintain network infrastructure using network protocols such as TCP/IP.\nIT Consultant: BCA graduates can work as IT consultants, providing advisory services to organizations on how to use technology to achieve their business goals. They can provide advice on hardware and software selection, system integration, and IT security.\nData Analyst: BCA graduates can work as data analysts, responsible for analyzing and interpreting data to help organizations make informed decisions. They can use tools such as Excel, R, or Python to perform data analysis and visualization.\n\nOverall, BCA graduates from BITS Pilani have a wide range of career opportunities in various industries, and they can choose a career path that aligns with their interests and skills\n\nadvisory services to organizations on how to use technology to achieve their business goals. They can provide advice on hardware and software selection, system integration, and IT security.\nData Analyst: BCA graduates can work as data analysts, responsible for analyzing and interpreting data to help organizations make informed decisions. They can use tools such as Excel, R, or Python to perform data analysis and visualization.\n\nOverall, BCA graduates from BITS Pilani have a wide range of career opportunities in various industries, and they can choose a career path that aligns with their interests and skills",
        "name": "Earning Affiliate Marketing",
        "views": "12 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-opportunities-for-BCA-graduates-at-BITS-Pilani",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the advantages and disadvantages of VIT and SCTC (MCA)?",
        "answer": "VIT and SCTC are two different educational institutions, with different programs and offerings. Here are some advantages and disadvantages of each:\n\nAdvantages of VIT:\n\nReputation: VIT has a good reputation in India and internationally for its engineering programs, particularly in the fields of computer science and information technology. It has been consistently ranked among the top private engineering colleges in India.\nInfrastructure: VIT has a modern and well-equipped campus with facilities such as labs, libraries, sports facilities, and hostels. The campus is Wi-Fi enabled and has a good network connectivity.\nPlacements: VIT has a strong placement record with many top companies visiting the campus for recruitment. The placement cell also provides training and guidance to students to help them prepare for the recruitment process.\n\nDisadvantages of VIT:\n\nHigh Fees: VIT's fees are relatively high compared to other colleges, and this can be a financial burden for some students.\nLimited Focus: VIT's programs are focused mainly on engineering, and students interested in other fields may not find the college suitable.\n\nAdvantages of SCTC (MCA):\n\nAffordability: SCTC is a government-run institution, and its fees are relatively lower than those of private colleges. This makes it accessible to students from diverse backgrounds.\nCurriculum: SCTC's MCA program is designed to provide students with a strong foundation in computer science and applications. The curriculum is regularly updated to keep up with industry trends.\nFaculty: SCTC has a team of experienced faculty members who have a good understanding of the industry and can provide guidance to students.\n\nDisadvantages of SCTC (MCA):\n\nLimited Scope: SCTC offers only MCA programs, and students interested in other programs may need to look for alternatives.\nInfrastructure: While SCTC has adequate infrastructure, it may not be as modern or well-equipped as that of private colleges.\nPlacements: While SCTC does have a placement cell, the number of companies visiting the campus for recruitment may be limited compared to private colleges.",
        "name": "Adnan Sohail",
        "views": "41 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-advantages-and-disadvantages-of-VIT-and-SCTC-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Which is best, an upgrade cyber security course or an MCA in cyber security?",
        "answer": "The answer to this question depends on your career goals and current level of education and experience in cybersecurity.\n\nIf you are already working in the field of cybersecurity and are looking to expand your knowledge and skills, an upgrade cybersecurity course might be the best option for you. These courses are typically shorter in duration, more focused on specific topics or skills, and can be completed while continuing to work full-time.\n\nOn the other hand, if you are looking to enter the field of cybersecurity or advance to a higher-level position, pursuing an MCA (Master of Computer Applications) in cybersecurity could be a better choice. An MCA program typically provides a broader and more comprehensive education, covering topics such as programming, computer networks, information security, and more.\n\nAn MCA in cybersecurity can also provide you with more opportunities for networking, internships, and research, which can be valuable for building your career in cybersecurity.\n\nUltimately, the choice between an upgrade cybersecurity course and an MCA in cybersecurity will depend on your individual circumstances and career goals. It may be helpful to speak with a career counselor or mentor in the field of cybersecurity to help you make an informed decision.",
        "name": "Sadam Parasara",
        "views": "12 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-best-an-upgrade-cyber-security-course-or-an-MCA-in-cyber-security",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/gradadmissions",
        "author": "u/ObsidianA5",
        "question": "I've submitted my application to a few master's programs in Computational Science and Engineering where I mentioned a few profs I'm interested in working with. I haven't contacted them though, since it was close to the holiday season. Should I reach out now?",
        "upvotes": "4",
        "comment": "4",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/gradadmissions/comments/zzpn5g/ive_submitted_my_application_to_a_few_masters/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "A,b, c are real numbers such that a^2+bc ≤ 2, b^2+CA ≤ 2, c^2+ab ≤ 2 What is the minimal value of a+b+c?",
        "answer": "Suppose that a2+b2+c2=1a2+b2+c2=1 for real positive numbers aa, bb, cc. Find the minimum possible value of abc+bca+cababc+bca+cab.So far I've got a minimum of 3–√3. Can anyone confirm this? However, I've been having trouble actually proofing that this is the lower bound. Typically, I've solved problems where I need to prove an inequality as true, but this problem is a bit different asking for the minimum of an inequality instead, and I'm not sure how to show that 3–√3 is the lower bound of it. Any ideas?",
        "name": "Junaid Khan",
        "views": "62 views",
        "link": "https://mathquestions.quora.com/A-b-c-are-real-numbers-such-that-a-2-bc-2-b-2-CA-2-c-2-ab-2-What-is-the-minimal-value-of-a-b-c",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "How beneficial is it to do an MCA after BTech?",
        "answer": "Hello There ,\n\nMCA after BE is not the better option to choose. You only eligible for study if you have mathematics has one of your subject in graduation and you are done BE so you are eligible to the course. As MCA is a masters degree in computer applications and you are very much interested in computers you join a good computer software programming course which can increase your opportunities in the field of computers. MCA will be 3 years course you will waste your valuable time if you do that course.\n\nMBA is a globally recognized degree and is highly accredited. The global recognition for MBA is higher than recognition for PhD in India. The noteworthy benefit of MBA after engineering is that graduates can look for job opportunities outside India as well, as it is a globally recognized degree.\n\nIf you need any kind of assistance regarding admission feel free to contact through whatsapp . (Link is in bio)\n\nHappy Learning…..",
        "name": "Suraj Late",
        "views": "22 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-beneficial-is-it-to-do-an-MCA-after-BTech",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Which one is better B.Sc or BCA after 12th PCM?",
        "answer": "Both http://B.Sc\n (Bachelor of Science) and BCA (Bachelor of Computer Applications) are good options after completing class 12th with PCM (Physics, Chemistry, and Mathematics) as your core subjects. However, which one is best for you would depend on your interests, skills, and career goals.\n\nhttp://B.Sc\n is a three-year undergraduate degree program that covers various science subjects such as Physics, Chemistry, Mathematics, Biology, and Computer Science. Students who are interested in pursuing careers in fields such as research, teaching, or technical writing often opt for a http://B.Sc\n degree.\n\nOn the other hand, BCA is a three-year undergraduate program that focuses primarily on computer applications and programming. This program provides students with a solid foundation in computer applications and programming languages, preparing them for careers in software development, programming, or IT management.\n\nSo, if you are interested in pursuing a career in science and research, http://B.Sc\n could be the better option for you. But if you have a keen interest in computer programming and want to work in the field of software development, then BCA could be the better choice.\n\nUltimately, you should choose the program that aligns with your interests and career goals. You can research the course curriculum, the career opportunities after completing the program, and the reputation of the college or university before making a decision.",
        "name": "Knowledge Universe",
        "views": "15 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-one-is-better-B-Sc-or-BCA-after-12th-PCM",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What happens if your best friend says I love you?",
        "answer": "I married him when he said that.\n\nWe were close from the day we met during our MCA. He was quick to notice my weaknesses and started helping me on those areas. It built our initial friendship and soon we were the best buddies.\n\nWhen our relationship transitioned from friendship to love is a grey area. He has his version of story in which I proposed him. I have my version in which he proposed me. What it means is that neither of us know how & when we actually started loving each other as significant other.\n\nJust about a year into our respective jobs, we opened our first joint savings account and we started saving for our future. It was limited to a good wedding and an excellent honeymoon. We just moved on and on from there.\n\nAll this was possible because we were friends, then became the best friends, and then became a couple, and finally spouse & parents. Quite a journey.\n\nNow, I am the Cancer Fighter and he is the Cancer Caregiver...\n\nAccess this answer and support the author as a Quora+ subscriber\nAccess all answers reserved by \nMeena Thakur\n for Quora+ subscribers\nAccess exclusive answers from thousands more participating creators in Quora+\nBrowse ad‑free and support creators\nStart free trial\nLearn more",
        "name": "Meena Thakur",
        "views": "307.9K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-should-I-prepare-for-JNU-MCA-entrance-exam",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Can I apply for a job at Google after completing a BCA, and MCA?",
        "answer": "Yes, it is possible to apply for a job at Google after completing a BCA (Bachelor of Computer Applications) and MCA (Master of Computer Applications). Google hires candidates from diverse educational backgrounds and places emphasis on skills and expertise rather than solely on academic qualifications.\n\nTo increase your chances of being considered for a job at Google, it is important to gain relevant skills and experience in areas such as software development, programming, data analytics, or cloud computing.\n\nAdditionally, you can participate in Google's programs and initiatives, such as Google Summer of Code, to gain experience and exposure to the company's culture and work processes. When applying for a job at Google, it is important to demonstrate your skills, experience, and passion for technology through your resume, cover letter, and interviews.",
        "name": "Ekta Rani",
        "views": "30 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-apply-for-a-job-at-Google-after-completing-a-BCA-and-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Is PGDCA really helpful to do before doing an MCA? I have done a B.Com and want to pursue a career in the IT sector.",
        "answer": "A course of PGDCA is better than an MCA to get a job in the IT industry. Firstly, the former is only a year long, whereas MCA takes 3 years. Secondly, an MCA is equivalent to a BTech course, whereas a PGDCA teaches enough to work in the IT industry.\n\nSo there's no need to pursue an MCA after doing a course in PGDCA.",
        "name": "Abhishek Dwivedi",
        "views": "874 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/If-Uganda-has-the-most-gold-in-the-nation-miner-why-is-the-country-not-one-of-the-top-richest-countries",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the job opportunities after completing an MCA degree?",
        "answer": "The Master of Computer Applications (MCA) degree is a postgraduate program that provides students with advanced knowledge and skills in various areas of computer applications. Graduates of an MCA program have a wide range of job opportunities available to them.\n\nHere are some of the job opportunities that graduates of an MCA program may pursue:\n\nSoftware Engineer/Developer: MCA graduates can work as software engineers or developers for IT companies. They can work on developing software applications, testing software, and maintaining software systems.\nWeb Developer: MCA graduates can also work as web developers, creating and maintaining websites and web applications for companies.\nDatabase Administrator: MCA graduates can work as database administrators, managing and maintaining the databases of organizations.\nSystem Analyst: MCA graduates can work as system analysts, analyzing the computer systems of organizations and recommending improvements.\nIT Consultant: MCA graduates can also work as IT consultants, providing advice and guidance on IT-related issues to organizations.\nTechnical Writer: MCA graduates can work as technical writers, creating user manuals, technical documentation, and other materials related to IT products and services.\nProject Manager: MCA graduates can also work as project managers, overseeing the development and implementation of IT projects.\nNetwork Administrator: MCA graduates can work as network administrators, managing and maintaining computer networks for organizations.\nCybersecurity Analyst: MCA graduates can work as cybersecurity analysts, protecting the computer systems of organizations from cyber attacks and security threats.\nMobile Application Developer: MCA graduates can work as mobile application developers, designing and developing mobile apps for various platforms like Android and iOS.\nData Scientist: MCA graduates with a strong background in mathematics and statistics can work as data scientists, analyzing and interpreting complex data sets to identify insights and trends.\nArtificial Intelligence/Machine Learning Engineer: MCA graduates can work as AI/ML engineers, developing and implementing AI/ML solutions for organizations.\nSoftware Quality Assurance (QA) Engineer: MCA graduates can work as software QA engineers, ensuring that software products meet quality standards and perform as expected.\nCloud Architect: MCA graduates can work as cloud architects, designing and implementing cloud-based solutions for organizations.\nTechnical Support Engineer: MCA graduates can work as technical support engineers, providing support to customers and resolving technical issues related to software products and services.",
        "name": "Aniket Sharma",
        "views": "14 views",
        "link": "https://collegeforum.quora.com/What-are-the-job-opportunities-after-completing-an-MCA-degree-1",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/AskAcademia",
        "author": "u/crawsecurityhub",
        "question": "Viability for a career in History related fields for a graduate of Bachelor of Technology Computer science and engineering",
        "upvotes": "2",
        "comment": "14",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/AskAcademia/comments/122gzoa/viability_for_a_career_in_history_related_fields/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/cscareerquestionsEU",
        "author": "u/HumanNutrStudent",
        "question": "Masters in CS in Germany for non cs students",
        "upvotes": "5",
        "comment": "12",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/cscareerquestionsEU/comments/r2bo1g/masters_in_cs_in_germany_for_non_cs_students/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is the difference between the MCA and the master's degree program in information security (MSC)?",
        "answer": "MCA stands for Master of Computer Applications, which is a postgraduate degree program that focuses on computer applications and software development. On the other hand, MSC stands for Master of Science and is a postgraduate degree program that covers a range of scientific and technical subjects.\n\nIn terms of information security, a Master's degree program in Information Security (MSC) specifically focuses on cybersecurity and related fields such as cryptography, network security, and risk management. The program is designed to provide students with the skills and knowledge necessary to protect information systems from threats and attacks.\n\nOn the other hand, MCA programs focus more broadly on computer applications and software development, which can include aspects of information security but is not the primary focus. MCA programs may cover topics such as programming, database management, and software engineering.\n\nOverall, while both MCA and MSC programs may include some overlap in coursework, the main difference is that an MSC in information security is specifically designed to provide in-depth knowledge and skills in cybersecurity, while an MCA covers a broader range of topics related to computer applications and software development.",
        "name": "GlobalStar Edu",
        "views": "7 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-the-MCA-and-the-masters-degree-program-in-information-security-MSC",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are the skills required for MCA?",
        "answer": "Master of Computer Applications (MCA) is a professional degree program that provides students with advanced knowledge and skills in computer applications, programming, and software development. The program is designed to equip students with the necessary skills to pursue careers in various domains such as software engineering, web development, mobile application development, data analytics, and cybersecurity. Here are some of the key skills that MCA graduates should possess:\n\nProgramming skills: MCA graduates should have a strong foundation in programming languages such as Java, C++, Python, and JavaScript. They should be proficient in developing software applications using these languages and be able to apply programming concepts to solve complex problems.\nAnalytical skills: MCA graduates should possess strong analytical skills to understand and solve complex problems. They should be able to analyze large amounts of data, identify patterns and trends, and make informed decisions based on the analysis.\nProblem-solving skills: MCA graduates should be able to approach problems systematically and logically. They should be able to break down complex problems into smaller components, identify the root cause, and develop effective solutions.\nCommunication skills: MCA graduates should possess strong communication skills to effectively communicate their ideas and solutions to others. They should be able to communicate technical information to non-technical stakeholders clearly and concisely.\nTeamwork skills: MCA graduates should be able to work collaboratively in a team environment. They should be able to share their knowledge and expertise with others, contribute to team goals, and work towards achieving common objectives.\nAdaptability skills: MCA graduates should be able to adapt to new technologies and programming paradigms. They should be able to learn new programming languages, tools, and techniques quickly and efficiently.\nAttention to detail: MCA graduates should possess strong attention to detail to ensure that software applications are developed to high standards of quality. They should be able to identify and fix errors in the code and ensure that the software meets the specified requirements.\nTime management skills: MCA graduates should be able to manage their time effectively to meet project deadlines. They should be able to prioritize tasks, plan their work, and ensure that they deliver work on time.\nCreativity skills: MCA graduates should be able to think creatively to develop innovative solutions to complex problems. They should be able to come up with new ideas and approaches that can help in improving the efficiency and effectiveness of software applications.\nLeadership skills: MCA graduates should possess leadership skills to manage and lead teams. They should be able to inspire and motivate team members, provide guidance and support, and ensure that projects are completed successfully.\n\nIn addition to these skills, MCA graduates should also possess a strong foundation in mathematics, statistics, and computer science concepts such as algorithms, data structures, databases, computer networks, and operating systems. They should be able to apply these concepts to solve real-world problems and develop high-quality software applications.\n\nTo acquire these skills, MCA graduates should take advantage of the various opportunities provided by their university such as project work, internships, research opportunities, and participation in coding competitions. They should also keep themselves updated with the latest trends and technologies in the industry by attending workshops, seminars, and online courses.\n\nIn conclusion, MCA graduates should possess a combination of technical and soft skills to succeed in their careers. They should be proficient in programming languages, possess strong analytical and problem-solving skills, possess good communication and teamwork skills, be adaptable to new technologies, possess attention to detail and time management skills, be creative and possess leadership skills. By acquiring these skills, MCA graduates can pursue successful careers in various domains of the IT industry.",
        "name": "Aniket Sharma",
        "views": "7 views",
        "link": "https://collegeforum.quora.com/What-are-the-skills-required-for-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/TUDelft",
        "author": "u/Altruistic-Meaning16",
        "question": "HOW MANY IB POINTS FOR BACHELOR IN COMPUTER SCIENCE",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "8",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/TUDelft/comments/128p9h1/how_many_ib_points_for_bachelor_in_computer/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/digiomg",
        "question": "BCA Top Colleges in India, Best College for Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA)",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/digiomg/comments/u4rng1/bca_top_colleges_in_india_best_college_for/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Is LPU good for a BCA?",
        "answer": "For BCA, LPU is really good option if you want a good placement, best infra-structure, Co-operative faculty, Library, residential facilities, environment etc. So, I am sharing you all about my view regarding LPU. Bachelor in Computer Application (BCA) is an undergraduate degree course in computer applications. The duration of the course is 3 years and it is divided into 6 semesters.\n\nLPU offers the programs in discipline of computer applications:\n\n· BCA (bachelors of computer application).\n\n· BCA (Hons)\n\n· Dual program BCA-MCA\n\n· Dual program BCA (Hons)- MCA(Hons)\n\nSome of the job profiles that one can bag after completing a BCA programme like, System Engineer, Software Tester, Junior Programmer, Web Developer, System Administrator, Software Developer. Bulk recruiters come at LPU to recruit new candidates. These are the companies come in LPU such as, AMAZON INDIA, COGNIZANT TECHNOLOGY SOLUTIONS, CAPGEMINI, SYNOPSYS, NATIONAL INSTRUMENTS INDIA LTD., LG SOFT INDIA PRIVATE LIMITED, FICO, MORGAN STANLE , HITACHI INDIA PVT. LTD., KPIT TECHNOLOGIE etc. The maximum package of BCA is 19.25 LPA. Every year 90% students get prestigious salary package.\n\nI thinkl this information help!",
        "name": "Neharika Mann",
        "views": "620 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-LPU-good-for-a-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Can one do MCA after BA?",
        "answer": "After earning a bachelor’s degree, one can pursue an MCA. A Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) degree is required to pursue a Master of Computer Applications (MCA) degree (MCA).\n\nCertainly, it is possible to pursue an MCA after completing a BSc in Computer Science. Indeed, MCA is an excellent and standard program. MCA coursework will expand your understanding of the fundamental ideas of Computer Science.\n\nChoosing this field will result in a better job. A BSc in Computer Science might not garner sufficient employment opportunities, but an MCA degree will, thanks to more exposure and higher pay.\n\nAt this time, I would like to propose that you select a reputable institution that can provide you with a decent education and has well-trained and helpful faculty, the most current course structure, excellent industry exposure, and excellent placements.\n\nThe MCA program is a three-year graduate program that will introduce you to several computer science-related topics. Numerous entrance examinations, such as BIT MCA, VIT MEE, MAH MCA CET, UPSEE, etc., determine admission based on merit.",
        "name": "Kundan Kumar",
        "views": "515 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-happened-between-Riyan-Parag-and-Harshal-Patel-after-making-the-last-over-of-18-roughly-runs-during-RCB-vs-RR",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Why didn’t Harry Truman face any trial for dropping a nuclear bomb that caused genocide of the Japanese?",
        "answer": "If the US had continued to fight island to island and eventually invading Japan the deaths would have been in the tens of millions so the bombs actually saved tens of millions of lives",
        "name": "Neil McA.",
        "views": "820 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-get-direct-admission-for-an-MCA-at-LPU",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the benefits of an MCA over a BTech+MCA in India?",
        "answer": "Nothing much , to get a job with good package u need to learn new skills or upskill urself with current demands in IT industry",
        "name": "Sabastian",
        "views": "14 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-benefits-of-an-MCA-over-a-BTech-MCA-in-India",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/EducationinIndia",
        "author": "u/Sariel007",
        "question": "Best Colleges in Uttarakhand for Pursuing BCA Course",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/EducationinIndia/comments/qfaxro/best_colleges_in_uttarakhand_for_pursuing_bca/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/TimscdrDm",
        "author": "u/TimscdrDm",
        "question": "Best master of computer application colleges in mumbai | Top MCA College",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/TimscdrDm/comments/xpkldf/best_master_of_computer_application_colleges_in/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Which are the top 10 best colleges in India to do a BCA?",
        "answer": "The ranking of colleges can vary based on various factors, and there are several excellent colleges in India that offer a Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) program. Here are the top 10 colleges in India to do a BCA, based on their reputation, academic excellence, faculty, and facilities:\n\nMedhavi Skills University (MSU), Sikkim\nLoyola College, Chennai\nSt. Xavier's College, Kolkata\nPresidency College, Bangalore\nMadras Christian College, Chennai\nFergusson College, Pune\nMount Carmel College, Bangalore\nKristu Jayanti College, Bangalore\nHansraj College, New Delhi\nWomen's Christian College, Chennai\n\nIt's important to research the colleges and their BCA programs to determine which one aligns with your academic and career goals.",
        "name": "Priyanka Bhardwaj",
        "views": "374 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-top-10-best-colleges-in-India-to-do-a-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "How good is Lovely Professional University for an MCA?",
        "answer": "hey,\n\nMCA is a professional Master's Degree Program designed to give students with solid theoretical and practical exposure in the field of computer applications. The MCA course is specifically tailored to fulfil the organization's IT requirements. It is intended to provide in-depth understanding of current technology. Students also receive substantial laboratory instruction on course content as well as current industry and R&D requirements. The MCA Program includes courses in Computation Theory, Programming Logic, Design & Optimization, Network, Database, Operating Systems, Mathematics, and Finance. NASSCOM has classified LPU's School of Computer Application as one of the top four Computer Applications Institutions in North India. LPU has done wonders in this field\n\nResearch\n\n250+ SCOPUS/WOS Publications\n\n150+ Conference Papers\n\n100+ Patents Published\n\n20+ Book Chapters\n\nLPU provides a program that prepares students to take up positions as systems analysts, system designers, programmers, and managers in any field related to IT.",
        "name": "Jyoti",
        "views": "126 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-good-is-KR-Mangalam-University-for-an-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is the career scope after a BCA+MCA?",
        "answer": "After completing a BCA (Bachelor of Computer Applications) and MCA (Master of Computer Applications), there are many career options available in the field of Information Technology (IT). Here are some popular career paths for BCA+MCA graduates:\n\nSoftware Developer\nSoftware Tester\nNetwork Engineer\nDatabase Administrator\nNetwork Administrator\nInformation Security Analyst\nProject Manager\nThey can take government exams such as those for banks, LICs, etc.",
        "name": "Bubai Das",
        "views": "270 views",
        "link": "https://itjobscareers.quora.com/What-is-the-career-scope-after-a-BCA-MCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is the career scope after a BCA+MCA?",
        "answer": "After completing a BCA (Bachelor of Computer Applications) and MCA (Master of Computer Applications), there are many career options available in the field of Information Technology (IT). Here are some popular career paths for BCA+MCA graduates:\n\nSoftware Developer\nSoftware Tester\nNetwork Engineer\nDatabase Administrator\nNetwork Administrator\nInformation Security Analyst\nProject Manager\nThey can take government exams such as those for banks, LICs, etc.",
        "name": "Bubai Das",
        "views": "270 views",
        "link": "https://itjobscareers.quora.com/What-is-the-career-scope-after-a-BCA-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/getadmision",
        "author": "u/Kinnnss",
        "question": "Is BCA a Good Career Option?",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/getadmision/comments/zmhd2j/is_bca_a_good_career_option/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which universities in the USA does SBI provide foreign education loans? I am not able to find a list online.",
        "answer": "Oh\n\nThey have a Long List\n\nTrust me , Almost All US Universities offering M.S will be included as will MBA\n\nAny State Funded University will be on that List & many Private ones too\n\nAlso if the University is not on their list - No Worries!!!\n\nThey will ask for a Prospectus and they can give you the loan and add the University to their list\n\nYou want the list\n\nVisit Select Branches of SBI and during Free time you can ask the Person responsible for the Education Loan if she can get you the list from the relevant department\n\nTechnically SBI has no rules on University based eligibility\n\nAs long as the Course is a JOPGC (Job Oriented Professional Post Graduation Course) which includes - M.D, MBA, MCA, MS- No Issues with the College (At least in theory)",
        "name": "Kanthaswamy Balasubramaniam",
        "views": "8.6K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Why-is-South-Africa-clearly-the-most-developed-African-country-with-a-predominant-black-population",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/mitscollegejadan",
        "author": "u/mitscollegejadan",
        "question": "Best College for Computer Science & Application in Pali, Rajasthan | MITS Jadan",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/mitscollegejadan/comments/xj278b/best_college_for_computer_science_application_in/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "How can I register for LLP?",
        "answer": "To register for an LLP (Limited Liability Partnership) in India, you will need to follow these steps:\n\nObtain a Digital Signature Certificate (DSC) and a Designated Partner Identification Number (DPIN): All designated partners of the LLP must have a DSC and DPIN, which can be obtained by submitting an online application on the Ministry of Corporate Affairs (MCA) website.\nReserve a name for your LLP: You can check the availability of your desired LLP name on the MCA website and reserve it by filing the LLP name reservation form online.\nPrepare the LLP agreement: The LLP agreement outlines the rights, duties, and obligations of the partners and the LLP. It can be prepared by a chartered accountant, company secretary, or lawyer.\nFile the incorporation form: After obtaining the DSC and DPIN, and preparing the LLP agreement, you can file the incorporation form online on the MCA website.\nPayment of fees: You will need to pay the prescribed fees at the time of filing the incorporation form.\nObtain the Certificate of Incorporation: After the incorporation form is approved, you will receive a Certificate of Incorporation from the Registrar of Companies, which confirms the creation of your LLP.\n\nIt is recommended that you engage the services of a professional, such as a chartered accountant or company secretary, to ensure that the registration process is completed correctly and in a timely manner.",
        "name": "Mr. Informat",
        "views": "52 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-register-for-LLP",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which are the good colleges for a BCA?",
        "answer": "For students pursuing a Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) degree, placements might be crucial since they can assist them land a job once they graduate. Students can get internships and jobs thanks to the placement offices found in many universities and schools.\n\nConsidering the significant need for qualified IT experts in the employment market, the placement rate for BCA students is generally favorable. BCA graduates can be hired for a range of entry-level IT professions, such as those in network administration, data analysis, and software development.\n\nThe placement rate, however, might differ based on a variety of variables, such as the standing of the institution or college, the standard of the education offered, the academic standing of the students, and the state of the job market.\n\nConsidering all of the above WCTM has one of the best placement records. No matter the criterion—placement rates, professors, facilities, infrastructure, internships, industrial training, extracurricular activities, or academics—WCTM has always been the #1 choice.\n\nWCTM was ranked number 1 in Gurugram in terms of placements, BBA and Engineering by Times of India Survey 2022.\n\nMany companies have dispatched recruiters, including HCL Technology, Accenture, Nokia Solutions, Byjus, and Maintech Technologies, among others.\n\nWCTM has a spotless record of placements. The college provides enough exposure, education, and opportunities for skill demonstration and the possibility to collaborate with experienced experts.\n\nStudents at WCTM have been exposed to a rigorous academic process that has equipped them with the knowledge and specialised skills necessary to excel in a range of demanding situations with ease and confidence. One of the main drivers of my development has been the specialist student training branch at WCTM.\n\nThis division focuses on fostering soft skills including good posture and communication. To build a presentable and professional personality, every student would go through rigorous training.\n\nHere is the web address for the college: Best engineering college in Gurgaon | Best engineering college in Delhi NCR | WCTM",
        "name": "Rachna Sharma",
        "views": "406 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-good-colleges-for-a-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the placements of an MCA student from Lovely Professional University (LPU) in Roorkee?",
        "answer": "Dear,LPU is the only single campus which is located in (Punjab) Phagwara,MCA is a professional Master's Degree Programme designed to provide sound theoretical and good practical exposure to students in the field of computer applications. MCA course is exclusively designed to meet the IT requirement of the organization. It is designed to offer in-depth knowledge of recent technologies in use today.\n\nStudents are also provided extensive laboratory training on the course content and the current requirements of industries and the R & D. MCA Programme covers various aspects of Computation Theory, Programming Logic, Design & Optimization, Network, Database, Operating Systems, Mathematics & Finance.\n\nLPU's School of Computer Application is ranked among the top four Computer Applications Institutes of North India by NASSCOM. Students from all across India and 15 plus countries around the globe are expertly mentored by an experienced and proficient team of faculty members.\n\nThe highest package offered was 31 LPA and the average salary was 4 lakhs.Microsoft, Google, Amazon, Optmyzr, IBM, Infosys, Cloudera, Lowes India, CISCO, D.E Shaw India, Oracle, Cognizant, TCS, Tech Mahindra, Wipro, Amdocs, Capgemini, Verizon, Cmware, Virtusa, Accenture, SAP Labs, Acko Technology Services, Tivo Corporation, Informatica, Infineon, Goodera, Rentomojo, Qualcomm, Dell, Deloitte, Drishti Soft Solutions, Tek Systems, Interviewbit (Scaler), LG Soft India, PEGA, Tavisca Solution, Hitachi Consulting, Blujay, Tesssolve, Code Nation, ITC Infotech, MAQ Software, Josh Technologies, Morgan Stanley, Schneider Electric, Directi, Sopra Steria, Tavant, Ericsson, Samsung, Bosch, CSS Corp, Temenos, KPIT Technologies, KPMG, Synopsys, MIQ Digital, Hashedin, Code Brew Labs, Genpact, Edoofa, Datagrokr Analytics, Ksolves, WorkIndia, Ernst & Young, L&T Technology Services, DXC Technologies, Nutanix etc",
        "name": "Vishnu Harry",
        "views": "66 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-placements-of-an-MCA-student-from-Lovely-Professional-University-LPU-in-Roorkee",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Nepal",
        "author": "u/allofaneek",
        "question": "Where is a good college around Samakhusi for Bachelors in Computer Applications? Money is really scarce!",
        "upvotes": "2",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Nepal/comments/10e6b6a/where_is_a_good_college_around_samakhusi_for/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Indians_StudyAbroad",
        "author": "u/softvisioncollege",
        "question": "Require advice on what to pursue for PG as an Indian student going abroad.",
        "upvotes": "3",
        "comment": "7",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Indians_StudyAbroad/comments/11wmrmx/require_advice_on_what_to_pursue_for_pg_as_an/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are some good colleges offering a BCA with data science in India?",
        "answer": "There are several colleges in India that offer a Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) program with a specialization in data science. Some of the top colleges for BCA in data science in India are:\n\nChrist University, Bangalore\nSymbiosis Institute of Computer Studies and Research, Pune\nJain University, Bangalore\nPresidency University, Bangalore\nLovely Professional University, Punjab\nSt. Xavier's College, Mumbai\nAmity University, Noida\nSRM Institute of Science and Technology, Chennai\nManipal University, Manipal\nVellore Institute of Technology (VIT), Vellore\n\nIt is important to research and compare the different colleges and their programs, including their curriculum, faculty, placement opportunities, and overall reputation, before making a decision on which one to pursue.",
        "name": "Sajjad Hussain",
        "views": "24 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-good-colleges-offering-a-BCA-with-data-science-in-India",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/india",
        "author": "u/KRMANGALMUNIVERSITY",
        "question": "I'm a fresher looking for 6 month internship",
        "upvotes": "2",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/india/comments/yd0ubn/im_a_fresher_looking_for_6_month_internship/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "I m doing b.sc can I do MCA?",
        "answer": "Yes, you definitely can. Prepare for entrance exams of MCA whoever you are eligible in. Take tests and crack the exam. That's all and you are in.",
        "name": "Rishav Bajaj",
        "views": "7 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/I-m-doing-b-sc-can-I-do-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Articles",
        "author": "u/GLBITM",
        "question": "Career After Master in Computer Applications",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Articles/comments/8wb3hc/career_after_master_in_computer_applications/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Which is better for MCA, IIIT Hyderabad or BITS Pilani?",
        "answer": "Both IIIT Hyderabad and BITS Pilani are renowned institutions for MCA programs in India, and both have their own unique strengths.\n\nIIIT Hyderabad is known for its strong focus on research and innovation, and its MCA program is designed to provide students with a strong foundation in computer science and information technology, as well as hands-on experience in research and development. The faculty at IIIT Hyderabad is highly qualified and experienced in their respective fields, and the institute has state-of-the-art facilities for research and education.\n\nOn the other hand, BITS Pilani is also a top-ranked institution in India, with a strong reputation for its MCA program. The curriculum at BITS Pilani is designed to provide students with a comprehensive understanding of computer science and applications, and the program emphasizes practical knowledge and skills. The institute has a strong focus on industry collaborations and partnerships, which provides students with excellent opportunities for internships and placements.\n\nUltimately, the choice between IIIT Hyderabad and BITS Pilani for MCA will depend on your personal preferences and career goals. You should consider factors such as the curriculum, faculty, facilities, research opportunities, industry collaborations, and placement records of both institutions before making a decision. It is also important to visit the campuses and talk to current students and faculty members to get a better understanding of the culture and learning environment at each institution.",
        "name": "MN Sathi",
        "views": "22 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-better-for-MCA-IIIT-Hyderabad-or-BITS-Pilani",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are the benefits of a BCA from IMT Nagpur?",
        "answer": "A strong foundation in computer science and technology is given to students in the Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) degree at IMT Nagpur. The following are some possible advantages of earning a BCA from IMT Nagpur:\n\nOpportunities for employment: IMT Nagpur's BCA graduates are well-prepared for professions in a range of areas, including consulting, software development, and IT.\n\nBuilding skills: The BCA programme offers instruction in a variety of areas, including software engineering, database administration, web development, and programming languages. The opportunity to practise using various tools and technologies hands-on will help students build crucial technical skills.\n\nOpportunities for entrepreneurship: The BCA programme at IMT Nagpur gives students the knowledge and abilities to launch their own technology-related businesses.\n\nIndustry exposure: IMT Nagpur collaborates with a number of industry partners, giving students practical insights into the application of their knowledge and abilities in the real world.\n\nPost-graduate options: IMT Nagpur's BCA graduates have the option of continuing their education in computer science or related subjects by earning an MBA or MCA.\n\nAn IMT Nagpur BCA can give students a solid foundation in computer science and technology, equipping them for a variety of jobs in the technology sector.",
        "name": "Fajar Zulfiqar",
        "views": "9 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-benefits-of-a-BCA-from-IMT-Nagpur",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/AxisCollege",
        "author": "u/AxisCollege",
        "question": "Axis Colleges is the one of the best Master in Computer Applications Colleges in Kanpur",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/AxisCollege/comments/vzi9tx/axis_colleges_is_the_one_of_the_best_master_in/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the drawbacks of doing an MCA from VIT University?",
        "answer": "Hello Aspirant,\n\nLike any educational program or institution, there may be some drawbacks to doing an MCA (Master of Computer Applications) from VIT (Vellore Institute of Technology) University. Some possible drawbacks of doing an MCA from VIT University are:\n\nHigh fees: VIT University is a private institution and has a relatively higher fee structure compared to some other universities in India. The high fees may be a drawback for some students who are looking for more affordable options.\nLocation: VIT University is located in Vellore, which may not be an ideal location for some students who are looking for more urban and cosmopolitan environments.\nAdmission process: The admission process for VIT University is quite competitive, with a significant emphasis on performance in the VITMEE (VIT Master's Entrance Examination) and the academic qualifications of the candidates. Some students may find it challenging to secure admission to the MCA program at VIT University.\nWorkload: The MCA program at VIT University is quite rigorous, with a lot of coursework and assignments. Some students may find it challenging to cope with the workload and balance other responsibilities.\nLimited research opportunities: VIT University is primarily focused on undergraduate and postgraduate teaching and has limited research opportunities for MCA students compared to some other universities in India.\n\nIt is important to note that these drawbacks may not apply to all students, and some students may find that the benefits of studying at VIT University outweigh the drawbacks. It is recommended that students thoroughly research and evaluate their options before making a decision.\n\nIf it is advisable and informative\n\nplz follow , upvote and share.\n\nThanks",
        "name": "Career Initiative",
        "views": "36 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-drawbacks-of-doing-an-MCA-from-VIT-University",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/tiipsindia",
        "author": "u/orang-i",
        "question": "Find The Top BCA College in Delhi for Quality Education",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/tiipsindia/comments/1032jqg/find_the_top_bca_college_in_delhi_for_quality/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Can I study BCA at the age of 27?",
        "answer": "Yes, you can pursue a Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) degree at the age of 26 years. There is no upper age limit for admission to BCA courses in most universities and colleges. BCA is a popular undergraduate course for students who want to build a career in the field of computer applications and software development. The duration of the BCA course is typically three years, and it covers topics such as programming languages, database management, computer networks, and software engineering. If you are interested in pursuing a career in the field of computer applications, BCA can be a great option for you.",
        "name": "Professor of HOW",
        "views": "18 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-study-BCA-at-the-age-of-27",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are the benefits of doing an MCA at Chitkara University? What kind of job placements do they offer for an MCA student there?",
        "answer": "First of all, the biggest benefit of doing MCA from Chitkara is the university itself! The institution is highly regarded where you will get all the resources which you would be able to use during your course duration. Masters in Computer Applications in Chitkara, It provides the basic yet important fundamental principles of the discipline to the students and teaches them the most recent business best practices, and prepares them to analyse and solve problems in a wide range of applications. You will be happy to know that more than 300 companies come to visit the campus during its placement season as to provide jobs and internships to the aspiring candidates. Chitkara offers the finest job placements, various renowned companies recruit students from the University.",
        "name": "GAURI DOGRA",
        "views": "14 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-benefits-of-doing-an-MCA-at-Chitkara-University-What-kind-of-job-placements-do-they-offer-for-an-MCA-student-there",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Nepal",
        "author": "u/gngroupinstitutes",
        "question": "How to take admission in TU? How expensive are the fees? Is there any restrictions? Also, Is TU affiliated and TU same?",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "4",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Nepal/comments/vvu40g/how_to_take_admission_in_tu_how_expensive_are_the/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What is the salary for MCA holders?",
        "answer": "Indian MCA Salary: Freshers & Experienced\n\nIn India, an MCA graduate makes about Rs 7.96 lakh annually. (Referring to Pay scale) Candidates who have recently entered the workforce after earning their MCA earn about Rs 3 Lakh annually. Depending on each company's position in the market and its clientele, this differs slightly. The wage structure is influenced even by the company's location.\n\n(Hope This Answer Will Help You)",
        "name": "College Sakha",
        "views": "1.1K views",
        "link": "https://indiancollegeadmissions.quora.com/How-to-do-an-MCA-in-VFX-and-animations",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/bcaklekun",
        "author": "u/bcaklekun",
        "question": "KLE GOOD BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATION COLLEGE IN BANGALORE",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/bcaklekun/comments/124mgso/kle_good_bachelor_of_computer_application_college/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "I have completed a BCA. Am I eligible for NIC requirements?",
        "answer": "No, As per the notification BCA is not among eligible branches however you need to upgrade to one more level to MCA to become eligible.\n\nHere is the screenshot of required notification page.",
        "name": "Pawan Kumar",
        "views": "66 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/I-have-completed-a-BCA-Am-I-eligible-for-NIC-requirements",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "twitter",
        "name": "Souvik Chanda",
        "handle": "@svk247",
        "timestamp": "Oct 21, 2009",
        "text": "diploma/degree/bachelor in Computer Application/Electronic and Communication/Instrumentation and Control Eng......",
        "link": "https://twitter.com/svk247/status/5034652481",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Is it a good option to do an MBA after a BCA?",
        "answer": "Yes, pursuing an MBA after completing a Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) can be a good option for several reasons.\n\nFirstly, an MBA can provide you with the business knowledge and skills necessary to succeed in management roles in the IT industry. It can help you develop leadership skills, improve your decision-making abilities, and give you a broader understanding of business concepts such as marketing, finance, and operations.\n\nSecondly, an MBA can enhance your career prospects and earning potential. It can help you qualify for higher-level positions such as project manager, program manager, or senior IT consultant, and potentially lead to higher salaries.\n\nThirdly, an MBA can help you build a professional network of like-minded individuals in the industry. You can gain access to alumni networks, industry associations, and other networking opportunities that can help you advance your career.\n\nHowever, it's important to note that pursuing an MBA requires significant time, effort, and financial resources. It's important to carefully evaluate your career goals and financial situation before making the decision to pursue an MBA. Additionally, consider exploring other options such as certifications, specialized training programs, or gaining relevant work experience before pursuing an MBA.",
        "name": "College49",
        "views": "9 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-a-good-option-to-do-an-MBA-after-a-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Which course is better for a student, an MTech or an MCA (from a good private college) after completing an MSc degree in Physics?",
        "answer": "The choice between an MTech and an MCA course depends on your interests, career goals, and skillset. Here is some information that can help you make an informed decision:\n\nMTech:\n\nAn MTech degree is a technical course that focuses on the application of engineering and technology concepts. It can be an excellent choice if you are interested in pursuing a career in research and development or want to work in the engineering industry. MTech programs typically provide specialized knowledge and skills in a particular domain, such as electrical engineering, mechanical engineering, computer science, etc.\n\nMCA:\n\nAn MCA (Master of Computer Applications) is a postgraduate degree course that provides in-depth knowledge of computer applications and programming. If you are interested in computer programming, software development, or information technology, then an MCA can be a good choice for you. An MCA degree can help you get jobs in IT companies, software development firms, and other related industries.\n\nFrom your background of an MSc degree in Physics, both MTech and MCA can be suitable options for you, depending on your interests and career goals. If you want to explore the field of engineering, then an MTech can be a good choice. However, if you are interested in computer programming and want to pursue a career in software development or IT, then an MCA can be a better option.\n\nIt's important to note that the reputation and quality of the college/university also play a significant role in the value of your degree. A good private college can provide you with the necessary skills and exposure to the industry, making you more employable. Therefore, it's essential to research and choose a college that has a good reputation and offers quality education in the field you are interested in.\n\nUltimately, the choice between an MTech and an MCA course depends on your interests, skills, and career aspirations. Consider your options, research thoroughly, and make an informed decision that aligns with your goals.",
        "name": "R Rana",
        "views": "16 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-course-is-better-for-a-student-an-MTech-or-an-MCA-from-a-good-private-college-after-completing-an-MSc-degree-in-Physics",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Indian_Academia",
        "author": "u/Sajwancrypto",
        "question": "B. tech Mechanical Graduate can not take admission in Master of computer Application?",
        "upvotes": "5",
        "comment": "8",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Indian_Academia/comments/xly3he/b_tech_mechanical_graduate_can_not_take_admission/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/Delicious-Dust-4811",
        "author": "u/King_Pagan_Min",
        "question": "Best BCA Colleges in Udaipur",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past hours",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/Delicious-Dust-4811/comments/tbkk1z/best_bca_colleges_in_udaipur/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "How is Sandip University for doing an MCA? Is it recognized abroad?",
        "answer": "Sandip University is one of the best schools for doing the MCA program. This is a two-year full-time program at Sandip University. The MCA at Sandip University is tailored in a manner that it meets the growing needs of the industry. The curriculum of the MCA program is designed to clear the concepts of basic computing to the students as well as impart them with advanced knowledge in the field of computers.\n\nStudying a MCA degree at Sandip University is not boring like studying any other program. At this University, the lectures are taught in an interactive way. The faculties adopt lot of participative and practical methods of teaching, which makes such a technical subject like MCA very interesting. The students are taught through fun-learning methods such as live case studies, group discussions, role-plays, brain storming sessions, field trips\n\nIt is worth joining this program at Sandip University because the faculties also teach the subject very well. The faculties who teach the MCA course at Sandip University are alumni of reputed organisations such as IIT’s and NIT’s. They are well versed in their subject with a sound technical knowledge. This helps the students to gain the latest information and knowledge about MCA. The faculties are also a mentor and life-coach to the student and their responsibilities at Sandip University are not only limited to ‘teaching’ the subject. This broader role of the faculties helps the students in shaping their careers and helps them in growing in their careers.\n\nMCA at Sandip University is a globalised program and is very much recognised abroad. The student has to do compulsory internship in the final semester of the program. Sandip University also offers international internships to students in countries such as Germany, Dubai and Russia. After doing this MCA program, students can study further or work in a foreign country.",
        "name": "Pankaj Gaikwad",
        "views": "7 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-is-Sandip-University-for-doing-an-MCA-Is-it-recognized-abroad",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/OMSCS",
        "author": "u/minavildansark",
        "question": "Can MCA student apply for OMSCS",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "4",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/OMSCS/comments/x026is/can_mca_student_apply_for_omscs/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Indians_StudyAbroad",
        "author": "u/lequangtri20",
        "question": "How to go to Germany for Masters. I want to go to Germany to pursue my masters from there. I am currently doing by bachelors from a private university in India and want to go this year to Germany. As i will get my degree in August 2023, and applications will begin in April, so what are all procedure",
        "upvotes": "11",
        "comment": "9",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Indians_StudyAbroad/comments/11r8agm/how_to_go_to_germany_for_masters_i_want_to_go_to/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/IWantOut",
        "author": "u/YASHY2K",
        "question": "[IWantOut] 28M Indian study electronics -> Anywhere Western",
        "upvotes": "79",
        "comment": "86",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/IWantOut/comments/jvsmsc/iwantout_28m_indian_study_electronics_anywhere/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Which is better B.Sc Computer science or BCA in terms of jobs?",
        "answer": "Both http://B.Sc\n Computer Science and BCA (Bachelor of Computer Applications) are undergraduate programs that focus on computer science and technology. Both degrees provide students with a solid foundation in computer programming, software development, and other related subjects.\n\nIn terms of job opportunities, both degrees can lead to lucrative careers in the tech industry. However, http://B.Sc\n Computer Science is generally considered to be more versatile, as it provides a broader range of career options. Graduates with a http://B.Sc\n in Computer Science can work as software engineers, data analysts, IT consultants, network administrators, web developers, and more.\n\nOn the other hand, BCA is more focused on software development and programming, which makes it a good choice for students who want to specialize in these areas. Graduates with a BCA degree can work as software developers, application programmers, web designers, and database administrators.\n\nOverall, both degrees can lead to rewarding careers in the tech industry. The choice between http://B.Sc\n Computer Science and BCA depends on the student's interests, career goals, and preferred area of specialization.",
        "name": "Ujjwal Matoliya",
        "views": "17 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-better-B-Sc-Computer-science-or-BCA-in-terms-of-jobs",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are some good colleges in Pune for BCA programs with good placement records and infrastructure?",
        "answer": "Hello Students,\n\nAs we know that Pune is the one of the Hub of reputed educational institutions offering courses in various fields and Pune is also home to several reputed colleges offering BCA programs with good placement records and infrastructure. Here are some of the top colleges in Pune for BCA:\n\nSymbiosis Institute of Computer Studies and Research (SICSR): SICSR is one of the top colleges in Pune for BCA with excellent infrastructure and placement opportunities. The college is affiliated with Symbiosis International University and has tie-ups with several reputed companies for placements.\nFergusson College: Fergusson College is a renowned college in Pune offering a three-year BCA program with good placement opportunities. The college has a well-equipped computer lab, library, and other facilities for students.\nMIT-WPU: MIT-WPU is another popular college in Pune offering a BCA program with a focus on practical training and hands-on experience. The college has tie-ups with several IT companies for placements and provides a modern learning environment with state-of-the-art facilities.\nBrihan Maharashtra College of Commerce (BMCC): BMCC is a well-known college in Pune for commerce and computer-related courses, including BCA. The college has a good placement record and provides excellent infrastructure and facilities for students.\nModern College of Arts, Science, and Commerce: Modern College is a reputed college in Pune offering a three-year BCA program with good placement opportunities. The college has a well-equipped computer lab, library, and other facilities for students.\n\nThese are some of the top colleges in Pune for BCA programs with good placement records and infrastructure.\n\nHope this will be Enough for you. Feel Free to contact as we provide Free counselling to the Students and their Parents for any College across India.\n\n6205238449 (Call/WhatsApp).\n\nThank-You…..!!!!",
        "name": "Anjali Mishra",
        "views": "57 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-good-colleges-in-Pune-for-BCA-programs-with-good-placement-records-and-infrastructure",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/Edubuild",
        "author": "u/Edubuild",
        "question": "Online Bachelor of Computer Application | BCA Degree in Vadodara",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/Edubuild/comments/126lxb9/online_bachelor_of_computer_application_bca/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "How many marks in the 12th is essential for admission in LPU?",
        "answer": "The eligibility is program specific at LPU and each program has different criteria for admissions.\n\nThere are various programmes offered in this university where you can take direct admission based on previous qualification (Pass in 12th) such as, BBA, BCA, B.COM BACHELOR OF PERFORMING ARTS IN THEATRE, BACHELOR OF ARTS IN MUSIC VOCAL, B.A. (Journalism and Mass Communication), B.A. (Hons.) and many other.\n\nWhereas, for other programs the score specified for eligibility must be attained by the candidate in order to proceed with the admission in desired course.",
        "name": "Mawal",
        "views": "247 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-many-marks-in-the-12th-is-essential-for-admission-in-LPU",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "I have done a BSc in computer science, and I got selected at Capgemini and I have accepted the offer. I want to do an MCA. Should I do a distance MCA, an online MCA or a regular MCA?",
        "answer": "Hi,\n\n“First of all congratulations for the selection”\n\nMy advice is that you should join there, work for at least a year, during this time you will understand your current profile, Industry trends, and upcoming career goals,\n\nOn behalf of the above choose the most suitable course weather it MCA , MBA or any Other.\n\nBelieve it any course would be more valuable if you do it with work experience .\n\nSome Corporates do sponsor their Employee’s Education,\n\nNote-No regular course can perused with full time job\n\nHope this helps you .\n\nRegards\n\nSangh Saran",
        "name": "Sangh Saran",
        "views": "885 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Who-will-be-the-right-Malay-PM-candidate-for-Malaysia-in-the-next-election-My-vote-is-for-Khairy",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/IWantToLearn",
        "author": "u/Specialist-Pride-585",
        "question": "iwtl i am doing master in computer applications what else can do to improve my chances to get hired fast with a decent salary?",
        "upvotes": "27",
        "comment": "8",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/IWantToLearn/comments/y9ilo5/iwtl_i_am_doing_master_in_computer_applications/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Indian_Academia",
        "author": "u/DifficultAccess4651",
        "question": "I met over 6 University Principals/Deans to study BCA in Chennai all of whom tell me that its not possible for me to enroll in UG program after 10 years gap after completing school. Qualification 12th Grade",
        "upvotes": "88",
        "comment": "17",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Indian_Academia/comments/vb9otm/i_met_over_6_university_principalsdeans_to_study/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "How much salary is offered in placements of MCA?",
        "answer": "The average salary for MCA placements is Rs.\n\n4.5 Lakhs per annum.\n\nThe highest salary offered was Rs.\n\n12 Lakhs per annum and the lowest salary offered was Rs.\n\n2 Lakhs per annum",
        "name": "Rafael S. Phillips",
        "views": "457 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Whats-the-strangest-thing-you-caught-a-flight-attendant-doing",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/gradadmissions",
        "author": "u/imnotryann",
        "question": "Paying for Grad School for a Master in Computer Science Applications in the National Capital Region (Washington D.C. region) at Virginia Tech",
        "upvotes": "4",
        "comment": "1",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/gradadmissions/comments/10xb3ml/paying_for_grad_school_for_a_master_in_computer/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Which is the best college for an MCA in Maharashtra?",
        "answer": "MCA is one of the best courses in the 21st century. Several colleges in Maharashtra are good for MCA.\n\nHere is a list of colleges -\n\nSandip University, Nashik\n\nVeermata Jijabai Technological Institute (VJTI), Mumbai\n\nDepartment of Computer Science University (DCS University), Pune\n\nKJ Somaiya Institute of Management, Mumbai\n\nGovernment College of Engineering, Aurangabad.\n\nI have some friends who are studying at Sandip University and they have given me very positive feedback. They provide 100% placement assistance.",
        "name": "Rahul Pawar",
        "views": "168 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-college-for-an-MCA-in-Maharashtra",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Can I get direct admission for an MCA at LPU?",
        "answer": "It is not very tough to get admitted to LPU; you just need to meet the requirements.This is the Eligibility Criteria (Qualifying Exam)\n\nPass with 60%\n\naggregate marks\n\nin BCA or http://B.Sc\n. (Computer Science) or http://B.Sc\n. (Information Technology) or any Graduation with Computer Science as a subject for three years OR B.A. or http://B.Com\n. or http://B.Sc\n. (any Graduation) with (Mathematics as one of the subject at Graduation or 10+2 level) or equivalent, subject to qualifying LPUNEST.\n\n(5% relaxation to North-East states and Sikkim candidates or Defence Personnel and their Dependents or Wards of Kashmiri Migrants).\n\nFor more you can visit LPU official website .\n\nHope this information helpful!!!",
        "name": "Shilpa Sachdav",
        "views": "264 views",
        "link": "https://itcompaniesemployees.quora.com/Im-30-years-old-and-completely-waste-my-life-in-preparing-for-a-government-job-exam-but-couldnt-get-anything-What-sho",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Who will be the right Malay PM candidate for Malaysia in the next election? My vote is for Khairy.",
        "answer": "The population of Malaysia is predominantly Bumiputera and Muslim. 67.4% of Malaysians are Bumiputeras and 61.3% are Muslims. Some of the Bumiputeras, especially in Sabah and Sarawak, are not Muslims.\n\nIt is therefore very likely that the Prime Minister of Malaysia will always be a Muslim Bumiputera. Whether we like it or not, most Malaysian voters vote based on race and religion.\n\nThe political parties don’t help in integration either. DAP is led mostly by non-Muslim Chinese, even though they claim to be non-racial. Just look at their Central Executive committee. It is almost an all Chinese team. The same with MCA and Gerakan. PAS, UMNO, BERSATU and Amanah are all 100% Malays or Bumiputeras.\n\nThe only West Malaysian party that looks like a “Malaysian” party is PKR, and PKR has two strong leaders for the future - Nurul Izzah and Rafizi. Both of them are close to Khairy Jamaluddin. I hope that one day these three would be working together, perhaps in one party, to lead the country. But for now, all three need more experience. For now, Ismail Sabri is probably the best choice. Under Ismail Sabri, the economy expanded 5% in the first quarter and 8,9% in the second quarter of 2022. Those are good figures.",
        "name": "Ridzwan Abdul Rahman",
        "views": "69.3K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-benefits-of-doing-an-MCA-after-graduation-if-you-want-to-be-a-software-developer",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/Broad-Worldliness7",
        "author": "u/Dependent_Hope9447",
        "question": "How BCA Distance Learning can Lead You a Successful Career in IT Sector?",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/Broad-Worldliness7/comments/y147df/how_bca_distance_learning_can_lead_you_a/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Can MCA graduates pursue MBA?",
        "answer": "MCA graduates can pursue an MBA (Master of Business Administration) program if they are interested in a career in business management. An MBA degree can help MCA graduates develop their managerial and leadership skills and gain a broader perspective on business operations, which can be beneficial in their careers.\n\nMCA graduates have a strong foundation in computer science and programming concepts, which can be useful in the business world as well. Many organizations today rely heavily on technology to manage their operations, and an MCA graduate with an MBA degree can be an asset to such organizations.\n\nHere are some of the benefits of pursuing an MBA after an MCA degree:\n\nManagement skills: An MBA program can help MCA graduates develop their management skills, which are essential for leading teams and managing projects. They can learn about different management styles, team building, decision-making, and communication skills, which can help them become effective leaders.\nBusiness acumen: An MBA program can provide MCA graduates with a broader perspective on business operations, such as finance, marketing, human resources, and operations. This knowledge can be useful in understanding the business goals and objectives and developing strategies to achieve them.\nEntrepreneurship: An MBA program can also provide MCA graduates with the skills and knowledge necessary to start their businesses. They can learn about business planning, marketing, finance, and operations, which can help launch a startup.\nNetworking opportunities: An MBA program can provide MCA graduates with opportunities to network with industry professionals, alumni, and other students. This can help them develop their professional network, which can be useful in finding job opportunities and building their career.\nCareer advancement: An MBA degree can help MCA graduates advance their careers by providing them with the necessary skills and knowledge to take on leadership roles in their organizations. They can also gain a broader perspective on the industry, which can be useful in identifying new career opportunities.\n\nHowever, before pursuing an MBA, MCA graduates should consider their career goals and determine if an MBA degree aligns with their aspirations. They should also consider the cost and time involved in pursuing an MBA degree and weigh the benefits against the investment.\n\nHere are some tips for MCA graduates considering pursuing an MBA:\n\nResearch: MCA graduates should research different MBA programs to identify the ones that best align with their career goals. They should consider factors such as program curriculum, faculty, rankings, and reputation.\nPrepare for admission: MBA programs have rigorous admission requirements, and MCA graduates should prepare accordingly. They should work on their communication and writing skills, prepare for the GMAT (Graduate Management Admission Test), and gather relevant documents such as transcripts and recommendation letters.\nChoose a specialization: MBA programs offer various specializations such as finance, marketing, human resources, and operations. MCA graduates should choose a specialization that aligns with their career goals and interests.\nConsider the cost: MBA programs can be expensive, and MCA graduates should consider the cost and determine if they can afford it. They should also explore scholarship and financial aid opportunities.\nNetwork: MCA graduates should take advantage of networking opportunities provided by their MBA program. They should attend industry events, connect with alumni, and participate in internships to build their professional network.\n\nIn conclusion, MCA graduates can pursue an MBA degree to develop their management and leadership skills and gain a broader perspective on business operations. An MBA degree can provide them with the necessary skills and knowledge to advance their career in the IT industry or pursue a career in business management. However, they should carefully consider their career goals and the cost and time involved in pursuing an MBA degree before making a decision.",
        "name": "Aniket Sharma",
        "views": "7 views",
        "link": "https://collegeforum.quora.com/Can-MCA-graduates-pursue-MBA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is the minimum percentage required to be eligible for an MCA course in PES University (CEC)?",
        "answer": "Hello Aspirant,\n\nThe eligibility criteria for admission to the MCA (Master of Computer Applications) course at PES University's Department of Computer Applications (CEC) are as follows:\n\nCandidates must have a bachelor's degree in any discipline from a recognized university.\nCandidates must have studied Mathematics or Statistics as a compulsory subject at the 10+2 level or at the graduation level.\nCandidates must have secured a minimum aggregate of 50% marks in their bachelor's degree (45% for SC/ST candidates).\n\nTherefore, the minimum percentage required to be eligible for an MCA course in PES University (CEC) is 50% (aggregate) in the bachelor's degree. Candidates who have secured less than 50% marks in their bachelor's degree are not eligible for admission to the MCA course at PES University.\n\nIf it is advisable and informative\n\nplz follow , upvote and share.\n\nThanks",
        "name": "Career Initiative",
        "views": "52 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-minimum-percentage-required-to-be-eligible-for-an-MCA-course-in-PES-University-CEC",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is the main criteria for admission at Christ University for a BCA?",
        "answer": "The main criteria for admission to the Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) program at Christ University are as follows:\n\nEducational Qualification: Candidates should have passed the 10+2 level examination (or equivalent) with Mathematics as one of the subjects.\nMinimum Percentage: Candidates should have secured a minimum of 50% aggregate marks in their 10+2 level examination (or equivalent) in order to be eligible for admission.\nEntrance Exam: Christ University conducts an entrance exam called the Christ University Entrance Test (CUET) for admission to the BCA program. Candidates are required to appear for the exam and secure a minimum score in order to be considered for admission.\nPersonal Interview: Shortlisted candidates are required to attend a personal interview, which is conducted to assess the candidate's communication skills, academic background, and suitability for the program.\n\nIn addition to the above criteria, candidates may also be required to meet certain age and physical fitness requirements, as specified by the university. It is recommended to visit the official website of Christ University or contact their admissions office for further information on the admission process and eligibility criteria.",
        "name": "Pakshal Ghiya",
        "views": "22 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-main-criteria-for-admission-at-Christ-University-for-a-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which bands or artists have closed out a decade by releasing one of their best albums?",
        "answer": "Hailing from Gainesville, Fla., Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers combined the folk-rock jangle of the Byrds with Rolling Stones crunch and a redneck snarl. Their first few singles didn't catch on in the U.S., but rather in the U.K., where they fit in perfectly with Britain's pub-rock scene. Americans discovered them by 1978, and in 1979, the Heartbreakers released their third album Damn the Torpedoes through MCA's Backstreet label.\n\nThe album was a breakthrough for Petty and the Heartbreakers. It was their first top 10 album, rising to #2 for seven weeks and kept from #1 by Pink Floyd's The Wall on the Billboard albums chart. Tom Petty's response to Westwood One about being anchored at #2 was \"I love Pink Floyd, but I hated them that year\". Damn the Torpedoes yielded two songs that made the top 15 on the Billboard Hot 100 singles chart, \"Don't Do Me Like That\" (#10) and \"Refugee\" (#15).\n\nThe album went on to become certified Triple Platinum by the Recording Industry Association of America (RIAA).\n\nTop 30 American Classic Rock Bands of the '70s\n\nTom Petty and the Heartbreakers - Wikipedia\n\nDamn the Torpedoes (album) - Wikipedia",
        "name": "Victor Padilla",
        "views": "31.8K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-better-an-MCA-or-2-2-LPA-at-Infosys-for-the-role-of-Systems-Associate",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/developersIndia",
        "author": "u/DustLiving2085",
        "question": "where should I focus more : masters or upskilling",
        "upvotes": "2",
        "comment": "2",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/developersIndia/comments/10f16ho/where_should_i_focus_more_masters_or_upskilling/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/saryuun12",
        "author": "u/saryuun12",
        "question": "Best College for BCA in Dehradun | Bachelor of Computer Application",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/saryuun12/comments/120bnbp/best_college_for_bca_in_dehradun_bachelor_of/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Nepal",
        "author": "u/Disastrous-Stick-329",
        "question": "Bachelor in computer application(BCA)",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "8",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Nepal/comments/11zjra2/bachelor_in_computer_applicationbca/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Is it worth doing an MCA degree? Would spending that time after graduating with a Bachelor’s in computer science gaining hands-on experience in a job be worth more?",
        "answer": "Deciding whether to pursue an MCA degree or gain hands-on experience after graduating with a Bachelor's in computer science depends on various factors, such as career goals and personal circumstances.\n\nAn MCA degree can offer specialized knowledge and training in computer applications that can be highly beneficial in certain career paths, such as software development, database management, and network administration. However, pursuing an MCA degree can also be expensive and time-consuming.\n\nOn the other hand, gaining hands-on experience in a job can provide valuable skills and knowledge in the field, which can be advantageous in securing job opportunities and advancing one's career. It can also help individuals identify specific areas within the field that interest them the most. However, it may take time to find suitable job opportunities, and there may be limited opportunities for growth in certain roles.\n\nUltimately, it is up to the individual to evaluate their career goals and personal circumstances to determine which path aligns best with their needs. In some cases, pursuing an MCA degree may be more beneficial, while in other cases, gaining hands-on experience may be a more viable option.",
        "name": "Janvi Chauhan",
        "views": "28 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-worth-doing-an-MCA-degree-Would-spending-that-time-after-graduating-with-a-Bachelor%E2%80%99s-in-computer-science-gaining-hands-on-experience-in-a-job-be-worth-more",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/cscareerquestions",
        "author": "u/jkluniversity",
        "question": "Switching Careers to IT security at 34",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/cscareerquestions/comments/y646al/switching_careers_to_it_security_at_34/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/srmuniversity7",
        "author": "u/admissionguru1",
        "question": "SRM University Delhi NCR Sonepat: An Ideal Place to Pursue Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA).",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/srmuniversity7/comments/1170fth/srm_university_delhi_ncr_sonepat_an_ideal_place/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/mohammadfaiz1",
        "author": "u/mohammadfaiz1",
        "question": "Study MCA in USA: A Quick Guide",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/mohammadfaiz1/comments/11169qd/study_mca_in_usa_a_quick_guide/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Can MCA students get jobs at PSUs through the GATE CS?",
        "answer": "Yes, MCA (Master of Computer Applications) students are eligible to apply for jobs in Public Sector Undertakings (PSUs) through the GATE CS (Computer Science and Information Technology) exam. Many PSUs such as BHEL, ONGC, HPCL, IOCL, and NTPC, among others, offer job opportunities for MCA graduates through the GATE CS exam.\n\nTo apply for these jobs, MCA students need to qualify in the GATE CS exam and then apply for the job openings advertised by the respective PSUs. The selection process usually includes a written test and/or interview, and candidates are selected based on their GATE score and performance in the selection process.\n\nHowever, it's worth noting that the number of job openings for MCA graduates in PSUs through GATE is relatively low compared to the openings available for candidates with an engineering background. Nonetheless, MCA graduates who qualify in GATE can also apply for job opportunities in other sectors such as software development, IT consulting, and data analytics, among others.\n\nHope it will help you.\n\nThank you for reading..!!",
        "name": "Vineet Kumar Sharma",
        "views": "73 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Can-MCA-students-get-jobs-at-PSUs-through-the-GATE-CS",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Which has the better scope, an MCA or an MSc in data science?",
        "answer": "Both MCA (Master of Computer Applications) and MSc (Master of Science) in Data Science have good career prospects, depending on your interests and career goals.\n\nMCA focuses on computer applications and programming skills, along with some business management and software development courses. Graduates with an MCA degree can find job opportunities in software development, IT consulting, system administration, and other areas of computer science.\n\nOn the other hand, an MSc in Data Science focuses specifically on data analysis, machine learning, and statistical modeling, among other data-related fields. Graduates with an MSc in Data Science can find job opportunities in data analysis, data engineering, data science, and other data-related fields.\n\nIn terms of scope, both fields have a high demand for skilled professionals, and the demand is expected to increase in the coming years. Ultimately, the better option depends on your interests and career goals, as both fields have their unique strengths and opportunities.",
        "name": "Puneett Bhatnagr",
        "views": "25 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-has-the-better-scope-an-MCA-or-an-MSc-in-data-science",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Why is South Africa clearly the most developed African country with a predominant black population?",
        "answer": "Because it was developed by the largest white population in Africa. Its gone steadily down hill or become more african since white people lost control\n\nEdit\n\nI have added this to illustrate how much the economy has been destroyed since the advent of black rule. South Africa up until the 1990’s produced more electricity than the rest of Africa combined. Had more miles of functioning(!!) roads and railway than the rest of Africa combined, had the highest employment and literacy levels and health care . All of which have collapsed and was the wealthiest country in the Southern hemisphere. On any measure South Africa was better before ANC rule than it is now. Especially crime. Now South Africa is looking more and more like the rest of Africa. Another African country. Proving the inability of Africa and its people to function in the modern world\n\nhttps://businesstech.co.za/news/finance/576512/what-it-takes-to-be-middle-class-in-south-africa-right-now/\nIQ by Country\nIQ compared by countriesThe question of the intelligence of a certain nationality or population may be controversial. In fact, intelligence is influenced by national, political, and geographic factors. Often surprisingly, but scientifically proven, a warmer climate has a markedly bad influence on the intelligence quotient. With an average IQ of 98 points, the USA ranks 26th in this ranking. With 108 points, the inhabitants of Singapore reach the highest intelligence quotas worldwide. The last place with only 56 points is occupied by Equatorial Guinea. In addition to the simple ranking of countries, the following table shows the influence of prosperity and climate.\nhttps://www.worlddata.info/iq-by-country.php\nAre the Wealthiest Countries the Smartest Countries?\nIt's not just how free the market is. Some economists are looking at another factor that determines how much a country's economy flourishes: how smart its people are. For a study published in an upcoming …\nhttps://www.psychologicalscience.org/news/releases/are-the-wealthiest-countries-the-smartest-countries.html",
        "name": "Neil McA.",
        "views": "1K views",
        "link": "https://worldhistory.quora.com/Why-didn-t-Harry-Truman-face-any-trial-for-dropping-a-nuclear-bomb-that-caused-genocide-of-the-Japanese",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/careerguidance",
        "author": "u/Puzzleheaded-Fox1868",
        "question": "Can i start my degree and enter IT sector now that i am 24?",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "2",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/careerguidance/comments/10rw8be/can_i_start_my_degree_and_enter_it_sector_now/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "I want to pursue a BCA after class 12. Which optional subject should I choose with commerce, maths or computer?",
        "answer": "Both are most important subject in bca.\n\nIf you want to choose maths and computer then I suggest maths. If you take both subject, that are good\n\nAnd banefacial for you and also for doing bca.",
        "name": "Rupa Kumari",
        "views": "19 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/I-want-to-pursue-a-BCA-after-class-12-Which-optional-subject-should-I-choose-with-commerce-maths-or-computer",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Is NSS/NCC at NIT Trichy for MCA students?",
        "answer": "The National Service Scheme (NSS) and National Cadet Corps (NCC) are voluntary programs that are available to all undergraduate and postgraduate students in many colleges and universities in India, including NIT Trichy.\n\nAs for NIT Trichy specifically, both NSS and NCC are available to students of all departments, including MCA (Master of Computer Applications) students. These programs provide opportunities for students to develop leadership skills, engage in community service, and participate in various activities and events.\n\nMCA students at NIT Trichy can choose to participate in NSS or NCC activities as per their interest and availability. The specific activities and requirements for participation may vary depending on the program, so interested students should check with the NSS or NCC coordinators at NIT Trichy for more information.",
        "name": "Ujjwal Matoliya",
        "views": "34 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-NSS-NCC-at-NIT-Trichy-for-MCA-students",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/getadmision",
        "author": "u/getadmision",
        "question": "Why BCA become Important in Today’s Life…",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/getadmision/comments/z0xdnf/why_bca_become_important_in_todays_life/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are some jobs for MCA or IT students?",
        "answer": "MCA (Master of Computer Applications) or IT (Information Technology) graduates have a wide range of job opportunities available to them. Here are some common jobs that MCA or IT students can pursue:\n\nSoftware Developer: This is a popular job option for MCA or IT graduates. They can work in software development companies or even start their own software development firm.\nDatabase Administrator: MCA or IT students can work as database administrators, managing the organization, storage, and retrieval of data in computer systems.\nSystem Analyst: System analysts work to improve computer systems by analyzing user requirements and designing solutions that meet those requirements.\nNetwork Administrator: Network administrators manage the computer networks of organizations, ensuring that they are secure and operating efficiently.\nCybersecurity Analyst: With the increasing importance of cybersecurity, MCA or IT graduates can work as cybersecurity analysts, protecting computer systems from security threats.\nWeb Developer: Web developers design and develop websites and web applications for individuals and organizations.\nMobile Application Developer: As mobile devices continue to grow in popularity, MCA or IT graduates can work as mobile application developers, creating applications for smartphones and tablets.\nIT Consultant: MCA or IT graduates can also work as IT consultants, advising organizations on how to use technology to achieve their goals.\n\nThese are just a few of the many job options available to MCA or IT graduates. The field of computer science and information technology is constantly evolving, so there are always new opportunities emerging.",
        "name": "Ritesh",
        "views": "13 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-jobs-for-MCA-or-IT-students",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What are some good and affordable BCA colleges in Gurugram, India?",
        "answer": "Bachelors in Computer Application, also known as BCA is a three-year degree program. It’s a digital course pursued by those who want to build their career in Information technology. It comprises of subjects such as networking, data structure, programming, etc. This three-year course gives a deep insight into the world of computers, technology, and its applications.\n\nAre you on a quest to find the perfect college for yourself that checks all the boxes?\n\nHere’s a list of some good and affordable BCA colleges in Gurugram, India:\n\n· World College of Technology and Management, Gurugram\n\n· KR Mangalam University, Gurugram\n\n· Brij Mohan Institute of Management, Gurugram\n\n· School of Engineering and Technology, Gurugram\n\n· Amity University, Gurugram\n\n· Starex University, Gurugram\n\nPersonally, I would suggest World College of Technology and Management (WCTM) which will full-fill all your parameters for a perfect college. WCTM Gurugram has everything you’re looking for- from experienced faculty, advanced infrastructure, inter-disciplinary pedagogy, extensive curricular, affordable course fee, hostel facilities, to impeccable placement records.\n\nIndia is a home to prestigious institutions for pursuing BCA. I’d suggest you to go for a college that fits in your demands along with being cost-effective. WCTM provides all the facilities of a world-class institution with an affordable tuition fee as well as hostel fee structure.\n\nThe department of computer applications aims at holistic development of the students, imbibing practical knowledge with the latest technology.\n\nTherefore, World College of Technology and Management checks all the boxes for being the best college for BCA in Gurugram.\n\nClick on the link for more information- Best engineering college in Gurgaon | Best engineering college in Delhi NCR | WCTM",
        "name": "Ashok Deshmukh",
        "views": "205 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-good-and-affordable-BCA-colleges-in-Gurugram-India",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "How are the placements for an MCA in Mount Carmel College, Bangalore?",
        "answer": "Mount Carmel College, Bangalore has a dedicated placement cell that works towards providing the best career opportunities to its MCA students. The placement cell organizes various placement activities, including campus drives, career fairs, and industry visits, to help students interact with potential employers and get job offers.\n\nMany reputed companies from various sectors visit the campus for recruitment, and a good number of students get placed in top-notch organizations every year. Some of the popular recruiters who have visited the campus for MCA placements include Infosys, Wipro, TCS, Cognizant, HCL, IBM, Oracle, and Capgemini, among others.\n\nThe average salary package offered to MCA students in Mount Carmel College is around 3 to 5 lakhs per annum, while the highest salary package offered can go up to 10 lakhs per annum, depending on the candidate's skills and performance during the placement process.\n\nOverall, Mount Carmel College has a good reputation for providing quality education and excellent placement opportunities to its MCA students, which makes it a preferred choice for students aspiring to pursue a career in computer applications.",
        "name": "Sandeep Jaiswal",
        "views": "50 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-are-the-placements-for-an-MCA-in-Mount-Carmel-College-Bangalore",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Can a BCom student study an MCA?",
        "answer": "After earning your B. Com., you can most definitely enroll in an MCA program. The candidate must have earned a bachelor's degree in science, commerce, engineering, or a related field from a recognized university or institute in order to be eligible for an MCA.\n\n(Hope This Answer Will Help You)",
        "name": "College Sakha",
        "views": "789 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-PGDCA-really-helpful-to-do-before-doing-an-MCA-I-have-done-a-B-Com-and-want-to-pursue-a-career-in-the-IT-sector",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Can I do an MCA from NIT after a BA or a BSc in zoology?",
        "answer": "Hello Aspirant,\n\nYes, you can pursue an MCA (Master of Computer Applications) from a National Institute of Technology (NIT) after completing a BA or a BSc in Zoology. However, you will have to fulfill certain eligibility criteria to be eligible for admission to the MCA program at an NIT.\n\nThe eligibility criteria for MCA admission at NITs usually include:\n\nCompletion of a Bachelor's degree in any discipline with Mathematics as a subject in Class 12 or at the undergraduate level.\nA minimum aggregate score of 60% or 6.5 CGPA (on a 10-point scale) in the qualifying examination.\nQualifying in a national-level entrance exam like NIMCET (NIT MCA Common Entrance Test).\n\nIf you fulfill the above eligibility criteria, you can appear for the NIMCET entrance exam and qualify for admission to the MCA program at any of the participating NITs, subject to the availability of seats and other admission criteria.\n\nIt is important to note that a background in Zoology may not be directly relevant to the MCA program, which is focused on computer applications and software development. However, if you have a strong interest in computer applications and are willing to work hard to develop your skills, you can certainly pursue an MCA and build a successful career in the field of information technology.\n\nIf it is advisable and informative\n\nplz follow , upvote and share.\n\nThanks",
        "name": "Career Initiative",
        "views": "84 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-prospects-for-an-MCA-graduate-from-UPES-Dehradun",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/UWindsor",
        "author": "u/seraphlive",
        "question": "Is application for Master of Applied Computing Winter 2024 closed？",
        "upvotes": "3",
        "comment": "2",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/UWindsor/comments/10ua8e9/is_application_for_master_of_applied_computing/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/resumes",
        "author": "u/getadmision",
        "question": "I'm graduating in 2022 with a bachelor's in Computer Science. I've been trying to apply for internships and Entry-level positions. I've sent almost 100 applications over the last month and a half and have not heard a peep back. Would anyone happen to have advice about how I can improve my resume?",
        "upvotes": "48",
        "comment": "23",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/resumes/comments/sflzcj/im_graduating_in_2022_with_a_bachelors_in/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Which is the best coaching for the NIMCET for the MCA exam in India?",
        "answer": "As per the 2023 March education survey report, Gate Indian Institute of Tutorials GATEIIT JP Nagar Bangalore is ranking on top of India for NIMCET MCA entrance examination.\n\nGateiit is known for it's high quality nimcet crash course and full courses with personal attention classes.\n\nBest teachers who all are nimcet toppers are teaching here with best efforts.\n\nI hope you will like them.\n\nBest of luck for your upcoming 2024 nimcet exam preparation!",
        "name": "Sonali Ganguli",
        "views": "122 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-coaching-for-the-NIMCET-for-the-MCA-exam-in-India",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Futurology",
        "author": "u/Tejas9311",
        "question": "This mirror reverses how light travels in time. There are already applications in wireless, radar, and optical-computing.",
        "upvotes": "685",
        "comment": "77",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Futurology/comments/120j5ro/this_mirror_reverses_how_light_travels_in_time/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the fee structures of online courses in Graphics Era University?",
        "answer": "Hi, I’m working in Graphic Era University as a member of online admission counsellimg team. Let me brief you a little about the courses and their fee structures available in the online mode.\n\nUndergraduate Programs:\n\n1. Bachelors in Business Administration (BBA),\n\n2. Bachelors in Commerce, and\n\n3. Bachelors in Computer Applications (BCA).\n\nPost-graduate Programs:\n\n1. Master in Business Administration (MBA) and\n\n2. Masters in Computer Applications (MCA).\n\nPlease find the Fee structure at the following link: https://geuonline.com/\n\nThere is also a fee concession available of 25% which is exclusive for the alumni of the university.\n\nThis concession’s available for the session 2023. It may vary in the further sessions\n\nFeel free to reply if you need more information.",
        "name": "Khushi Mehrotra",
        "views": "92 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-fee-structures-of-online-courses-in-Graphics-Era-University",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "I m doing b.sc can I do MCA?",
        "answer": "NO, you can't do mca after bsc.\n\nYou can do MCA after only BCA rather than other degree.\n\nYou can do MBA after BCA through CAT exam..",
        "name": "Jayram Sharma",
        "views": "347 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Would-Mensa-notice-if-a-person-with-an-average-IQ-slipped-into-a-meeting",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Now I have completed an MCA, and I’m planning to go to the UK for another master’s. Which one is better, an MSc in project management or an Msc in software engineering?",
        "answer": "Software engineering.",
        "name": "Dominic Lawson",
        "views": "27 views",
        "link": "https://jobsandcareersguide.quora.com/Now-I-have-completed-an-MCA-and-I-m-planning-to-go-to-the-UK-for-another-master-s-Which-one-is-better-an-MSc-in-proje",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "How good is mca at srm university?",
        "answer": "Depending on the companies you receive, you should maintain a minimum of 8.0 cgpa in order to be on every company's list and have a better chance of being selected for an interview.You will receive an app for placement offers in which you can select and apply to any company you want! It will display your compatibility cgpa and all of the companies to which you can apply.\n\nBest wishes!",
        "name": "Get College Vidya",
        "views": "163 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-good-is-mca-at-srm-university",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Has CA New Scheme of Education and Training proposed by ICAI already implemented or yet to be implemented?",
        "answer": "It is yet to be implemented as the approval of MCA is still awaited. Once MCA approves the new scheme, it will come into effect for the future attempts.",
        "name": "Saumya",
        "views": "324 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-can-you-register-a-company-with-two-names-in-India",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is the full form of MCA?",
        "answer": "MCA stands for \"Master of Computer Applications\".",
        "name": "Kajal Kumari",
        "views": "109 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-full-form-of-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Which college is better for a BCA, NIM Mumbai, D. Y. Patil Pune or Sandip University Nashik?",
        "answer": "Sandip University is definitely a best place to pursue your BCA studies. The BCA degree at Sandip University is designed in a very unique manner. The curriculum for the course is designed according to the current market needs and is industry-oriented. The curriculum is designed by faculties from premier institutions such as IIT’s and IIM’s.\n\nOne of the important highlights of this program is also the guest lectures by industry professionals. Industry professionals give guest lectures to the students. This helps the students to know about the current happenings in the industry and also helps them to understand the ways and means in which they can apply their BCA degree in the industry. The guest lectures helps the students in knowing about the latest trends in the industry.\n\nThe BCA degree is a 3 year course spread across 6 semesters, which helps the students to gain practical skills in addressing problems that arise from computer systems and applications. Subjects such as computer fundamentals, basic programming skills and IT, problem-solving technique using C, exposure of computer discipline, computer architecture and much more are taught in this course.\n\nAfter graduating BCA, 100% guaranteed job placement is given to the students. Various MNC’s visit the University for recruiting students. The students are trained through the employability enhancement program for cracking these interviews. Students are trained via mock interviews, group discussions, simulation and role-play sessions amongst many other activities.\n\nThe BCA course has a very good placement record and students are placed in various MNC’s such as:\n\n· Microsoft\n\n· Amazon India\n\n· Deloitte\n\n· Larson & Toubro\n\n· Intel\n\n· Marvell\n\n· IBM\n\nIf you want to pursue a BCA degree, look no further than Sandip University!",
        "name": "Janardan Yadav",
        "views": "16 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-college-is-better-for-a-BCA-NIM-Mumbai-D-Y-Patil-Pune-or-Sandip-University-Nashik",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/digiomg",
        "author": "u/Interesting-Animal67",
        "question": "Best MCA College List 40+ All Over India: Best college for Master of Computer Application (MCA) in India. Top MCA Government Colleges/Universities in India and Best private colleges for Master of Computer Application (MCA) in India.",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/digiomg/comments/utnskm/best_mca_college_list_40_all_over_india_best/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/MakeNewFriendsHere",
        "author": "u/chaoticquantaa",
        "question": "M22 India/Anywhere - An Infj and demi looking for someone to connect with and talk about daily lives",
        "upvotes": "2",
        "comment": "1",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/MakeNewFriendsHere/comments/1115k4a/m22_indiaanywhere_an_infj_and_demi_looking_for/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/gmu",
        "author": "u/Ok_Pineapple_12",
        "question": "Masters in computer science",
        "upvotes": "6",
        "comment": "11",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/gmu/comments/12a3iks/masters_in_computer_science/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/TapTitans2",
        "author": "u/throwawayIELTS",
        "question": "[CLAN RECRUITMENT - zgypb] Active Players - Currently 55th in Master Tier but aiming for the top 50 and then ever higher! We are one of the highest public clans that you can join without an application! 1 space is available right now!",
        "upvotes": "3",
        "comment": "1",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/TapTitans2/comments/129jfzy/clan_recruitment_zgypb_active_players_currently/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Which one is better, an MCA or an MSc in computer science?",
        "answer": "Both MCA (Master of Computer Applications) and MSc (Master of Science) in Computer Science are valuable degrees that can lead to a successful career in the field of computer science. However, the better option depends on your interests and career goals.\n\nMCA is more focused on application development, database management, and software engineering. It is a specialized degree that provides students with a strong foundation in computer science and software development. MCA courses also cover subjects such as data structures, algorithms, computer networks, and programming languages.\n\nOn the other hand, MSc in Computer Science is a more research-oriented degree that focuses on theoretical aspects of computer science such as algorithms, programming languages, and computer systems. MSc courses cover subjects such as artificial intelligence, machine learning, computer vision, and data analytics.\n\nIf you are interested in pursuing a career in software development, application development, and database management, MCA may be a better option for you. If you are interested in pursuing a career in research, development of new technologies, and computer systems, MSc in Computer Science may be a better option.\n\nUltimately, it is important to research and carefully consider your career goals and interests before choosing between these two degrees.",
        "name": "Eduxprts",
        "views": "24 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-one-is-better-an-MCA-or-an-MSc-in-computer-science",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/MechanicalEngineering",
        "author": "u/saryuun12",
        "question": "Can I study mechanical engineering in master if I have degree in bachelor in computer science ? If yes which university in US will accept me?",
        "upvotes": "10",
        "comment": "5",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/MechanicalEngineering/comments/12alvtr/can_i_study_mechanical_engineering_in_master_if_i/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "How is SGT University for BCA in Cloud Computing?",
        "answer": "SGT University is a private university located in Gurgaon, India, that offers a Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) program with a specialization in Cloud Computing. The quality of the BCA in Cloud Computing program at SGT University can vary depending on factors such as the quality of faculty, the resources available to students, and the curriculum.\n\nThat being said, SGT University has been accredited by the University Grants Commission (UGC) and is recognized by the All India Council for Technical Education (AICTE). The university also has partnerships with several companies, which may provide students with opportunities for internships and practical experience.\n\nTo get a better understanding of the quality of the BCA in Cloud Computing program at SGT University, you may want to consider factors such as the university's reputation, the experience, and qualifications of the faculty, the resources available to students (such as computer labs and library facilities), and the curriculum. You may also want to speak with current students or alumni of the program to get their perspectives on the program's strengths and weaknesses.",
        "name": "Syed Asad",
        "views": "6 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-is-SGT-University-for-BCA-in-Cloud-Computing",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/Broad-Worldliness7",
        "author": "u/Intrepid_Arrival_166",
        "question": "Find the Best BCA Distance Colleges Online in India with Distance Pathshala",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/Broad-Worldliness7/comments/zrdod1/find_the_best_bca_distance_colleges_online_in/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Were you able to do CA and BCA together?",
        "answer": "CA and BCA can be done together. But both are different fields. With CA, B. Com goes better. But if you really want to do BCA with it, it shouldn't be a problem.",
        "name": "Navkar Digital Institute",
        "views": "22 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Were-you-able-to-do-CA-and-BCA-together",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/MBA",
        "author": "u/ta201608",
        "question": "I have a Master in computer science but I’m having problems breaking into management. Is it worth it to pick up an MBA? Did it make a big difference for you?",
        "upvotes": "34",
        "comment": "22",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/MBA/comments/11ojdet/i_have_a_master_in_computer_science_but_im_having/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/gradadmissions",
        "author": "u/Edubuild",
        "question": "Is doing Masters in Computer Science worth it amidst current Market layoffs?",
        "upvotes": "38",
        "comment": "13",
        "timestamp": "Past hours",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/gradadmissions/comments/11uj3vl/is_doing_masters_in_computer_science_worth_it/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Is MCA admission available in Bangalore?",
        "answer": "Hello Candidate,\n\nMCA admissions 2022 to the best MCA colleges in Bangalore are based on merit and also through entrance exams such as Karnataka PGCET/ KMAT followed by a GD/ PI round. The top government MCA colleges in Bangalore are Bangalore University, Dr.\n\nIf it is advisable and informative\n\nplz upvote and share.\n\nThanks",
        "name": "Career Initiative",
        "views": "189 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Does-MIT-WPU-offer-an-MCA-program",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/saryuun12",
        "author": "u/saryuun12",
        "question": "Best BCA college in Dehradun| Bachelor of Computer Application",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/saryuun12/comments/12bayrc/best_bca_college_in_dehradun_bachelor_of_computer/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/getadmision",
        "author": "u/tiipsindia",
        "question": "Why BCA is so Important…",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/getadmision/comments/y2tlmo/why_bca_is_so_important/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Is it a good option to do an MBA after a BCA?",
        "answer": "There is no one-size-fits-all answer to this question, as the best option for pursuing an MBA after a BCA will vary depending on each individual's qualifications and goals.\n\nHowever, in general, an MBA can be a great way to further develop your skills and knowledge in business administration and management, which can be beneficial for careers in a variety of industries.",
        "name": "Louis Stevens",
        "views": "723 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-a-good-option-to-do-an-MBA-after-a-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "How long does it take to complete an M.Tech course after a BCA?",
        "answer": "To pursue an M.Tech course, one needs to have a Bachelor's degree in Engineering or Technology. BCA (Bachelor of Computer Applications) is not a qualifying degree for admission to M.Tech programs.\n\nTypically, M.Tech is a two-year postgraduate degree program in engineering or technology. To be eligible for M.Tech admission, candidates should have completed a Bachelor's degree in Engineering or Technology (B.Tech or B.E.) in a relevant field from a recognized university with a minimum of 60% marks. However, some institutes may also consider candidates with a Master's degree in Science (http://M.Sc\n.) or a Master's degree in Computer Applications (MCA) for admission to M.Tech programs.\n\nSo, after completing a BCA degree, one needs to pursue a B.Tech or B.E. degree in a relevant field to become eligible for M.Tech admission. The duration of the B.Tech or B.E. program is typically four years, after which one can apply for M.Tech admission.\n\nIn summary, to pursue an M.Tech course, one needs to complete a Bachelor's degree in Engineering or Technology (B.Tech or B.E.) in a relevant field after BCA, which typically takes four years, followed by a two-year M.Tech program.",
        "name": "Study Rate",
        "views": "12 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-long-does-it-take-to-complete-an-M-Tech-course-after-a-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Indian_Academia",
        "author": "u/jakedc13",
        "question": "Does 3 Gap years(no job experience) between bachelor's and master's affect placements/PhD admissions in tier 1 colleges for Mtech CS/IT",
        "upvotes": "4",
        "comment": "7",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Indian_Academia/comments/w24wx6/does_3_gap_yearsno_job_experience_between/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "twitter",
        "name": "V.Rahul Pillai",
        "handle": "@vrahulpillai",
        "timestamp": "Nov 5, 2009",
        "like": "",
        "replies": "",
        "retweets": "",
        "text": "graduation in Bachelor in Computer Application",
        "link": "https://twitter.com/vrahulpillai/status/5455110989",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/education",
        "author": "u/saryuun12",
        "question": "Is Australia a better option for Masters in Computer Science?",
        "upvotes": "6",
        "comment": "12",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/education/comments/128mi2i/is_australia_a_better_option_for_masters_in/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "I am planning of doing BCA then an MBA. Should I do a MCA as well?",
        "answer": "The decision to pursue a MCA degree depends on your career goals and the field you wish to specialize in. MCA is a postgraduate degree that provides advanced knowledge and skills in computer applications and software development.\n\nIf you are interested in a career in the field of computer science and want to specialize in software development or programming, then MCA can be a good option for you. However, if you are more interested in business management and want to work in a managerial position, an MBA degree would be more appropriate.\n\nIt's important to note that having multiple degrees can make you more competitive in the job market and broaden your career prospects. However, pursuing multiple degrees can also be time-consuming and expensive. Therefore, you should carefully evaluate your career goals, interests, and financial resources before making a decision.",
        "name": "College Sakha",
        "views": "19 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/I-am-planning-of-doing-BCA-then-an-MBA-Should-I-do-a-MCA-as-well",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/saryuun12",
        "author": "u/phineasandferb2011",
        "question": "Best BCA college in Dehradun| Bachelor of Computer Application",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/saryuun12/comments/12abxdc/best_bca_college_in_dehradun_bachelor_of_computer/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are the best universities for an MCA course in Bihar?",
        "answer": "There are several universities in Bihar that offer MCA (Master of Computer Applications) courses. Some of the best universities for MCA in Bihar are:\n\nNalanda Open University, Patna\nPatna University, Patna\nMagadh University, Bodh Gaya\nBabasaheb Bhimrao Ambedkar Bihar University, Muzaffarpur\nAryabhatta Knowledge University, Patna\n\nThese universities are well-known for their quality education in the field of computer science and have experienced faculty members, well-equipped computer labs, and updated curriculum to provide a better learning experience to the students. It is recommended to research each university's admission process, curriculum, and other relevant information to determine which one best suits your needs and preferences.\n\nWhen I was searching for university , I take a help of vidya planet which provide me proper guidance in finding Distance and online University .",
        "name": "Priya Joshi",
        "views": "25 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-universities-for-an-MCA-course-in-Bihar",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/careeradvice",
        "author": "u/eksing",
        "question": "Switching Careers to IT security at 34",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "2",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/careeradvice/comments/y5je69/switching_careers_to_it_security_at_34/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/jamiamilliaislamia",
        "author": "u/Jaded_Presentation62",
        "question": "Can I do Bachelor in computer application from jamia millia if i have done my 12th with pcb",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "2",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/jamiamilliaislamia/comments/zmieye/can_i_do_bachelor_in_computer_application_from/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What are name of BCA colleges for arts students?",
        "answer": "First I want to list out some of the BCA colleges in India and then I will suggest you some points so that you can choose a better college for your future.\n\nChrist University - Bangalore,\nSymbiosis Institute of Computer Studies and Research - Pune,\nMadras Christian College (MCC) - Chennai,\nLovely Professional University, Amity University - Noida,\nLoyola College - Chennai, St. Xavier's College - Ahmedabad,\nWomen's Christian College – Chennai,\nDAV College - Chandigarh,\nStella Maris College – Chennai,\nKristu Jayanti College – Bangalore,\n\nLet’s come to second part of the answer, I want to recommend you a college with better exposure which is also leading in these days. Lovely professional University. After completing the course from this university, students will have a thorough understanding of how to create computer programmes that meet the needs of users utilising a variety of programming languages such as C, C++, Python, Java, and others. With solid academic understanding of computer applications, an entry-level computer applications software engineer can readily find work in big IT businesses. BCA graduates can work as Software Consultants, Network Engineers, Database Administrators, Test Engineers, System Analysts, Programmers, and Quality Assurance Engineers with companies like Microsoft, Oracle, Wipro, Infosys, Cisco, Citibank, and so on.\n\nThe students at LPU have strong career chances in the banking industry as well. The BCA degree also prepares students for a variety of postgraduate programmes. MSc. I.T., PGDCA, MSc. CS, and MCA are among them.\n\nTo know more visit its website.",
        "name": "Ayush Raj",
        "views": "3K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-name-of-BCA-colleges-for-arts-students",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/csMajors",
        "author": "u/Malikthehedgehog",
        "question": "Switching Careers to IT security at 34",
        "upvotes": "3",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/csMajors/comments/y647al/switching_careers_to_it_security_at_34/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the differences between an MCA and a BCA from VIT?",
        "answer": "Hello Aspirant,\n\nMCA (Master of Computer Applications) and BCA (Bachelor of Computer Applications) are both computer science programs offered at VIT University, but there are some significant differences between the two degrees. Here are a few key differences between the two:\n\nLevel of study: BCA is an undergraduate program, while MCA is a postgraduate program. This means that MCA is a more advanced degree and requires more in-depth study and specialization.\nDuration: BCA is typically a three-year program, while MCA is a two-year program. However, some universities may offer a four-year integrated MCA program.\nCurriculum: BCA focuses on building a strong foundation in computer science and programming fundamentals, while MCA is more specialized and focuses on advanced topics such as software engineering, database management, and advanced programming languages.\nJob opportunities: MCA is a more specialized degree and may open up more job opportunities in areas such as software development, database administration, and systems analysis. BCA graduates may find entry-level positions in software development, web development, and IT support.\nSalary potential: In general, MCA graduates may earn a higher salary than BCA graduates due to their advanced degree and specialized knowledge.\nEligibility: To pursue a BCA degree at VIT University, a student must have completed 10+2 with Mathematics or Business Mathematics as one of the subjects. For MCA, a student must have completed a Bachelor's degree in any discipline with Mathematics as one of the subjects in 10+2 or at the undergraduate level.\n\nOverall, both BCA and MCA can be great options for students interested in computer science and information technology. The choice between the two will depend on the student's academic background, career goals, and personal interests.\n\nIf it is advisable and informative\n\nplz follow , upvote and share.\n\nThanks",
        "name": "Career Initiative",
        "views": "47 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-differences-between-an-MCA-and-a-BCA-from-VIT",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "How is Doon Business School for a BCA?",
        "answer": "Doon Business School is a great option for students looking to pursue a Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) degree. Located in Dehradun, India, the school offers a wide range of courses and specializations within the BCA degree.\n\nThis is 3 years full-time undergraduate program offered by Doon Business School affiliated with HNB Garhwal University, Srinagar, Garhwal (Uttarakhand) - A central University. The BCA degree is conferred at the convocation held by HNB Garhwal Universit\ny\n\nDoon Business School attracted students from 29 states and 5 countries. This instigates a healthy and unmatched culture because one of the best sources of student learning is peer interaction.\n\nImagine the variety of experiences students from different backgrounds bring to the classroom, and the contribution they make to the learning process. The different backgrounds, cultures, and mindsets will lead to many long, fascinating, classroom discussions. No doubt, many friendships will also be formed that will last long years after graduation.\n\nThe fees at Doon Business School are affordable and students can apply for financial aid if needed. The school also offers several scholarships and awards to help students with their tuition fees.\n\nIn conclusion, Doon Business School is an excellent option for students looking to pursue a BCA degree.",
        "name": "Shreyansh",
        "views": "10 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-is-Doon-Business-School-for-a-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is the eligibility for an MCA in SRM?",
        "answer": "Being an Educational Consultant, MCA (Master of Computer Applications) program at SRM Institute of Science and Technology, candidates must meet the following eligibility criteria:\n\nEducational qualification: Candidates must have a Bachelor's degree with a minimum of 50% marks in any discipline from a recognized university. Candidates who have studied Mathematics/Statistics/Computer Science/Computer Applications/Business Mathematics/Business Statistics as a subject in their 10+2 or undergraduate level are preferred.\nEntrance exam: Candidates must have a valid score in the SRM Joint Entrance Examination (SRMJEEE) for MCA or other national level entrance exams such as TANCET, NIMCET, or GATE.\nAge limit: There is no age limit for admission to the MCA program at SRM Institute of Science and Technology.\n\nHope it’s fine, feel free to contact 📲8292699093 (Call/WhatsApp) regarding colleges and admissions.\n\nThank you 😊",
        "name": "Sandesh Kumar",
        "views": "66 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-eligibility-for-an-MCA-in-SRM",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/cscareerquestions",
        "author": "u/Specialist-Pride-585",
        "question": "I am doing master in computer applications what else can i do to improve my chances to get hired fast with a decent salary?",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "2",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/cscareerquestions/comments/y9lt9v/i_am_doing_master_in_computer_applications_what/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "How can I engage with you as my personal and company legal advisor?",
        "answer": "Company Law is a different kettle of fish.\n\nIt needs expertise in many areas of Legal operations of companies and legal codes pertaining to SEBI, MCA and ROC\n\nI have never worked in company law and would be totally lost\n\nYou need someone who knows every section of the 2013 Code.\n\nPersonal Legal Advisor?\n\nSure.\n\nIf you have any legal problems (Criminal) and want advise on least cumbersome way to settle the issue, then mediation and arbitration is my speciality especially wrt State Police cases on 420 IPC Or 138 NI Act Or 406 IPC Or 409 IPC Or 498A (Chennai, Trichy, CBE or Bangalore only)\n\nIf you have insurance problems with Health Insurance claims, I handle that\n\nIf you want to import from China & Singapore and need to register a company or tie up with local companies there and establish an LC facility, I handle that\n\nIf you want to export to Russia and pay in AED / Yuan instead of Dollars and want to promote business in Russia, I handle that too\n\nIn any such case if you DM your issue, and if I can offer professional (paid) collaboration, then I will have one of the six people who work with me contact you (Again Bangalore, Chennai, Trichy and Coimbatore only)\n\nOtherwise I can offer you free advise and guide you to people who can help you (Like Real Estate Title Deeds etc)",
        "name": "Kanthaswamy Balasubramaniam",
        "views": "6.8K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-engage-with-you-as-my-personal-and-company-legal-advisor",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/digiomg",
        "author": "u/forrestDumbinho",
        "question": "MCA Top Colleges in India, Best College for Master of Computer Application (MCA)",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/digiomg/comments/u9ded5/mca_top_colleges_in_india_best_college_for_master/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/developersIndia",
        "author": "u/srmuniversity7",
        "question": "BCA degree in India (is it dying?)",
        "upvotes": "9",
        "comment": "28",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/developersIndia/comments/x6c10e/bca_degree_in_india_is_it_dying/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are the drawbacks of doing an MCA from VIT University?",
        "answer": "Hello Aspirant,\n\nLike any educational program or institution, there may be some drawbacks to doing an MCA (Master of Computer Applications) from VIT (Vellore Institute of Technology) University. Some possible drawbacks of doing an MCA from VIT University are:\n\nHigh fees: VIT University is a private institution and has a relatively higher fee structure compared to some other universities in India. The high fees may be a drawback for some students who are looking for more affordable options.\nLocation: VIT University is located in Vellore, which may not be an ideal location for some students who are looking for more urban and cosmopolitan environments.\nAdmission process: The admission process for VIT University is quite competitive, with a significant emphasis on performance in the VITMEE (VIT Master's Entrance Examination) and the academic qualifications of the candidates. Some students may find it challenging to secure admission to the MCA program at VIT University.\nWorkload: The MCA program at VIT University is quite rigorous, with a lot of coursework and assignments. Some students may find it challenging to cope with the workload and balance other responsibilities.\nLimited research opportunities: VIT University is primarily focused on undergraduate and postgraduate teaching and has limited research opportunities for MCA students compared to some other universities in India.\n\nIt is important to note that these drawbacks may not apply to all students, and some students may find that the benefits of studying at VIT University outweigh the drawbacks. It is recommended that students thoroughly research and evaluate their options before making a decision.\n\nIf it is advisable and informative\n\nplz follow , upvote and share.\n\nThanks",
        "name": "Career Initiative",
        "views": "36 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-drawbacks-of-doing-an-MCA-from-VIT-University",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which is better doing MCA or MBA?",
        "answer": "Both the MBA and the MCA are regarded as prestigious degrees that are relevant in today's corporate world. But generally speaking, an MBA is a better option for candidates who are more likely to hold leadership and management positions, whilst an MCA is more suitable for students who wish to focus on their technical talents. Your MBA qualifies you for some of the top managerial positions inside the organization.\n\nIt can be challenging for students to decide between the MCA and MBA because both have significant demand.\n\n(Hope This Answer will Help You)\nVote it up if you think the response is helpful.\nPlease feel free to ask any questions in a remark.",
        "name": "College Sakha",
        "views": "654 views",
        "link": "https://careerinitiativesspace.quora.com/Can-I-do-an-MCA-from-NIT-after-a-BA-or-a-BSc-in-zoology",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/sikhadawan",
        "author": "u/vivans720",
        "question": "COMPUTER APPLICATION PROGRAMS IN HARYANA",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/sikhadawan/comments/bh8d0s/computer_application_programs_in_haryana/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What is the eligibility for an MCA in SRM?",
        "answer": "Being an Educational Consultant, MCA (Master of Computer Applications) program at SRM Institute of Science and Technology, candidates must meet the following eligibility criteria:\n\nEducational qualification: Candidates must have a Bachelor's degree with a minimum of 50% marks in any discipline from a recognized university. Candidates who have studied Mathematics/Statistics/Computer Science/Computer Applications/Business Mathematics/Business Statistics as a subject in their 10+2 or undergraduate level are preferred.\nEntrance exam: Candidates must have a valid score in the SRM Joint Entrance Examination (SRMJEEE) for MCA or other national level entrance exams such as TANCET, NIMCET, or GATE.\nAge limit: There is no age limit for admission to the MCA program at SRM Institute of Science and Technology.\n\nHope it’s fine, feel free to contact 📲8292699093 (Call/WhatsApp) regarding colleges and admissions.\n\nThank you 😊",
        "name": "Sandesh Kumar",
        "views": "66 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-good-are-the-Impetus-Gurukul-s-MCA-NIMCET-video-content-lectures",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Which is better, MCA or MSc Computer Science from a private college?",
        "answer": "MCA is best from private college.As it offers a greater amount of practical exposure to aspirants, while M.Sc offers more research scope for graduates.\n\n💖 Hope this helps you 💖",
        "name": "Miss᭄𝄞➳⃝ANNU᭄✿ɢɪʟʟ࿐",
        "views": "266 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-better-MCA-or-MSc-Computer-Science-from-a-private-college",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/india",
        "author": "u/Prior-Ad-7898",
        "question": "“Location: Khandwa, Madhya Pradesh A Muslim student, who is doing Masters in Computer Science was talking to a girl about books when a group of extremists took him aside, slapped & brutally thrashed him with canes.“",
        "upvotes": "1.3k",
        "comment": "259",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/india/comments/10fuvfz/location_khandwa_madhya_pradesh_a_muslim_student/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/tuberlin",
        "author": "u/gunjan_mimo",
        "question": "Application for Masters in Computer Science, summer semester",
        "upvotes": "2",
        "comment": "3",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/tuberlin/comments/111yus7/application_for_masters_in_computer_science/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "How much salary will I get after completing my BCA?",
        "answer": "The salary you can expect after completing your BCA (Bachelor of Computer Applications) in India will depend on various factors such as your skills, experience, industry, and location.\n\nOn average, a fresher BCA graduate in India can expect a salary between ₹2,00,000 to ₹4,00,000 per annum. However, if you have excellent coding skills, you could earn more. Additionally, pursuing further education like an MCA (Master of Computer Applications) or certification courses in programming languages like Java, Python, and web development, could increase your earning potential.\n\nThe salary also varies based on the industry you are working in. For example, the IT industry pays higher compared to other industries. The location of your workplace also plays a crucial role in determining your salary.\n\nIf you want to learn Fullstack development then take this course with more then 600000 students with 4.7 rating out of 5.",
        "name": "TechBis",
        "views": "251 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-much-salary-will-I-get-after-completing-my-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is the duration of a BCA after a DCA?",
        "answer": "Hello There ,\n\nIt is three-year undergraduate computer course. BCA curriculum emphasizes learning the fundamentals of computer application and software development.\n\nIf you need any kind of assistance regarding admission feel free to contact through Whatsapp. (Link is in bio)\n\nHappy Learning……",
        "name": "Suraj Late",
        "views": "14 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-duration-of-a-BCA-after-a-DCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which bands came to regret having kicked a member out of the band?",
        "answer": "Beastie Boys regret firing their female drummer from the band.\n\nThe two remaining Beastie Boys members Ad-Rock and Mike D regret letting down women by ditching drummer Kate Schellenbach when they switched from punk music to hip-hop.\n\nThe two, who haven't performed or recorded together since the death of third member Adam 'MCA' Yauch in 2012, started out as a punk four-piece before switching to rap when Kate left the band in 1984, signing to Def Jam and going on to huge success.\n\nAd-Rock, real name Adam Horovitz, tells Britain's The Sunday Times newspaper that he regrets falling out with Kate and letting down women by living up to misogynist caricatures of behaviour in the music industry.\n\n\"We started out as a hardcore punk band, with Kate Schellenbach as our drummer,\" he says. \"We ended up a cartoon rap version of a 1980s metal band and we kicked Kate out. How wrong was that? When the Beastie Boys began, the majority of our friends were girls. It's embarrassing to think we let them down.\"\n\nRedirect Notice\nhttps://www.google.com/amp/s/www.aceshowbiz.com/amp/news/view/00152816.html",
        "name": "Victor Padilla",
        "views": "59.8K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-private-MCA-college-in-India",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Do I opt for CA or BCA+ MCA as the demand of CA will be less in the next 10 years due to the modernization of accounting software?",
        "answer": "If you want to go in computer field then you should pursue BCA and if you are interested in accounts then you should do CA. Actually, CA is a different area of study while BCA is another. If you are good in Commerce than go for CA. Actually, CA is a different area of study while BCA is another.\n\nDepends on your skill and potential. I know, both a CA who earns more than most BCA graduates and a BCA graduate earning more than average CA. If you think you can handle accounts choose CA. If you think you can handle programming and IT then choose BCA. If you are interested in computers and want to make your career in IT industry then go for BCA",
        "name": "IIMT Group Of Colleges",
        "views": "12 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Do-I-opt-for-CA-or-BCA-MCA-as-the-demand-of-CA-will-be-less-in-the-next-10-years-due-to-the-modernization-of-accounting-software",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Should I do MSC in computer science after doing BCA?",
        "answer": "Whether or not you should pursue an MSC in computer science after completing a BCA degree depends on your career goals and interests.\n\nIf you are interested in pursuing a career in the field of computer science, an MSC in computer science can provide you with advanced knowledge and skills that can help you excel in your career. The program can also give you exposure to new technologies and research areas in the field, which can be beneficial for your career growth.\n\nHowever, if you are more interested in pursuing a career in the practical application of computer science, such as software development or web development, it may be more beneficial for you to gain work experience in the field rather than pursuing an MSC. Many employers in the tech industry value hands-on experience and practical skills over academic credentials.\n\nUltimately, the decision to pursue an MSC in computer science after completing a BCA degree should be based on your career goals, interests, and personal circumstances. Consider talking to a career counselor or academic advisor to help you make an informed decision.",
        "name": "Vinay Timothy",
        "views": "36 views",
        "link": "https://codinglanguageshtmlpythoncss.quora.com/Should-I-do-MSC-in-computer-science-after-doing-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/georgetelegraph72",
        "question": "Best Diploma in Computer Application in Kolkata | George Telegraph",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/georgetelegraph72/comments/124i9k6/best_diploma_in_computer_application_in_kolkata/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is your opinion of Lovely Professional University? Do you think it is a good college for an MCA course? How much does it cost to do an MCA there?",
        "answer": "Hello reader,\n\nI hope you are doing well,\n\nLovely Professional University (LPU) is one of India’s largest private universities. It was established in 2005 and is located in Phagwara, Punjab. It is a multi-disciplinary, research-oriented university with a vibrant student community.\n\nThe university offers a wide range of courses in various disciplines including engineering, management, commerce, science, humanities, and information technology. It also offers a range of postgraduate and doctoral programs.\n\nWhen it comes to courses related to computer applications, LPU offers several options. Specifically, it offers an MCA (Master of Computer Applications) program. The program is spread over three years and has a strong emphasis on practical training. The curriculum is designed to give students an in-depth understanding of computer applications and related technologies.\n\nThe university also provides a range of facilities and resources to students. It has a modern library, well-equipped laboratories, and a dedicated IT support team. It also provides Wi-Fi access in all its buildings.\n\nOverall, I believe that LPU is a good college for an MCA course. The university has a good reputation and the curriculum is well-structured and comprehensive. It also provides a range of facilities and resources to students. The MCA program at LPU is also well-regarded and has a good placement record.\n\nIn conclusion, I believe that LPU is a good college for an MCA course. It provides a comprehensive curriculum and a range of facilities and resources to students. It also has a good placement record. Thus, I believe that LPU is a good college for an MCA course.\n\nI hope it helps!\n\nThank you:)",
        "name": "Vidushi Sharma",
        "views": "31 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-your-opinion-of-Lovely-Professional-University-Do-you-think-it-is-a-good-college-for-an-MCA-course-How-much-does-it-cost-to-do-an-MCA-there",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is the best book to prepare for the St. Xavier's College Ranchi MCA entrance exam?",
        "answer": "There is no single \"best book\" for preparing for the St. Xavier's College Ranchi MCA entrance exam as the exam covers various topics in computer science, mathematics, and general aptitude. However, here are some books that can be useful for preparing for the exam:\n\n\"A Modern Approach to Verbal and Non-Verbal Reasoning\" by R.S. Aggarwal - This book covers a wide range of topics related to logical reasoning, which is an essential component of the MCA entrance exam.\n\"Higher Engineering Mathematics\" by B.S. Grewal - This book provides a comprehensive coverage of various mathematical concepts and formulas, which are an important part of the MCA entrance exam syllabus.\n\"Data Structures and Algorithms Made Easy\" by Narasimha Karumanchi - This book covers various data structures and algorithms that are frequently asked in MCA entrance exams.\n\"Computer Science Test Preparation\" by S. L. Gulati - This book covers the syllabus for various computer science entrance exams, including the St. Xavier's College Ranchi MCA entrance exam.\n\"General Knowledge 2021\" by Manohar Pandey - This book can be helpful for preparing for the general aptitude section of the MCA entrance exam.\n\nIt's important to note that while these books can be useful for exam preparation, it's also crucial to practice solving previous years' question papers and mock tests to get a better idea of the exam pattern and difficulty level",
        "name": "Ahsan Technical",
        "views": "19 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-book-to-prepare-for-the-St-Xaviers-College-Ranchi-MCA-entrance-exam",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is the current number of people employed in MCA jobs in India?",
        "answer": "according to a report by NASSCOM (National Association of Software and Services Companies) and Zinnov, the IT industry in India employed around 4.47 million professionals in 2020, with approximately 2.5 million employed in the software services sector. While the report did not provide specific figures for MCA jobs, it is safe to assume that a significant portion of these professionals hold degrees or have expertise in computer applications and related fields. It is also worth noting that the IT industry in India continues to grow rapidly, with a projected revenue of $194 billion in 2021, and is expected to create more employment opportunities in the future.",
        "name": "Eduxprts",
        "views": "13 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-current-number-of-people-employed-in-MCA-jobs-in-India",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/rwth",
        "author": "u/getadmision",
        "question": "Application to the winter semester 2023 of the Computer Engineering Bachelor Open Course",
        "upvotes": "2",
        "comment": "5",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/rwth/comments/1133t80/application_to_the_winter_semester_2023_of_the/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the differences between an MCA and a BCA from VIT?",
        "answer": "Hello Aspirant,\n\nMCA (Master of Computer Applications) and BCA (Bachelor of Computer Applications) are both computer science programs offered at VIT University, but there are some significant differences between the two degrees. Here are a few key differences between the two:\n\nLevel of study: BCA is an undergraduate program, while MCA is a postgraduate program. This means that MCA is a more advanced degree and requires more in-depth study and specialization.\nDuration: BCA is typically a three-year program, while MCA is a two-year program. However, some universities may offer a four-year integrated MCA program.\nCurriculum: BCA focuses on building a strong foundation in computer science and programming fundamentals, while MCA is more specialized and focuses on advanced topics such as software engineering, database management, and advanced programming languages.\nJob opportunities: MCA is a more specialized degree and may open up more job opportunities in areas such as software development, database administration, and systems analysis. BCA graduates may find entry-level positions in software development, web development, and IT support.\nSalary potential: In general, MCA graduates may earn a higher salary than BCA graduates due to their advanced degree and specialized knowledge.\nEligibility: To pursue a BCA degree at VIT University, a student must have completed 10+2 with Mathematics or Business Mathematics as one of the subjects. For MCA, a student must have completed a Bachelor's degree in any discipline with Mathematics as one of the subjects in 10+2 or at the undergraduate level.\n\nOverall, both BCA and MCA can be great options for students interested in computer science and information technology. The choice between the two will depend on the student's academic background, career goals, and personal interests.\n\nIf it is advisable and informative\n\nplz follow , upvote and share.\n\nThanks",
        "name": "Career Initiative",
        "views": "47 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-differences-between-an-MCA-and-a-BCA-from-VIT",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/TGBSMBA",
        "author": "u/TGBSMBA",
        "question": "Best master of computer application colleges in mumbai | Top MCA College",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/TGBSMBA/comments/yehyj6/best_master_of_computer_application_colleges_in/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What are the best private universities for an MCA in Delhi NCR?",
        "answer": "The top colleges in Delhi NCR offering Masters in Computer Applications degree:\n\n1. World College of Technology and Management (WCTM), Gurugram\n\n2. Institute of Management studies (IMS), Noida\n\n3. Lingaya’s Vidyapeeth, Haryana\n\n4. Manav Rachna International Institute of Research and Studies (MRIIRS), Faridabad\n\n5. RC Institute of Technology (RCIT), New Delhi\n\n6. KR Mangalam University of Information and Technology, Gurgaon\n\n7. Institute of Professional Excellence and Management (IPEM), Ghaziabad\n\n8. JSS Academy of Technical Education (JSSATE), Noida\n\n9. ATM Global Business School, Faridabad\n\n10. Galgotias University, Greater Noida\n\nMCA is a two-year course that gives comprehensive knowledge about the world of computers, technology, and its applications. It comprises of subjects such as networking, data structure, core programming languages, etc. with an extended curriculum.\n\nOut of these bunch of top colleges offer the MCA degree in Delhi, NCR the college that tops my list is the World College of Technology and Management (WCTM), Gurugram.\n\nI recommend you WCTM because this college checks off not one, but multiple boxes for being the best college for doing an MCA in Delhi NCR.\n\nWCTM has an excellent placement record of outgoing batch by 100 plus companies ORACLE, IBM, HCL, L&T, WIPRO, DELHI-METRO, and many more.\n\nThe students get an opportunity to go on many industry visits that not only stimulates their curiosity but also boosts their confidence.\n\nThe college has an aesthetically designed state-of-art infrastructure in 18 acres lush green campus.\n\nWCTM has received:\n\n· The best IT innovation and excellence award.\n\n· Best emerging technical institute for providing holistic education.\n\n· IT Silver Jubilee award from Capital Foundation.\n\nThis is the most apt college for pursing your MCA.\n\nClick on the link for more information- Best engineering college in Gurgaon | Best engineering college in Delhi NCR | WCTM",
        "name": "Neelam Singh",
        "views": "391 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-some-best-private-college-for-MCA-in-Delhi",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "How is Sinhgad College in Pune for an MCA?",
        "answer": "Hey,\n\nSinhgad college is most reputed private universities in Pune, Maharashtra. Sinhgad Institute of Management and Computer Application (SIMCA) in Pune is one of the top 25 MCA institutes in India and top 5 in Pune. Sinhgad College in Pune is well-known for its MCA program. It is a popular destination for students who want to pursue a Master of Computer Applications degree. The Master of Computer Application Program has been running since 1996 under the umbrella of Sinhgad Technical Education Society . institute is affiliated with the University of Pune and managed by the Sinhgad Technical Education Society (STES). It has been approved by AICTE, recognized by the Government of Maharashtra, and accredited by the National Board of Accreditation, New Delhi.\n\nSinhgad College has a strong faculty with expertise in a wide range of topics related to computer science and applications. The college also offers state-of-the-art infrastructure, including well-equipped computer labs and a large library.\n\nIn addition, Sinhgad College has a good track record of placements for MCA graduates. Many leading companies in the IT industry regularly visit the college like Infosys, TCS, Accenture, Deloitte, Tech Mahindra, ICICI Bank,,,,,. to recruit students for various positions. The average package starts from 7–9 lakh and the highest package offered was around Rs. 15 lakhs per annum.\n\nHope it helps.\n\nFor more queries feel free to contact 📞6205238449 Call/WhatsApp provide free counseling to students and parents in India regarding College, admission, placement, fees structure of any college in India.\n\nThank You",
        "name": "Anjali Mishra",
        "views": "61 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-is-Sinhgad-College-in-Pune-for-an-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/learnmachinelearning",
        "author": "u/RauhanSheikh",
        "question": "I have a bachelor's in computer application and I want to do masters in AI/ML/DS. so, what are the best universities in Germany for that?",
        "upvotes": "3",
        "comment": "9",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/learnmachinelearning/comments/whechj/i_have_a_bachelors_in_computer_application_and_i/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/MSCS",
        "author": "u/CuriousDepartureOne",
        "question": "Which university is best for a master's degree in computer science, and why?",
        "upvotes": "4",
        "comment": "12",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/MSCS/comments/12bexgv/which_university_is_best_for_a_masters_degree_in/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Indian_Academia",
        "author": "u/sickboi33",
        "question": "Is BCA(Bachelor's in Computer Application) a good course after 12th?",
        "upvotes": "17",
        "comment": "25",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Indian_Academia/comments/enocl3/is_bcabachelors_in_computer_application_a_good/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/getadmision",
        "author": "u/uidmudaipur",
        "question": "Importance of BCA in today’s life…",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/getadmision/comments/u2kv0r/importance_of_bca_in_todays_life/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Is an MCA in SRM University worth it (to join 2023-2024)?",
        "answer": "The value of an MCA degree from SRM University or any other institution ultimately depends on a variety of factors, such as the quality of the program, the reputation of the university, the faculty, the curriculum, and the career prospects for graduates.\n\nSRM University is a well-regarded institution in India, with a strong focus on technology and innovation. Its MCA program is designed to provide students with a comprehensive understanding of computer applications, software development, and other related topics.\n\nHowever, before deciding to pursue an MCA degree at SRM University, it may be helpful to research the program thoroughly and consider factors such as the cost of tuition, the availability of financial aid or scholarships, and the specific courses and opportunities offered within the program. It may also be helpful to speak with current or former students in the program, as well as faculty members, to gain a better understanding of the program's strengths and weaknesses.\n\nUltimately, the decision to pursue an MCA degree at SRM University or any other institution should be based on a careful evaluation of your own academic and career goals, as well as your financial and personal circumstances. It may be helpful to speak with academic advisors, career counselors, and other professionals to help you make informed decisions about your education and career.",
        "name": "Krishna Kumar",
        "views": "28 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-an-MCA-in-SRM-University-worth-it-to-join-2023-2024",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/Edubuild",
        "author": "u/Edubuild",
        "question": "Online Master of Computer Applications | MCA Degree",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/Edubuild/comments/11x7l5k/online_master_of_computer_applications_mca_degree/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/getadmision",
        "author": "u/Harild123",
        "question": "Importance of BCA in the digital world",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/getadmision/comments/u8kjbt/importance_of_bca_in_the_digital_world/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/ITCareerQuestions",
        "author": "u/No-Ice-8632",
        "question": "Switching Careers to IT security at 34",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "11",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/ITCareerQuestions/comments/y645y0/switching_careers_to_it_security_at_34/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Which is better doing MCA or MBA?",
        "answer": "Deciding between pursuing an MCA (Master of Computer Applications) or an MBA (Master of Business Administration) depends on your academic and career goals.\n\nAn MCA degree is typically focused on developing advanced technical skills in computer applications and software development. Graduates with an MCA degree may find employment as software developers, system analysts, and other related roles in the IT industry. MCA graduates are well-prepared for technical roles that require strong programming skills, analytical thinking, and problem-solving abilities.\n\nOn the other hand, an MBA degree is designed to provide students with a broad understanding of business administration, including topics such as finance, marketing, human resources, and operations management. Graduates with an MBA degree may find employment in a variety of industries, including consulting, finance, marketing, and management. MBA graduates are typically well-suited for roles that require strong leadership, communication, and strategic thinking skills.\n\nUltimately, the decision between pursuing an MCA or an MBA should be based on your personal interests, career goals, and strengths. If you are passionate about computer applications and have a strong technical background, an MCA may be the better choice for you. If you are interested in business administration and have strong leadership and communication skills, an MBA may be a better fit. It may also be possible to combine the two degrees through a dual-degree program, depending on the options available at your chosen institution.",
        "name": "Eduxprts",
        "views": "7 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-better-doing-MCA-or-MBA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Indian_Academia",
        "author": "u/Broad-Worldliness7",
        "question": "Can I go for a master's in computer applications when I have a bachelor in arts?",
        "upvotes": "12",
        "comment": "3",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Indian_Academia/comments/vo7qbh/can_i_go_for_a_masters_in_computer_applications/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/Longjumping_Box_2039",
        "author": "u/Longjumping_Box_2039",
        "question": "Just finished a demo reel for a computer graphics master's program application",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/Longjumping_Box_2039/comments/10rdib4/just_finished_a_demo_reel_for_a_computer_graphics/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "twitter",
        "name": "chalocampus",
        "handle": "@chalocampus",
        "timestamp": "Jun 16, 2009",
        "text": "ASN DEGREE COLLEGE TENALI BCA ADMISSIONS&#8217;09: Bachelor Degree(BCA)2009 Admissions in Computer Application a.. http://tinyurl.com/kqeozc",
        "link": "https://twitter.com/chalocampus/status/2190290752",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "I am planning to take a BCA at VIT Vellore. How much do I need to score, and is it worth it to take BCA there?",
        "answer": "The stated eligibility criteria is 60 percent. The seats are generally less for BCA and other 3 year programs, though it has been increasing every year. It is every penny worth to do your BCA in VIT Vellore.\n\nThe highest package among all three year course was bagged from BCA. 25 lac from D.E Shaw last year.",
        "name": "Pradyumn Niroula",
        "views": "77 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/I-am-planning-to-take-a-BCA-at-VIT-Vellore-How-much-do-I-need-to-score-and-is-it-worth-it-to-take-BCA-there",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/mumbai",
        "author": "u/Harsh00077",
        "question": "College for masters",
        "upvotes": "3",
        "comment": "1",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/mumbai/comments/yv8q2r/college_for_masters/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "How do I do an MCA in VFX and animations? Currently, I am doing a BCA.",
        "answer": "If you want to make a career in VFX and animation, then doing an MCA is the right choice. An MCA will give you in-depth knowledge about these fields and help you build a strong foundation for your career. You can do an MCA from any reputed college or university. However, it is important to do some research before making your final decision.\n\nSome of the best colleges for doing an MCA in VFX and animation are Pune University, Mumbai University, and Andhra University. These colleges offer excellent courses that will help you hone your skills and become a proficient VFX and animation professional. After completing your MCA, you can find jobs in various production houses, studios, or advertising agencies.\n\nIf you want to become an Animator, you could refer to this Ultimate Guide on how to become an animator.",
        "name": "Nikhil Ray",
        "views": "90 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/My-brother-and-I-plan-to-start-a-clothing-company-in-my-mother-s-name-What-is-the-process-for-applying-for-a-name",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which college I should join for a B.C.A in Delhi NCR?",
        "answer": "Thanks for A2A\n\nBachelors in Computer Application, also known as BCA is a full-time three-year undergraduate program that focuses on providing the students with required knowledge and necessary skills to get rewarding careers into the changing world of Information Technology. BCA is one of the most popular options to get the career started in the field of IT.\n\nAre you looking for a college that fulfils all your parameters for being the best suitable college to pursue a BCA degree?\n\nWell, we’re here with our recommendation for you. You’ll come across a list of the best college for doing a BCA in Delhi NCR followed by our recommendation from a personal point of view. Keep reading!\n\nHere’s a list of some of the best colleges offering a BCA in Delhi NCR:\n\nWorld college of Technology and Management (WCTM), Gurugram\nGuru Gobind Singh Indraprastha university (GGSIPU)\nVivekanand Institute of Professional Studies (VIPS), New Delhi\nDelhi Skill and entrepreneurship university (DSEU)\nIndra Gandhi National Open University, New Delhi\nBaba Sahib Ambedkar Technical Education Society (BSAITM), Delhi\nInstitute of Information Technology and Management, Delhi\nBrij Mohan Institute of Management (BIMT), Gurugram\nSchool of Engineering and Technology, Gurugram\nAmity University, Gurugram\n\nOut of all these colleges/ Universities, I would suggest you the World college of Technology and Management (WCTM) as the best option because this college undoubtedly checks off all the boxes, from infrastructure to exposure, affordability to top-notch placements, and everything in between.\n\nWhat gives this institute a cut above the rest?\n\nPlacement record- WCTM has an impeccable placement record.\nExperience faculty- Most of the WCTM faculty members are experienced teachers from Indian B-schools.\nPedagogy – WCTM offers an interactive-digital pedagogy for your three-year course\n24x7 support- The WhatsApp support groups available for the students 24 x 7.\nExposure- The college offers internships, workshops, seminars, and other morale boosting competitions every now and then.\nInfrastructure- WCTM has a world class, aesthetically designed infrastructure in an 18-acre lush green campus.\n\nFor more information, visit- Best engineering college in Gurgaon | Best engineering college in Delhi NCR | WCTM",
        "name": "Chinar Kashyap",
        "views": "605 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-college-I-should-join-for-a-B-C-A-in-Delhi-NCR",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Can MCA graduates work abroad?",
        "answer": "Yes, MCA graduates can work abroad, and there are several opportunities available for them in various countries. The demand for skilled IT professionals is high in many countries, and MCA graduates are highly valued for their knowledge and expertise in the field of computer applications.\n\nThe following are some of the countries where MCA graduates can work:\n\nUnited States: The United States is one of the most popular destinations for IT professionals, and there are numerous job opportunities available for MCA graduates. The country is home to some of the largest IT companies in the world, including Microsoft, Apple, Google, and Amazon. MCA graduates can work as software developers, database administrators, systems analysts, project managers, and other related roles.\nCanada: Canada is another popular destination for IT professionals, and there is a high demand for skilled workers in the field. The country has a strong economy and a stable job market, and MCA graduates can work in various industries, including healthcare, finance, and education. Some of the top IT companies in Canada include CGI, IBM, and Accenture.\nAustralia: Australia is a country that offers excellent job opportunities for IT professionals, and there is a high demand for skilled workers in the field. The country has a robust economy and a growing IT industry, and MCA graduates can work in various roles, including software development, web development, and systems analysis. Some of the top IT companies in Australia include Atlassian, WiseTech Global, and Canva.\nUnited Kingdom: The United Kingdom is a popular destination for IT professionals, and there are numerous job opportunities available for MCA graduates. The country has a diverse economy and a thriving IT industry, and MCA graduates can work in various roles, including software development, database administration, and project management. Some of the top IT companies in the UK include IBM, Accenture, and Capgemini.\nGermany: Germany is a country that offers excellent job opportunities for IT professionals, and there is a high demand for skilled workers in the field. The country has a strong economy and a growing IT industry, and MCA graduates can work in various roles, including software development, data analysis, and cybersecurity. Some of the top IT companies in Germany include SAP, Deutsche Telekom, and Siemens.\nSingapore: Singapore is a country that offers excellent job opportunities for IT professionals, and there is a high demand for skilled workers in the field. The country has a thriving IT industry and a strong economy, and MCA graduates can work in various roles, including software development, project management, and systems analysis. Some of the top IT companies in Singapore include Google, Microsoft, and IBM.\n\nTo work abroad as an MCA graduate, candidates may need to fulfill certain requirements, such as obtaining a work visa or work permit. The eligibility criteria for work visas may vary from country to country, and candidates may need to meet certain educational and language proficiency requirements.\n\nIn addition to work visas, candidates may also need to have relevant work experience, certifications, and knowledge of specific programming languages and technologies. It is also important to have a good understanding of the local culture and work practices to succeed in a foreign work environment.\n\nConclusion:\n\nIn conclusion, MCA graduates can work abroad and there are several opportunities available for them in various countries. The demand for skilled IT professionals is high in many countries, and MCA graduates are highly valued for their knowledge and expertise in the field of computer applications. To work abroad, candidates may need to fulfill certain requirements, such as obtaining a work visa or work permit, and they may also need to have relevant work experience and certifications. With the right skills, experience, and qualifications, MCA graduates can have a successful career in the global IT industry.",
        "name": "Aniket Sharma",
        "views": "9 views",
        "link": "https://collegeforum.quora.com/Can-MCA-graduates-work-abroad",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "I am planning of doing BCA then an MBA. Should I do a MCA as well?",
        "answer": "No, after doing mba, mca is not worth of. Either you can opt for mba Or mca as both are master level degree. If you are interested in management then go for mba. If you like coding you can choose mca. After completing your graduation degree you can decide it based upon your interest. For pursuing mca it is necessary for you to be good in maths and have a bachelor degree in maths or computer science.",
        "name": "Annu Kumari",
        "views": "14 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/I-am-planning-of-doing-BCA-then-an-MBA-Should-I-do-a-MCA-as-well",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Can I get admission in LPU for an MCA hons. course after failing in the LPUNEST?",
        "answer": "Hello reader,\n\nI hope you are doing well,\n\nLovely Professional University (LPU) has its admission test known as the LPUNEST for various undergraduate and postgraduate programs, including the MCA hons. course. If a candidate fails to secure the minimum required marks in the LPUNEST, they may not be eligible for admission to the MCA hons. the course at LPU. However, there may be alternative admission procedures available that the candidate can explore.\n\nOne option is to try and secure admission through the management quota, which allows candidates to gain admission to a program based on their academic records or other qualifications. However, the availability of seats under the management quota and the eligibility criteria may vary from year to year and may be subject to change.\n\nAnother option is to explore other universities that offer similar programs and have different admission procedures. The candidate can research and apply to these universities to pursue their MCA hons. course.\n\nIn any case, it is important to note that failing to secure the required marks in the LPUNEST does not necessarily mean that the candidate is not capable of pursuing the MCA hons. course. They can try other options and work hard to achieve their goals.\n\nI hope it helps!\n\nThank you:)",
        "name": "Vidushi Sharma",
        "views": "24 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-get-admission-in-LPU-for-an-MCA-hons-course-after-failing-in-the-LPUNEST",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "My grandma suffered an MCA stroke, now she is on the bed and can do nothing on her own except that she keeps growling and is pushing herself to the right. What does it mean?",
        "answer": "So sorry to hear that. It means she has aphasia or difficulty speaking and motor weakness. For you to read:\n\n“As described previously, MCA strokes typically present with the symptoms individuals associate most commonly with strokes, such as unilateral weakness and/or numbness, facial droop, and speech deficits ranging from mild dysarthria and mild aphasia to global aphasia.Feb 7, 2023”\n\nMiddle Cerebral Artery Stroke\n\nMiddle Cerebral Artery Stroke\nContinuing Education Activity The middle cerebral artery (MCA) is the most common artery involved in acute stroke. It branches directly from the internal carotid artery and consists of four main branches, M1, M2, M3, and M4. These vessels provide blood supply to parts of the frontal, temporal, and parietal lobes of the brain, as well as deeper structures including the caudate, internal capsule, and thalamus. This activity describes the presentation, evaluation, and management of middle cerebral artery strokes, and explains the role of the members of the interprofessional team in assessing, diagnosing, managing, and rehabilitating patients who suffer from this, and how to try to prevent a recurrence. Objectives: Identify the various potential etiologies of middle cerebral artery stroke. Summarize the most important evaluations needed to diagnose a middle cerebral artery stroke. Outline the differential diagnoses that must be considered if a patient presents with stroke-like symptoms but does not have a stroke. Review how to address the modifiable risk factors for secondary stroke prevention after a stroke, and how the interprofessional team can be involved in improving the outcome and quality of life of a stroke patient. Access free multiple choice questions on this topic. Introduction The middle cerebral artery (MCA) is the most common artery involved in acute stroke. It branches directly from the internal carotid artery and consists of four main branches, M1, M2, M3, and M4. These vessels provide blood supply to parts of the frontal, temporal, and parietal lobes of the brain, as well as deeper structures, including the caudate, internal capsule, and thalamus. Its vast supply means that strokes involving the MCA territory can have a multitude of presenting symptoms, depending on which branches and structures are affected. [1] Etiology There are multiple risk factors for strokes, which can be divided into modifiable and nonmodifiable categories—many of the causes of hemorrhagic and ischemic stroke overlap. The nonmodifiable risk factors of each include age, sex, race, and genetics. The risk increases as you get older; the risk is higher in men at a younger age, but the risk of death is higher overall in women; and the risk is significantly greater in African Americans, and slightly higher in Hispanics and Native Americans as well, compared to whites. Modifiable risk factors, including hypertension, smoking, obesity, alcohol consumption, and diet all contribute to both ischemic and hemorrhagic stroke. However, hyperlipidemia, physical inactivity, diabetes, and cardiac causes such as cardiomyopathy, heart failure, and atrial fibrillation, are risk factors for ischemic stroke but not hemorrhagic stroke. The etiology of hemorrhagic stroke is most frequently hypertension, especially in developing countries where the burden of hypertension is unknown due to infrequent screening and diagnosis. Less frequently, hemorrhagic strokes can also be due to angio\nhttps://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK556132/#:~:text=As%20described%20previously%2C%20MCA%20strokes,mild%20aphasia%20to%20global%20aphasia.\n\n“What is the most common cause of MCA stroke?\n\nMCA strokes are generally caused by a blood clot that travels from outside the brain. Typically, it's from the heart or carotid artery. Then the clot gets lodged in the MCA and blocks blood flow. This is called an embolic stroke.Oct 14, 2022″\n\nCould You Recognize the Symptoms of a Middle Cerebral Artery Stroke?\nLearn about the symptoms, causes, and effects of middle cerebral artery (MCA) strokes, a well-identified type of stroke.\nhttps://www.verywellhealth.com/middle-cerebral-artery-stroke-3146460#:~:text=MCA%20strokes%20are%20generally%20caused,is%20called%20an%20embolic%20stroke.",
        "name": "Maria Pugliese",
        "views": "18 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/My-grandma-suffered-an-MCA-stroke-now-she-is-on-the-bed-and-can-do-nothing-on-her-own-except-that-she-keeps-growling-and-is-pushing-herself-to-the-right-What-does-it-mean",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "twitter",
        "name": "sunil joshi",
        "handle": "@sunjoshi1969",
        "timestamp": "Oct 9, 2009",
        "text": "Finished one training session with bachelors in computer application students on management",
        "link": "https://twitter.com/sunjoshi1969/status/4728974769",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "How should I prepare for JNU MCA entrance exam?",
        "answer": "There is no one-size-fits-all answer to this question, as the best way to prepare for the JNU MCA entrance exam will vary depending on your individual strengths and weaknesses.\n\nHowever, some general tips that may be helpful include:1.\n\nFamiliarize yourself with the syllabus and exam format: Make sure you are aware of what topics will be covered on the exam, and familiarize yourself with the multiple choice/fill in the blank/essay format of questions that will likely be used.2.\n\nPractice, practice, practice: In addition to becoming familiar with the material, it is also important to get comfortable with answering questions under time pressure.\n\nOne way to do this is by taking practice exams under timed conditions.3.\n\nUnderstand your own learning style: Some students learn best by listening to audio recordings or watching videos, while others prefer reading texts or working through practice problems.\n\nFind a study method that works better for you and stick to it!",
        "name": "Vincent S. Drake",
        "views": "246 views",
        "link": "https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/0010880401424001",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Concordia",
        "author": "u/boredndconfused",
        "question": "Prospective application for Masters in Computer Science",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Concordia/comments/x7i6ze/prospective_application_for_masters_in_computer/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the benefits of pursuing a B.Tech (ECE) or MCA at NIT Kurukshetra?",
        "answer": "Hello Aspirant,\n\nNIT Kurukshetra (National Institute of Technology Kurukshetra) is a highly respected technical institute in India, and pursuing a B.Tech (ECE) or MCA degree from NIT Kurukshetra can offer several benefits, some of which are listed below:\n\nBenefits of pursuing B.Tech (ECE) at NIT Kurukshetra:\n\nStrong industry connections: NIT Kurukshetra has established strong ties with leading industries and research organizations, which can provide students with opportunities to gain real-world experience, internships, and job placements.\nQuality education: The B.Tech (ECE) program at NIT Kurukshetra offers a comprehensive curriculum that covers various aspects of electronics and communication engineering, including advanced topics such as VLSI, embedded systems, and wireless communication.\nResearch opportunities: NIT Kurukshetra is well-equipped with advanced research facilities, and students pursuing B.Tech (ECE) can participate in cutting-edge research projects under the guidance of experienced faculty members.\n\nBenefits of pursuing MCA at NIT Kurukshetra:\n\nGood job prospects: NIT Kurukshetra has a strong reputation in the industry, and many leading companies actively recruit MCA graduates from the institute.\nIndustry-oriented curriculum: The MCA program at NIT Kurukshetra is designed to provide students with the knowledge and skills required to succeed in the rapidly evolving IT industry, and the curriculum is regularly updated to reflect the latest trends and technologies.\nResearch opportunities: NIT Kurukshetra has a vibrant research community, and MCA students can participate in research projects and work on cutting-edge technologies under the guidance of experienced faculty members.\nStrong alumni network: NIT Kurukshetra has a large and active alumni network, which can provide students with valuable guidance, mentorship, and networking opportunities.\n\nIf it is advisable and informative\n\nplz follow , upvote and share.\n\nThanks",
        "name": "Career Initiative",
        "views": "41 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-benefits-of-pursuing-a-B-Tech-ECE-or-MCA-at-NIT-Kurukshetra",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What are the career prospects for an MCA graduate from UPES, Dehradun?",
        "answer": "UPES provides professional MCA courses with a well-rounded curriculum designed specifically for students of MCA. After the successful completion of MCA from UPES, students can make a successful career as a software developer, database engineer, data scientist, cloud architect, web designer, web developer and even technical writer.",
        "name": "Niharika Kapoor",
        "views": "90 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-true-that-MCA-has-very-low-value-compared-to-MBA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Can MCA graduates pursue research?",
        "answer": "MCA graduates can pursue research opportunities in various areas of computer science and applications. Research in computer science is a highly dynamic field that involves discovering and creating new technologies, algorithms, and programming paradigms. MCA graduates can contribute to this field through research in areas such as artificial intelligence, machine learning, data analytics, computer networks, software engineering, and cybersecurity.\n\nResearch in artificial intelligence and machine learning involves developing intelligent algorithms and systems that can learn and adapt to new situations. MCA graduates with a background in computer science, mathematics, and statistics can contribute to this field by designing and implementing new machine learning algorithms, developing natural language processing systems, and exploring applications of AI in various domains such as healthcare, finance, and education.\n\nData analytics is another area where MCA graduates can contribute through research. Data analytics involves extracting insights and knowledge from large datasets using statistical and machine learning techniques. MCA graduates can apply data analytics to various domains such as marketing, finance, and healthcare to discover patterns, trends, and relationships that can help in decision-making.\n\nIn computer networks, MCA graduates can research new protocols and technologies that can improve the performance, security, and reliability of communication systems. They can also study the impact of emerging technologies such as 5G, IoT, and cloud computing on network design and management.\n\nSoftware engineering is another area where MCA graduates can pursue research. Software engineering involves designing and developing high-quality software systems that are scalable, maintainable, and reliable. MCA graduates can research new software engineering methodologies, programming languages, and development tools that can help in creating better software systems.\n\nCybersecurity is a growing concern in today's world, and MCA graduates can contribute to this field through research. Cybersecurity involves protecting computer systems, networks, and data from cyber-attacks and threats. MCA graduates can research new cybersecurity technologies, tools, and methodologies that can improve the security of computer systems and networks.\n\nApart from these areas, MCA graduates can also pursue research in other fields such as computer vision, game development, natural language processing, and robotics. The research opportunities for MCA graduates are numerous and diverse, and they can choose the area that interests them the most.\n\nTo pursue research in computer science, MCA graduates can opt for higher studies such as a Ph.D. in Computer Science or a related field. A Ph.D. in Computer Science involves conducting original research under the guidance of a research supervisor and submitting a thesis based on the research findings. MCA graduates can apply for PhDPh.D. programs in reputed universities in India and abroad. Some of the top universities for Ph.D. in Computer Science include Carnegie Mellon University, Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Stanford University, University of California Berkeley, and Indian Institute of Technology (IIT) Delhi.\n\nApart from Ph.D., MCA graduates can also participate in research projects and internships during their MCA program. Many universities offer research internships to MCA students where they can work on ongoing research projects under the guidance of a research supervisor. This can provide MCA graduates with hands-on experience in research and prepare them for higher studies or research careers.\n\nIn conclusion, MCA graduates can pursue research opportunities in various areas of computer science and applications. Research in computer science is a highly dynamic and exciting field that involves discovering and creating new technologies that can shape the future of the industry. MCA graduates can apply their programming and analytical skills to conduct research in areas such as artificial intelligence, machine learning, data analytics, computer networks, software engineering, and cybersecurity. Pursuing research in computer science can open up new career opportunities and provide MCA graduates with a deeper understanding of the field.",
        "name": "Aniket Sharma",
        "views": "8 views",
        "link": "https://collegeforum.quora.com/Can-MCA-graduates-pursue-research",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "How good is Lovely Professional University for an MCA?",
        "answer": "Hello readers, Lovely Professional University is a private university located in Jalandhar, Punjab, India. It is one of the largest universities in India, with over 30,000 students enrolled in its various programs. LPU offers a Master of Computer Applications (MCA), which is a three-year program designed to prepare students for careers in the field of computer applications.\n\nThe MCA program at LPU covers a wide range of topics related to computer applications, including programming languages, software engineering, database management, and computer networking. The program is designed to provide students with the knowledge and skills they need to become successful professionals in the field of computer applications.\n\nLPU has a good reputation for its academic programs, and its MCA program is no exception. The university has a strong faculty with expertise in the field of computer applications, and the program is designed to be practical and hands-on, with opportunities for students to gain real-world experience through internships and other experiential learning opportunities.\n\nOverall, Lovely Professional University is a good choice for an MCA, particularly for students who are interested in pursuing careers in the field of computer applications in India.\n\nHope this helps!!",
        "name": "Vidushi Sharma",
        "views": "10 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-good-is-Lovely-Professional-University-for-an-MCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/getadmision",
        "author": "u/Temporary-Shift-6160",
        "question": "Why BCA become Important in Today’s Life…",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/getadmision/comments/yxi36h/why_bca_become_important_in_todays_life/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What are the career options after earning a Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA)?",
        "answer": "A Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) degree can lead to a variety of careers in the computer field.\n\nSome common career options include software development, systems analysis, network administration, and web design.\n\nWith experience and additional training, many BCA graduates also find work as IT managers or project managers.",
        "name": "Kelly Freddie",
        "views": "716 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-options-after-earning-a-Bachelor-of-Computer-Applications-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What should I do if I have a Capgemini job (2 years bond), or should I go for an MCA?",
        "answer": "I had gone through with this phase I can give you my experience insights which help you to decide what To do.\n\nI have done full-time MCA and now I feel I wasted my 3 years of life. Whatever I achieved now it might have been achieved after my graduation, there is no need of masters at the end of the day graduate and pg both get the same role while starting career .But MCA guy gets 3 year behind with other colleagues in the professional career . Time is money don't waste it if we can get the same job after graduation why would we need to do pg. Instead I will suggest do some specialization in one tech give 1 year to it build something using that tech. That will help you in career rather just doing PG . Please think wisely MCA will not add any value to your career.\n\nP.S: Its my personal experience and openion.",
        "name": "Ali Bin Mazi",
        "views": "2K views",
        "link": "https://businesstech.co.za/news/finance/576512/what-it-takes-to-be-middle-class-in-south-africa-right-now/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Will it be difficult to do an MCA after a BA?",
        "answer": "It depends on what you mean by MCA and your background knowledge and skills. MCA could refer to a Master of Computer Applications, which is a postgraduate degree program in India that focuses on computer science and applications, or it could refer to something else depending on your context.\n\nIf you are referring to the Master of Computer Applications program in India, then it is generally not difficult to pursue this degree after completing a Bachelor of Arts (BA) degree. However, you may need to fulfill certain requirements or prerequisites, such as having a strong background in mathematics, computer science, or related fields. You may also need to clear an entrance exam or meet other eligibility criteria to qualify for admission to an MCA program.\n\nIf you do not have a strong background in mathematics or computer science, you may find the MCA program challenging. However, with hard work and dedication, it is certainly possible to succeed and excel in the program.\n\nOverall, pursuing an MCA after a BA degree may require some effort and preparation, but it is not inherently difficult. It ultimately depends on your background knowledge, skills, and willingness to learn and work hard.",
        "name": "Zaid Khan",
        "views": "12 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Will-it-be-difficult-to-do-an-MCA-after-a-BA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Is it possible to get good packages from service-based companies like TCS and Infosys?",
        "answer": "There is a common perception among people that service-based companies do not pay their employees well enough and, to some extent, this claim is true. I mean, if you see the starting salary offered to freshers by these companies, it is one of the lowest in the IT industry in India. Cognizant and Accenture pay 4.5 LPA, Infosys pays 4 LPA to a fresher while the rest pay around 3.5 to 3.8 LPA. TCS pays the lowest at 3.36 LPA. The above salary figures are those of BTech graduates, however. It is even low for BCA, BSc and BCom graduates in BPOs.\n\nTo make things worse, the salary hikes are also one of the lowest in the IT industry in service-based companies. This includes companies like Wipro, Infosys, TCS, Cognizant, HCL (famously known as WITCH), Capgemini, Accenture and a few others. Hikes range between 2% to 5% in most cases and, if you are very lucky, upto 8%, barely beating inflation.\n\nBut if you switch jobs, the equation changes completely. These companies treat existing employees this way but offer good packages to lateral employees joining their company. I have a friend who worked in TCS for three years where his last package was 4.2 LPA and he switched to Infosys with a 17 LPA package. I have another friend who switched from TCS with a package of 4 LPA after two years of experience and joined Wipro at a package of 15 LPA plus got a joining bonus separately.\n\nSo, yes, it is definitely possible to get good packages in the service-based sector, but you have to switch jobs for that. And one not only needs good knowledge and skill set for that but has to work in a niche technology which has a good demand in the market to justify the high salary.",
        "name": "Shaunak Bhattacharjeee",
        "views": "45.2K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-possible-to-get-good-packages-from-service-based-companies-like-TCS-and-Infosys",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What is the highest package you can get as an MCA student from Lovely Professional University (LPU)?",
        "answer": "Hello reader,\n\nI hope you are doing well,\n\nThe Lovely Professional University (LPU) is a private university located in Jalandhar, Punjab, India. It has been ranked among the best universities in the country. It offers a wide range of courses in the field of Engineering, Management, Law, Architecture, and Design. MCA is one of the most popular and sought-after courses offered by LPU. It is a three-year full-time post-graduate course, which provides students with the skills and knowledge necessary to pursue a career in the field of information technology.\n\nThe highest package available to an MCA student from LPU is usually in the range of 8-15 lakhs per annum. This is the highest package that is generally offered to an MCA student from LPU. This package includes salary, bonus, and other benefits.\n\nThe salary of an MCA student from LPU depends on his/her qualifications and experience. The average salary for MCA students from LPU is around 4-6 lakhs per annum. The salary also depends upon the company he/she is working for. MCA students from LPU can expect to get higher salaries from reputed companies.\n\nMCA students from LPU can also expect to get benefits such as medical insurance, transport allowance, and other perks. These benefits also depend on the company he/she is working for. Apart from salary and benefits, MCA students from LPU can also expect to get other career growth opportunities. Many MCA students from LPU have been able to get promotions or other job opportunities in the IT field.\n\nOverall, the highest package available to an MCA student from LPU is usually in the range of 8-15 lakhs per annum. This package includes salary, bonus, and other benefits. The actual package may also depend on one's qualifications and experience, and the company he/she is working for. However, the highest package available to an MCA student from LPU is usually in the range of 8-15 lakhs per annum.\n\nI hope it helps!\n\nThank you:)",
        "name": "Vidushi Sharma",
        "views": "44 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-highest-package-you-can-get-as-an-MCA-student-from-Lovely-Professional-University-LPU",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Nepal",
        "author": "u/Harild123",
        "question": "China or India for Undergrad?",
        "upvotes": "3",
        "comment": "9",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Nepal/comments/pl0hy9/china_or_india_for_undergrad/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What should I go for MCA or MBA after BSC(IT)?",
        "answer": "Hello There ,\n\nThe choice between an MBA and MCA course will depend on the career goals and preference of a candidate and no one course can be said to be the better between the two. MBA is a better course for candidates who wish to take up leadership roles while MCA is more suitable for candidates who prefer technical roles.\n\nIf you need any kind of assistance regarding admission feel free to contact through Whatsapp . (Link is in bio)\n\nHappy Learning…..",
        "name": "Suraj Late",
        "views": "54 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-should-I-go-for-MCA-or-MBA-after-BSC-IT-1",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "For an online MCA, which one is better in overall benefits, Jain online or Amrita ahead online?",
        "answer": "MCA is a vast program and has wider scope in terms of developing your technical prowess in computer science as well as laying a strong foundation for you to land a lucrative job.\n\nThat is why the Online MCA Program from JAIN Online should be your preferred option because we take you along on your learning journey with 2 years of studying a particular MCA elective separately rather than just include that elective as a part of the curriculum during any of the semesters.\n\nThis opportunity is not available in the MCA program offered by Amrita Online.",
        "name": "JAIN Online",
        "views": "197 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-course-is-easier-an-MCA-or-an-MBA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Which course is easier, an MCA or an MBA?",
        "answer": "The MCA is a three-year advanced post-graduate degree that concentrates on technical elements of software development and the IT sector. The curriculum combines theoretical knowledge with practical experience. Students with an MCA degree have the opportunity to work with technology designs to create apps more quickly and easily.\n\nA wide range of computational theory, programming, network, and database management topics are covered by MCA.\n\nThe MCA program prepares students for a variety of careers, including entry-level jobs like data entry and more specialized ones like web and graphic design.\n\nMBA students learn leadership, management, and academic abilities as part of their PG business administration degree. Additionally, the MBA is a very flexible degree and can help you find employment because areas like finance, accounting, marketing, etc. are relevant to a variety of businesses. Expertise in a variety of fields, including economics, logistics, human resources, communications, etc., are covered in the MBA course.\n\nThe MBA and MCA have rigorous curricula and are both difficult courses. Due to the curriculum's similarity to BCA, MCA will appear to be a simpler course for candidates. In a similar vein, MBA will appear to be a simpler subject following BBA.\n\n(Hope This Will Help You)",
        "name": "College Sakha",
        "views": "227 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-college-is-best-for-MCA-MSc-IT-with-affordable-fees",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are the best BCA colleges in India? How do we get admission in that college?",
        "answer": "Bachelor in Computer Application (BCA) is an undergraduate degree course in computer applications. With the rapid growth of IT industry in India, the demand of computer professional is increasing day by day. This increasing growth of IT industry has created a lot of opportunities for the computer graduates.\n\nBachelor in Computer Application (BCA) is one of the popular courses among the students who want to make their career in the IT (Information Technology) field. The duration of the course is 3 years and divided into 6 semesters. It consists of the subjects like database, networking, data structure, core programming languages like ‘C’ and ‘java’. This course provides a lot of opportunities to the students who are interested in computer field and wants to work in the IT sector as programmer or software developer. To get complete knowledge about the course and career scope, you can go through this article.\n\nEligibility\n\nBefore planning for any examination it is very important to check out some basic but important points. One of the most important point before applying any course is the eligibility. It needs to be checked whether the candidate is eligible for appearing for desired course or not. The students who are interested in BCA as their higher studies must fulfill the following eligibility criteria:\n\nCandidate Should be a citizen of India.\nCandidate must have passed class 12th or senior secondary examination with at least 50% marks including English.\nThe 12th examination must be passed/Appearing with mathematics as a compulsory subject.\nThe minimum age limit is 17 years and the maximum age varies between 22-25 years.\nThe students are generally admitted on the basis of personal interview and written examination conducted by various institutes/universities.\nSome institutes/universities admit student on merit basis.\nThe merit is prepared on the basis of candidate’s performance in the qualifying examination (12th).\n\nScope\n\nThere is a huge scope in the field of BCA. One can do job or can go for higher studies after the completion of course.\n\nSelf employment option is also available. You can do freelancing or develop your own software if you have that much skills. There are many software MNCs (Multi-National Companies) which provide job to the BCA graduates. If the candidate has a work experience and all the necessary required skills then he/she can hold good positions in MNCs.\n\nTop 10 BCA colleges in Rajasthan\n\nBanasthali University, Jaipur. Jaipur, Rajasthan.\nChandigarh University , Jaipur. Jaipur, Rajasthan.\nBirla Institute of Technology (BIT), Jaipur. Jaipur, Rajasthan.\nPacific University, Udaipur\nMewar University, Chittorgarh\nApex University, Jaipur\nJaipur National University, Jaipur\nVivekananda Global University, Jaipur.\n\nBest BCA College in Rajasthan, Punjab, and North India\n\nBCA is a route for the Arts and Commerce students of 10+2 to join the band of computer professionals. The field relates to design, development and use of computer applications. Application, Implies amalgamation of operating system (which runs a computer), a utility (which performs maintenance or general-purpose chores), and a programming language (with which computer programs are created). Thus, BCA students, graduated from Best BCA college in Punjab and India, are able to develop and prepare documents, projects, presentations, design websites and demonstrate skills in running software programs.\n\nComputer applications professionals learn networking, integration, server management, and the use of computers in the business world. They learn software developing, system programming, systems analysis, systems management and project management. They can also pursue master's program in computer applications (MCA) after graduation. Pursue BCA course from the best BCA College in Punjab.\n\nChandigarh University is fully committed to its Institutional Social Responsibility. The University, besides being pioneers in quality education is proactive in uplifting the education standard and qualification of students of the nation in general and North region in particular. CU is enthusiastic to encourage and motivate bright students by providing additional benefits and facilities to shining stars and super achievers.\n\nAs a sequel to this, fresh and impressive scholarship options have been added in the academic year 2020-2021.\n\nCareer Options\n\nGovernment: Many government information technology companies and government like BHEL, NSDL, MTNL and BSNL are hiring BCA graduates.\nPrivate: Several reputed companies like Hindalco, Larson and Turbo, TCS, Wipro, Infosys, are recruiting BCA graduates.\n\nUSPs\n\nHands on learning through Industry Sponsored Laboratories which includes Microsoft Azure Lab, Red Hat Lab, Infor Lab, SAP next-gen lab, Google (Android) Lab.\nUIC was awarded as the best institute by IIT-Bombay(Spoken Tutorial) to enroll their maximum students to attend courses offered by MOOC.\nOption for students to get nano degree or certification through various MOOCs like FOSS, Microsoft LaaS, UiPath RPS, UDEMY, Swayam, NPTEL etc. included as a part of curriculum.\nThe major companies visited the Chandigarh University campus for UIC students’ placements includes- Wipro, NIIT Technologies, Microsoft, Amazon, Deloitte, TCS, IBM, Infosys, Informatica and many more.\nThe UIC Department has filed patents such as QUEEN BELT (followed by AICTE Canada India Acceleration Program at Carleton University, Canada as Young Woman Entrepreneur), HELIUM PAY, LOCK-O-SMART related to social cause.\nDepartment has recently done MoU with M/s Red Hat Academy and MoU with M/S Cloud Computing using Azure Academy where the company has established Red Hat Academy as well as Cloud Computing Using Azure Centre for the students, where they will be able to explore the modern trends being followed in the industry.\nOpportunities for Undergraduate and Post-Graduate students to explore higher education through various semester exchange programs.\nExposure to participate in various Co-Curricular and Extension activities at National and International platforms.\nExposure of National & International Conferences/ Workshop/ Symposium. Till date more than 200 SCOPUS indexed reputed journals are credited under the UIC department.\nBest Entrepreneur facilities are provided through CU-Technology Business Incubator which includes mentorship, Annual Start-up Meet, Investment Summit, IPR & patent support and seed money.\nThere are 4 startups of students of UIC which includes Heavy Décor, Yaaran Di Logistics(YDL Pvt.Ltd), Tulyeko Food Limited, Amalgus Solutions, Waste Paper Recycling.\n\nIndustrial Visits\n\nStudents attending the technical session at Tech Mahindra\nStudents gathered during their Industrial Visit at Solitaire Infosys Pvt. Ltd\nStudents gathered during their Industrial Visit at Eureka Electro soft\nSports Achievements\n\nInter-Club Basketball Championship (Men/Women)-2020\n\nChandigarh University provides a platform for students for extracurricular activities on a regular basis. Chandigarh University organised Inter Club Basketball Championship for both Men and Women category to show their talent. Students from the UIC department also participated in it. One team of girls and two teams of boys took part in the championship.\n\nUIC Women's Basketball team\n\nInter Hostel Military Press Championship (Men/Women)-2020\n\nChandigarh University provides a platform for students for extracurricular activities on a regular basis. Chandigarh University organised Inter Hostel Military Press Championship (Men/Women) for the students living in the hostel to show their talent and strength. Students from the UIC department living in the university hostel also participated in it. Mr. Sourav Biswas won the Gold medal in the championship along with the title of Mr. Strongest Man 2020.\n\nSourav Biswas won gold medal along with Strongest Man Title\n\nUIC Students won medals in the competition.\n\nRink Football League-2020\n\nChandigarh University provides a platform for students for extracurricular activities on a regular basis. Chandigarh University is a place from where students shine in different sports events and make us proud by winning medals at regular intervals. John, studying BCA from UIC department participated in the Rink Football League held at Mumbai, Maharashtra. John was part of Chandigarh University team which won Gold medal in the League.\n\nJohn with the team after winning Gold in League.\n\nAll the best.",
        "name": "Hardik Vashisht",
        "views": "28 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-BCA-colleges-in-India-How-do-we-get-admission-in-that-college",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/brussels",
        "author": "u/teeth_and_tentacles",
        "question": "My application to a master degree in vrije university brussels is not being processed!??",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "18",
        "timestamp": "Past hours",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/brussels/comments/127hefh/my_application_to_a_master_degree_in_vrije/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "How much salary will I get after completing my BCA?",
        "answer": "The salary for a person who has completed a Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) degree can vary based on various factors such as industry, location, job role, and level of experience.\n\nHowever, on average, the starting salary for a BCA graduate in India is around INR 2.5 to 5 lakhs per annum, while in the United States, it can range from $40,000 to $60,000 per annum.\n\nSome popular job roles for BCA graduates include software developer, web developer, database administrator, network administrator, and systems analyst. The salary for these roles can vary depending on the industry and level of experience. For example, a software developer with 1-2 years of experience can earn an average salary of around INR 4 to 6 lakhs per annum in India.\n\nIt is important to note that these are just average figures, and individual salaries can be higher or lower than these based on the aforementioned factors.\n\nAdditionally, it is also important to keep in mind that salaries can increase with experience, skills, and expertise in the field.\n\nThanks.",
        "name": "SID Editz",
        "views": "734 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-much-salary-will-I-get-after-completing-my-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the top BCA colleges in North India?",
        "answer": "I think BCA colleges are to be double-checked before taking admission. BCA has now become a generic course and is not as specified as CSE. BCA is an undergraduate degree that provides a wide spectrum of computers and their applications. To further specialize in this, you need to get an MCA degree to secure better job prospects.\n\nNowadays, students prefer to do engineering in CSE, AI, or MI as these are more futuristic but these courses come with high costs. Therefore, many of them who have a cost constraint but still want to pursue this stream go for the likes of BCA and MICA.\n\nComing back to your question, I have done my BCA from Graphic Era Hill University, which is in Dehradun, Uttarakhand. Personally, I liked my course because of two reasons:\n\n1. The university is renowned for its CSE specialization and since BCA as a course is kind of a younger brother to it, good attention is given to theoretical as well as practical knowledge in our university. The labs are good, the books in the library are up to date, and a lot of experiential learning is given as projects like creating smaller apps, etc.\n\nThe university also provides MCA and most of the faculties are well-educated and have expert knowledge.\n\nAnother factor why I took admitted to GEHU is that I am from Dehradun itself and so I got a 25%. discount on tuition fees which is available for all the domicile students from Uttarakhand or\n\nHimachal Pradesh taking admission in any course in Hill campus\n\nOverall, I would recommend you do thorough research as per your requirements and check out this university in North India.",
        "name": "Anurag Negi",
        "views": "124 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-top-BCA-colleges-in-North-India",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/OrientalSchool2018",
        "author": "u/OrientalSchool2018",
        "question": "BCA - Bachelor in Computer Application",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/OrientalSchool2018/comments/asznwi/bca_bachelor_in_computer_application/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is the future scope of BCA?",
        "answer": "Hello there,\n\nAfter completing your BCA, you are eligible for various entry-level jobs in the IT sector. You can also go for higher studies and pursue an MCA, which will open even more doors to success for you. The BCA degree is an efficient enabler that sets you up for a bright career in terms of jobs.\n\nIf you need any kind of assistance regarding admission feel free to contact through Whatsapp. (Link is in bio)\n\nHappy Learning……….",
        "name": "Suraj Late",
        "views": "72 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-future-scope-of-BCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Which is better, a PGDCA or a MCA to start your career in IT after doing bachelor’s?",
        "answer": "Either you do an MCA or PGDCA, many a thing will depend on your college. So pursue it from a decent level college.",
        "name": "Sunil Kumar Bose",
        "views": "28 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-better-a-PGDCA-or-a-MCA-to-start-your-career-in-IT-after-doing-bachelor-s",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Luxembourg",
        "author": "u/SvenOfAstora",
        "question": "Application to Bachelors in Computer Science at Luxembourg. Need help with the application process.",
        "upvotes": "0",
        "comment": "10",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Luxembourg/comments/u5jvfr/application_to_bachelors_in_computer_science_at/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "What is the average salary of an MCA graduate in India? What are some companies that hire them with high salaries?",
        "answer": "The median salary of MCA graduates in India is INR 7.58 Lakh per annum.\n\nFreshers with an MCA degree earn around INR 1.99 Lakh per annum.\n\nOn the other hand, senior professionals with an MCA degree earn around INR 20 Lakh per annum.\n\nCompanies like\n\nTata Consultancy Services Limited,\n\nCognizant,\n\nHCL Technologies,\n\nAccenture Technology Solutions, and\n\nAccenture are active recruiters hiring MCA graduates",
        "name": "Sonal Toshniwal",
        "views": "715 views",
        "link": "https://brexitbites.quora.com/What-is-it-that-Remainers-find-so-irresistible-about-the-EU-that-they-are-in-favour-of-UK-Laws-being-made-by-people-who",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Is there any scope in BCA and MCA?",
        "answer": "Yes, there is a lot of scope in both BCA (Bachelor of Computer Applications) and MCA (Master of Computer Applications) degrees. The IT industry is constantly evolving and growing, and there is a high demand for skilled professionals in the field of computer applications.\n\nHere are some of the career options and job opportunities available for BCA and MCA graduates:\n\nSoftware Developer: BCA and MCA graduates can work as software developers and develop software applications for different industries.\nWeb Developer: BCA and MCA graduates can work as web developers and design, develop and maintain websites and web applications.\nDatabase Administrator: BCA and MCA graduates can work as database administrators and manage, design, and maintain databases for various organizations.\nNetwork Administrator: BCA and MCA graduates can work as network administrators and manage and maintain computer networks for organizations.\nSystem Analyst: BCA and MCA graduates can work as system analysts and analyze business requirements and recommend technology solutions to meet the requirements.\nIT Consultant: BCA and MCA graduates can work as IT consultants and provide consulting services to organizations on various aspects of IT.\nProject Manager: BCA and MCA graduates can work as project managers and manage IT projects for organizations.\nData Analyst: BCA and MCA graduates can work as data analysts and analyze and interpret data to provide insights to organizations.\n\nIn addition, BCA and MCA graduates can also start their own software development companies or become freelancers and work on projects independently.\n\nOverall, there is a lot of scope and job opportunities in both BCA and MCA degrees, and the demand for skilled professionals in the field of computer applications is expected to grow in the future.",
        "name": "Dipak Singh",
        "views": "15 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-there-any-scope-in-BCA-and-MCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "How can you register a company with two names in India?",
        "answer": "As per Companies Act 2013, a person can't register a company with 2 different names in India. Such a concept is not available in India.\n\nThere is an online process which needs to be followed for name reservation of company i.e.\n\nCheck the availability of proposed company name on the MCA website\nThe Name of the Company should be unique. It should not be same, similar, identical, or resembling the name of the existing Company or LLP Registered. Phonetically similar names are also to be avoided.\nThe Name of the Company should strictly be in accordance with Rule 8 of The Companies Incorporation Rules, 2014.\nMake sure that there is no such trademark already registered with the same name.\nGo to Spice in MCA services and click on new application, proceed further with the application.\nSummary of the objects to be pursued by the company on its incorporation. Write as “THE MAIN OBJECT CLAUSE OF THE COMPANY IS ATTACHED HEREWITH”\nParticulars of the proposed or approved name (There are 2 options given for proposing Names for Name application of a Company) as per the preference to be given one should write names.\nChoose file: The last step for Name reservation of the Company is to browse the attachments to be done; if the name is not registered then only Main Object Clause of the proposed Company is required to be attached.",
        "name": "Dilip Bohra",
        "views": "237 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-better-a-BCA-with-an-MCA-or-a-B-Engineering-B-E-in-CS",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Indian_Academia",
        "author": "u/tiipsindia",
        "question": "Conflicted about MCA Post-BCA: Navigating Entrance Exams & Eligibility Criteria",
        "upvotes": "4",
        "comment": "3",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Indian_Academia/comments/10rjoss/conflicted_about_mca_postbca_navigating_entrance/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Nepal",
        "author": "u/Professional-Stop768",
        "question": "Future suggestion needed",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "5",
        "timestamp": "Past hours",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Nepal/comments/11p9w0p/future_suggestion_needed/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/BennettUniversityedu",
        "author": "u/rohitvermaridge",
        "question": "Best MCA Master of Computer Applications University in India - BU",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/BennettUniversityedu/comments/11yfqmr/best_mca_master_of_computer_applications/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "How are the on campus placements for MCA at USICT, New Delhi?",
        "answer": "Placements for MCA (SE) at USICT have improved drastically. 100+ companies are coming to our college.The highest package this for 2022 session was 44 lpa for Amazon.Two students got selected.One was 18 lpa in one mg and many other like that rest depends upon ur preparation how much good you are at DSA.\n\nThe avg placements 11–12 lpa and highest to I've written already.\n\nSo if u have descent preparation u can grab a good offer from here.",
        "name": "Akansha Khandelwal",
        "views": "5.2K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-the-F-22-and-the-F-35-Why-is-the-F-22-more-expensive",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What is the average day like for an MCA student at IIIT Delhi?",
        "answer": "The average day for an MCA student at IIIT Delhi may vary depending on their academic schedule, extracurricular activities, and personal preferences. However, here's a general overview of what a typical day might look like:\n\nClasses: MCA students usually attend lectures, tutorials, and lab sessions throughout the day. The class timings may vary depending on the course and semester. Usually, the classes start in the morning and end in the evening.\nStudy time: After classes, students usually have some time to study or complete assignments. MCA students need to devote a significant amount of time to self-study to keep up with the coursework.\nGroup activities: MCA students often engage in group activities like project work, presentations, and discussions. These activities may take place during or after classes, depending on the schedule.\nSports and fitness: IIIT Delhi encourages students to participate in sports and fitness activities. Students can use the gym or play outdoor games during their free time.\nCultural and social events: IIIT Delhi organizes various cultural and social events throughout the year. MCA students can participate in these events and showcase their talents.\nRelaxation time: Students need to take breaks and relax to avoid burnout. MCA students can spend their free time socializing with friends, reading books, or pursuing hobbies.\n\nOverall, the life of an MCA student at IIIT Delhi can be busy and demanding, but also exciting and rewarding. Students need to manage their time effectively and balance their academic and personal lives to make the most of their college experience.",
        "name": "Questions Answers",
        "views": "5 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-average-day-like-for-an-MCA-student-at-IIIT-Delhi",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are the career prospects for graduates of the Master of Computer Applications (MCA) program at the Birla Institute of Management Science (BMSC)?",
        "answer": "Master In Computer Application is great course, start salary from BIMSC can fetch closely 1.4Cr to 10Cr depending on experience.",
        "name": "Surya Menon",
        "views": "11 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-prospects-for-graduates-of-the-Master-of-Computer-Applications-MCA-program-at-the-Birla-Institute-of-Management-Science-BMSC",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "What are the cutoff marks for admission into an MCA batch of SRM University Chennai?",
        "answer": "Hello Aspirant,\n\nThe cutoff marks for admission into an MCA batch at SRM University Chennai may vary from year to year, depending on various factors such as the number of candidates applying, the difficulty level of the exam, and the availability of seats. However, based on previous year's cutoff trends, a candidate may need to score around 50-60% marks in the qualifying examination to be eligible for MCA admission at SRM University Chennai. Additionally, candidates may also need to appear for an entrance examination conducted by the university, and the admission decision will be based on the performance in the entrance exam as well as the candidate's academic record. It's recommended to check the official website of SRM University or contact the admission office for the latest information on MCA admission cutoffs and other admission-related queries.\n\nIf it is advisable and informative\n\nplz follow , upvote and share.\n\nThanks",
        "name": "Career Initiative",
        "views": "71 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-cutoff-marks-for-admission-into-an-MCA-batch-of-SRM-University-Chennai",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Is doing BCA worth it? Which are the best colleges for pursuing BCA?",
        "answer": "Hello Aspirant,\n\nYes, pursuing a Bachelor's in Computer Application (BCA) can be worth it if you are interested in computer science and wish to build a career in the IT industry. BCA can prepare you for a range of job roles such as software developer, web developer, system analyst, database administrator, and more.\n\nWhen it comes to the best colleges for pursuing BCA, there are many good options available across India. Here are some of the top colleges for BCA:\n\nChrist University, Bangalore\nLoyola College, Chennai\nSt. Xavier's College, Kolkata\nKristu Jayanti College, Bangalore\nSymbiosis Institute of Computer Studies and Research, Pune\nAmity University, Noida\nInstitute of Management Studies, Ghaziabad\nIndraprastha College for Women, Delhi University\nMount Carmel College, Bangalore\nMadras Christian College, Chennai\n\nHowever, it's important to note that the best college for you depends on factors like your location, budget, academic background, and career goals. So, it's recommended that you research and compare the colleges based on these factors before making a decision. Additionally, consider the accreditation and ranking of the college, faculty expertise, placement opportunities, and overall infrastructure before finalizing a college for BCA.\n\nIf it is advisable and informative\n\nplz follow , upvote and share.\n\nThanks",
        "name": "Career Initiative",
        "views": "232 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-doing-BCA-worth-it-Which-are-the-best-colleges-for-pursuing-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "What are the top colleges for MCA in India?",
        "answer": "Several top MCA colleges in India offer quality education and excellent career opportunities to their graduates. Here are some of the top MCA colleges in India.\n\nNational Institute of Technology (NIT), Trichy: NIT Trichy is a premier engineering college that offers a three-year MCA program. The college has state-of-the-art facilities and an excellent faculty that provides a comprehensive education to its students.\nBirla Institute of Technology (BIT), Mesra: BIT Mesra is a renowned technical institute that offers a three-year MCA program. The college has a strong industry-academia interface and provides excellent placement opportunities to its graduates.\nVellore Institute of Technology (VIT), Vellore: VIT is a reputed engineering college that offers a two-year MCA program. The college has a modern campus and a highly qualified faculty that provides an excellent education to its students.\nDepartment of Computer Science, University of Delhi: The University of Delhi is a prestigious university that offers a two-year MCA program through its Department of Computer Science. The college has a strong research focus and provides excellent opportunities for research and internships.\nJawaharlal Nehru University (JNU), New Delhi: JNU is a renowned university that offers a two-year MCA program through its School of Computer and Systems Sciences. The college has a highly qualified faculty and a strong research focus.\nChrist University, Bangalore: Christ University is a private university that offers a two-year MCA program. The college has a modern campus and a highly qualified faculty that provides an excellent education to its students.\nInternational Institute of Information Technology (IIIT), Hyderabad: IIIT Hyderabad is a premier technical institute that offers a two-year MCA program. The college has a strong focus on research and innovation and provides excellent opportunities for internships and placements.\nSymbiosis Institute of Computer Studies and Research (SICSR), Pune: SICSR is a well-known institute that offers a two-year MCA program. The college has a modern campus and a highly qualified faculty that provides an excellent education to its students.\nMadras Christian College (MCC), Chennai: MCC is a prestigious college that offers a two-year MCA program. The college has a strong focus on research and provides excellent opportunities for internships and placements.\nUniversity of Hyderabad: The University of Hyderabad is a renowned university that offers a two-year MCA program. The college has a strong research focus and provides excellent opportunities for research and internships.\nNarsee Monjee Institute of Management Studies (NMIMS), Mumbai: NMIMS is a reputed institute that offers a two-year MCA program. The college has a modern campus and provides excellent opportunities for internships and placements.\nPSG College of Technology, Coimbatore: PSG College of Technology is a well-known technical institute that offers a three-year MCA program. The college has a highly qualified faculty and provides excellent opportunities for internships and placements.\nInstitute of Engineering and Management (IEM), Kolkata: IEM is a well-known institute that offers a two-year MCA program. The college has a modern campus and provides excellent opportunities for internships and placements.\nUniversity of Mumbai: The University of Mumbai is a renowned university that offers a three-year MCA program. The college has a highly qualified faculty and provides excellent opportunities for research and internships.\nManipal Academy of Higher Education (MAHE), Manipal: MAHE is a premier university that offers a two-year MCA program. The college has a modern campus and provides excellent opportunities for internships and placements.\nAmity University, Noida: Amity University is a private university that offers a two-year MCA program. The college has a highly qualified faculty and provides excellent opportunities for internships and placements.\nLovely Professional University (LPU), Jalandhar: LPU is a well-known university that offers a two-year MCA program. The college has a modern campus and provides excellent opportunities for internships and placements.\nBharathiar University, Coimbatore: Bharathiar University is a renowned university that offers a two-year MCA program. The college has a highly qualified faculty and provides excellent opportunities for research and internships.",
        "name": "Aniket Sharma",
        "views": "14 views",
        "link": "https://collegeforum.quora.com/What-are-the-top-colleges-for-MCA-in-India-1",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/Oulu",
        "author": "u/aquvvv",
        "question": "Job market for a master student in computer science and engineering from University of Oulu after graduation",
        "upvotes": "5",
        "comment": "11",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/Oulu/comments/128yh6m/job_market_for_a_master_student_in_computer/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Which has the better scope, an MCA or an MSc in data science?",
        "answer": "Both MCA (Master of Computer Applications) and MSc (Master of Science) in Data Science have good career prospects, depending on your interests and career goals.\n\nMCA focuses on computer applications and programming skills, along with some business management and software development courses. Graduates with an MCA degree can find job opportunities in software development, IT consulting, system administration, and other areas of computer science.\n\nOn the other hand, an MSc in Data Science focuses specifically on data analysis, machine learning, and statistical modeling, among other data-related fields. Graduates with an MSc in Data Science can find job opportunities in data analysis, data engineering, data science, and other data-related fields.\n\nIn terms of scope, both fields have a high demand for skilled professionals, and the demand is expected to increase in the coming years. Ultimately, the better option depends on your interests and career goals, as both fields have their unique strengths and opportunities.",
        "name": "Puneett Bhatnagr",
        "views": "25 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-has-the-better-scope-an-MCA-or-an-MSc-in-data-science",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Is it possible for a fresher to become the CEO of Tata Consultancy Services (TCS)?",
        "answer": "Lets take an example of N Chandra, who was the CEO f TCS and now the chairman of entire Tata group.\n\nHe is from a small tamil medium school in his hometown. He earned his Master of Computer Applications (MCA) from the Regional Engineering College, Tiruchirappalli (now National Institute of Technology, Tiruchirappalli).\n\nJoining TCS in 1987,AS a fresher, Chandrasekaran took over as CEO on 6 October 2009.\n\nIf Chandra can attain CEO level after starting as an MCA fresher in TCS in approximately 22 years, so can anyone",
        "name": "Prosenjit Paul",
        "views": "42.7K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-possible-for-a-fresher-to-become-the-CEO-of-Tata-Consultancy-Services-TCS",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/MeetPeople",
        "author": "u/chaoticquantaa",
        "question": "22 [M4F][Chat] India/Anywhere - An INFJ and Demi guy looking for someone to connect with as a whole",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/MeetPeople/comments/10boy9y/22_m4fchat_indiaanywhere_an_infj_and_demi_guy/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "twitter",
        "name": "chalocampus",
        "handle": "@chalocampus",
        "timestamp": "Jun 3, 2009",
        "text": "AIMS NEW DELHI BCA ADMISSIONS 2009: Bachelor Degree(BCA)2009 Admissions in Computer Application at Asia-Pacific .. http://tinyurl.com/qjhcld",
        "link": "https://twitter.com/chalocampus/status/2014649907",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "Which college is best for an online BCA, Manipal Online University or LPU Online University?",
        "answer": "Hello reader,\n\nI hope you are doing well,\n\nBCA (Bachelor of Computer Applications) is a popular undergraduate program in the field of computer science. It is a three-year degree program that aims to provide students with a strong foundation in computer science, programming languages, database management, web development, and other related areas.\n\nLPU (Lovely Professional University) offers a fully online BCA program for students who are unable to attend traditional on-campus classes. The online program is designed to provide students with the same high-quality education as the on-campus program, with the added flexibility of being able to study from anywhere in the world.\n\nThe online BCA program at LPU is a comprehensive program that covers a wide range of topics in computer science. Students will learn about programming languages such as C++, Java, and Python, as well as web development languages such as HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. They will also learn about database management, data structures, computer networks, and software engineering.\n\nThe program is delivered entirely online, using a variety of digital tools and resources to support student learning. These include online lectures, video tutorials, interactive quizzes, and discussion forums. Students are also able to access course materials and assignments through a dedicated online learning platform.\n\nOne of the key benefits of studying the BCA program online at LPU is the flexibility it offers. Students are able to study at their own pace, and can choose to complete the program in as little as three years or take longer if needed. This makes it an ideal option for working professionals or students who have other commitments.\n\nIn summary, the online BCA program at LPU is a comprehensive and flexible program that provides students with a strong foundation in computer science. With its focus on practical skills and the use of digital tools, it prepares students for a wide range of careers in the technology industry.\n\nYou can refer tot the following link for more details,\n\nBachelor of Computer Application(BCA) Online Distance Education Course Fees\nB.Com acts as a gateway to a career in commerce, finance, accounting, banking and insurance. Students also consider the course while preparing for Chartered Accountancy, Cost Accounting and Company Secretaryship.\nhttps://www.lpuonline.com/bachelor-of-computer-application-course-online.php\n\nI hope the information shared by me was helpful to you!\n\nThank you:)",
        "name": "Vidushi Sharma",
        "views": "16 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Which-college-is-best-for-an-online-BCA-Manipal-Online-University-or-LPU-Online-University",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "question": "Can I get a direct second year admission to a BCA after completing a diploma in computer engineering?",
        "answer": "Yes, it is possible to get direct second-year admission to a Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) program after completing a diploma in computer engineering. This is known as lateral entry admission, and it allows diploma holders to directly enter the second year of the BCA program.\n\nThe eligibility criteria for lateral entry admission may vary depending on the university or college offering the BCA program. In general, you will need to have completed a three-year diploma in computer engineering or a related field with a minimum percentage of marks as specified by the university. You may also be required to pass an entrance exam or meet other admission requirements set by the university.\n\nIf you are interested in pursuing a BCA program through lateral entry admission, you should contact me here — Aman Agarwal",
        "name": "Aman Agarwal",
        "views": "283 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-get-a-direct-second-year-admission-to-a-BCA-after-completing-a-diploma-in-computer-engineering",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/QuantumComputing",
        "author": "u/Taiyou04",
        "question": "Are there legit industry jobs in the quantum computing field?",
        "upvotes": "14",
        "comment": "7",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/QuantumComputing/comments/10mrgfv/are_there_legit_industry_jobs_in_the_quantum/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/careerguidance",
        "author": "u/mukhijaparth",
        "question": "Masters in Economics or social science after Computer science in Bachelors?",
        "upvotes": "3",
        "comment": "1",
        "timestamp": "Past day",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/careerguidance/comments/ib673u/masters_in_economics_or_social_science_after/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "How is a BCA in Jain University, Bangalore?",
        "answer": "Jain University Bangalore offers a Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) program that is well-regarded for its quality education, experienced faculty, and overall development opportunities for students. Here are some key aspects to consider when evaluating the BCA program at Jain University Bangalore:\n\nCurriculum: Jain University's BCA program has a comprehensive curriculum that covers essential subjects such as programming languages, data structures, algorithms, computer networks, and database management systems. The curriculum is designed to provide students with both theoretical and practical knowledge, enabling them to become competent professionals in the field.\nFaculty: Jain University boasts a team of experienced and knowledgeable faculty members who are dedicated to providing quality education to their students. The faculty's expertise and commitment to student success help create a conducive learning environment.\nInfrastructure: The university has state-of-the-art infrastructure, including well-equipped computer labs, libraries, and modern classrooms. These facilities enable students to access the latest technology and resources, which is crucial for a successful learning experience in a BCA program.\nIndustry Exposure: Jain University emphasizes industry exposure, providing students with opportunities to participate in internships, live projects, and workshops. This practical experience helps students gain valuable insights into the industry and enhances their employability.\nExtracurricular Activities: The university encourages students to participate in various clubs, committees, and events, which helps them develop essential soft skills and fosters a sense of community. Engaging in these activities allows BCA students to gain a holistic education.\nPlacement Assistance: Jain University has a dedicated placement cell that assists students in securing job opportunities in well-reputed companies. While placement assistance may vary depending on the job market and individual performance, the university's focus on industry exposure and skill development aims to enhance students' employability.\n\nIn conclusion, a BCA from Jain University Bangalore can be a rewarding educational experience, given its comprehensive curriculum, experienced faculty, modern infrastructure, and focus on practical learning. However, it is essential to consider your career goals, interests, and personal preferences when making a decision about pursuing a BCA at Jain University.",
        "name": "Devi Prasad",
        "views": "15 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-is-a-BCA-in-Jain-University-Bangalore",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/PE_Exam",
        "author": "u/Humorous_Artist",
        "question": "Total Number of Professional Engineering References for an Applicant with an Accredited Master and Bachelor Degrees in Engineering",
        "upvotes": "3",
        "comment": "6",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/PE_Exam/comments/1281suj/total_number_of_professional_engineering/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/getadmision",
        "author": "u/getadmision",
        "question": "Why BCA becomes so important for our new generation Kids…",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/getadmision/comments/z3hxlh/why_bca_becomes_so_important_for_our_new/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/sanjanasbm",
        "author": "u/sanjanasbm",
        "question": "Best master of computer application colleges in mumbai | Top MCA College",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/sanjanasbm/comments/vozbv4/best_master_of_computer_application_colleges_in/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "How good will be the lovely professional university for BCA?",
        "answer": "The university offers a Bachelor of Computer Application (BCA) program, which is a 3-year undergraduate degree program that provides students with a strong foundation in computer science and prepares them for a career in the technology industry.\n\nThe BCA program at LPU covers a range of subjects, including programming languages, computer networks, data structures and algorithms, software engineering, database management, artificial intelligence, and computer graphics. The program also includes practical training and projects to help students develop real-world skills and experience.\n\nSalient features of the course are Projects, Contemporary Curriculum, Interdisciplinary Minors, Industrial Visits, Holistic Development, Professional Enhancement, Software Skills, Industry Immersion,\n\nStudents have instant access to the latest technology labs like iMac, SAP, etc. BCA Course at LPU is designed to build programming skills for developing efficient and resource-optimized software, website, cloud, mobile applications. The students are prepared on topics like Programming languages, hardware, and software, computer networks, World Wide Web, Database Management, Logic, Multimedia etc.",
        "name": "Vishnu Harry",
        "views": "126 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-good-will-be-the-lovely-professional-university-for-BCA",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/digiomg",
        "author": "u/Responsible-Dealer21",
        "question": "Best BCA College List 28+ All Over India: Best college for Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) in India. Top BCA Government Colleges/Universities in India and Best private colleges for Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) in India.",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/digiomg/comments/utnni0/best_bca_college_list_28_all_over_india_best/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/gsbcollege",
        "author": "u/gsbcollege",
        "question": "Best BCA Colleges in Indore (Bachelor of Computer Applications)",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/gsbcollege/comments/127inn6/best_bca_colleges_in_indore_bachelor_of_computer/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/OntarioGrade12s",
        "author": "u/Maleficent-Risk2240",
        "question": "McMaster Computer Science Supplementary Application Interview Tips",
        "upvotes": "8",
        "comment": "6",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/OntarioGrade12s/comments/10i90wu/mcmaster_computer_science_supplementary/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/ITCareerQuestions",
        "author": "u/Ecstatic-Title3982",
        "question": "Certification for someone who has Bachelors in Computer Applications?",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "2",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/ITCareerQuestions/comments/o8c36i/certification_for_someone_who_has_bachelors_in/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Is it true that MCA has very low value compared to MBA?",
        "answer": "No, MCA is very interesting and better than MBA as, After completing MCA degree online one can assure that this course will open different doors to the big IT companies. I would like to list some of the highly paid jobs after doing MCA online.\n\nThere are so many jobs and specializations after completing MCA degree online, some of them are: Data base engineer, senior software engineer, data scientist, web developer and many more.\n\nThere are so many universities offering MCA online course, but I would recommend MANAV RACHNA UNIVERSITY, as it is one of the topmost universities in India, it assures the placement of the students. The faculty of Manav Rachna is highly experienced in IT field. Manav Rachna provides:\n\n24/7 student support\n\nSeamless e-learning\n\n100 plus hiring partners\n\nHands on learning experience\n\nBuilding of portfolio with industry projects, etc.\n\nCentre for Distance and Online Education\nHome 1 June 19, 2021 2023-03-09 12:24 Home 1\nhttps://manavrachnaonline.com/mca/?utm_source=stu&utm_medium=promo&utm_campaign=28",
        "name": "Nishant Jawa",
        "views": "583 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-worth-doing-a-MCA-after-a-BCA",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past week",
        "question": "How is ABES Ghaziabad for mca?",
        "answer": "ABES Ghaziabad is renowned for providing high-quality instruction in a number of subjects, including Master of Computer Applications (MCA). The following are some elements that make ABES Ghaziabad an excellent choice for MCA study:\n\nFaculty: The MCA faculty at ABES Ghaziabad is extremely skilled and knowledgeable, with the majority of them possessing Ph.D.s. They are committed to giving you a solid academic basis in computer science and applications, as well as practical skills.\n\nCurriculum: You will receive a solid foundation in computer science, programming, and software development as part of the ABES MCA curriculum. The program offers a variety of core classes, electives, and project work that allow students to have a thorough understanding of a number of computer science specialties.\n\nInfrastructure: ABES Ghaziabad features a contemporary campus with computer labs, classrooms, and a library that are all well stocked. The university has made investments in cutting-edge facilities and infrastructure, creating a supportive atmosphere for learning.\n\nPlacements: The ABES Ghaziabad campus has a dedicated placement cell that strives to place you in reputable firms like TCS, Wipro, Infosys, Capgemini, etc. The placement rates of ABES Ghaziabad's MCA graduates in various IT firms are generally good.\n\nIn general, ABES Ghaziabad is a decent university for MCA study. It has a team of faculty members who are highly qualified, has modern facilities, and a successful placement rate. Hence, ABES is a good university to pursue MCA.",
        "name": "Mayank Sharma",
        "views": "2 views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/How-is-ABES-Ghaziabad-for-mca",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "quora",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "question": "Why are people still joining TCS, Infosys, Wipro, Accenture and several other IT companies or any other private companies when they have understood that even a tea stall owner or Ola drivers earn more than them?",
        "answer": "This is a pretty stupid question if you ask.\n\nMy driver used to get 22 thousands in 2014. One of my cousin who worked in Infosys started his career at 20 thousands in same year. My cousin earnt half of what an established momo business would make and pretty less than my driver.\n\nAfter 5 years, my driver got 25 thousands and my brother who started his career in IT was earning 96 thousands in-hand. Not to forget the Health-insurance, family insurance, PF, retirement benefits, allowances and all other amenities which comes with it.\n\nIt's true that IT employees start with very low salary but if you look at Vice-presidents, Head of HRs, Head of Operations they earn way more. .\n\nLesson : You can never compare a professional with small business owners.\n\nN Chandrasekaran ~ Chairman of Tata Group\n\nNot an IITian/ IIM graduate. He started as a graduate trainee in TCS after completing his MCA from NIT, Trichy. He did not had an engineering degree or a full time MBA degree. Even if some chai-wala, momo maker happened to earn more than him when he stared his career, I can never compare them both - Before or After",
        "name": "Salman Haider",
        "views": "381.1K views",
        "link": "https://www.quora.com/What-is-better-preparing-for-SSC-CGL-or-preparing-for-NIMCET-MCA-during-my-BCA-My-financial-condition-is-not-well",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/KRMANGALMUNIVERSITY",
        "author": "u/Grand-Garage-6479",
        "question": "Mca colleges in gurgaon (Master of computer application)",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/KRMANGALMUNIVERSITY/comments/uh9pgi/mca_colleges_in_gurgaon_master_of_computer/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "r/mumbai",
        "author": "u/Harsh00077",
        "question": "College's for MCA (Master's in Computer Application)",
        "upvotes": "6",
        "comment": "7",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/r/mumbai/comments/z2z6on/colleges_for_mca_masters_in_computer_application/",
        "searchType": "mca"
    },
    {
        "type": "reddit",
        "group": "u/contaicollegeoflearn",
        "author": "u/contaicollegeoflearn",
        "question": "Best Bachelor in Computer Application | CCLMS",
        "upvotes": "1",
        "comment": "0",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "link": "https://www.reddit.com/user/contaicollegeoflearn/comments/m2jg8o/best_bachelor_in_computer_application_cclms/",
        "searchType": "bca"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/TEqeo_GflAA",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA Degree is Worth it in 2023 or Not ? | We have to do BCA in 2023 or not ?"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/UtNqNpp7iZw",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA Subjects Explain in Hindi | BCA Complete Syllabus in Hindi | By Sunil Adhikari"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/6fsGjcMHmXQ",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "How to do Online BCA ? || Online BCA Kaise kare? || Guru Chakachak"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/N1J9n9o66BM",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "💥BCA vs B.Sc CS! Which is Better? | B.Sc Computer Science Vs BCA! Admissions 2023 #bca #bsccs"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/mxLs5WmAA_A",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA COURSE DETAILS IN HINDI | BCA COURSE KYA HOTA HAI | FEES | ADMISSION 2023 | SYLLABUS"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/7e-bBvd4yb0",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA+MCA Vs BTech"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/jnFQYobdN34",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "💥BCA vs B.Sc IT! Best for Career? B.Sc Information Technology Vs BCA Admissions 2023 #bca #bscIT"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/XTnd3XKxEpo",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "HOW I SELECTED IN WIPRO | Full Story From BCA To Wipro Fresher | Story Of BCA Student From BCA To .."
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/--_oGSFxjsA",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "What is BCA? – All about BCA | Jobs | Salary | Complete Information [Hindi]"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/zyF1mtH3LPA",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA IP University 2023:Entrance exam Syllabus Pattern Admission Process🔥Complete Details"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/undefined",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "💥BCA + MCA Dual Degree by CUET 2023! Ek Saath 2 Degrees! #cuet #cuet2023 #cuetexam #cuetcolleges"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/YcPHylAsLAk",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "Career after BCA ? BCA करने के बाद Jobs Options #career_after_bca"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/wxq3Jd1z3P4",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "Which Degree is Right for You ? | BBA Vs BCA"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/aXGevHfNFh4",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA from LPU | LPU BCA total Cost of Studying | Fees | Admission | Placements | LPUNEST EXAM Tips"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/eoXrp9IWwRM",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "My 2 Year Experience In BCA Course | Reality Of BCA | Miss Khushi Vlogs |"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/uRfHvQddqnI",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "MSL 8 - ZARKAWT BCA vs MISSION VENG HOTSHOTS"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/U7cdJ6gI45M",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "💥CUET 2023 BCA + MCA Dual Degree! Ek Saath 2 Degree! CUET Colleges for Integrated Course #cuet2023"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/LCOTUOVq440",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "MSL8 - Zarkawt BCA vs Bungkawn LB ASSOCIATES"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/undefined",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA Student Raushan Arya Sharing Experiences and Learnings of Workshop at IIT BHU, Varanasi"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/undefined",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past month",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "💥What is CUET Exam 2023? BCA Entrance Exam CUET 2023! #cuet #cuet2023 #shorts #youtubeshorts"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/R2uj7sdhZXQ",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "💥Salary After BCA? 10-12 Lakhs Expectation🤩 BCA Students Interview Sushant University #bca #bcajobs"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/TEqeo_GflAA",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA Degree is Worth it in 2023 or Not ? | We have to do BCA in 2023 or not ?"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/Lcie1QiDQOc",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "5 Reasons Why I Hate BCA | BCA in 2023"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/pmZISkX2yp8",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "What is BCA course?|Best college's for BCA in India|Career and Salary after BCA|Placement after BCA"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/uSzbiGEu3yc",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "JOB Reality after BCA | Bca course Reality in India | Don’t waste your money and time."
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/fKhUjHZGlZU",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA के बाद जॉब ही नहीं मिलता | What Is BCA | Job After BCA | Best Career Option After BCA |"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/9B9RQUms1qo",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA करने से पहले सच्चाई जान लें | Best Career Options After 12th for Science Commerce Arts| #BCA"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/CXrhDQRWawU",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "My 2 year Experience of Bachelor's In Computer Application ( BCA ) ~ A Dark Truth | BCA KA BANDA"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/gMk185F4MSg",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "Should You Do BCA in 2023? BCA Reality! | BCA Roadmap, Is BCA Worth Doing?"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/UtNqNpp7iZw",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA Subjects Explain in Hindi | BCA Complete Syllabus in Hindi | By Sunil Adhikari"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/KfSuTYbVMa4",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "He got TCS in BCA and cracked Amazon with 45LPA after MCA"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/iVCtBOahHFg",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA in India to working at Amazon in USA full journey with 100% scholarship| Amazon campus USA"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/jwATjhVzmHE",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "My BCA Story || Reality of BCA"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/undefined",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA Kya Hota Hai #BCA #softwareengineer #India #Shorts #Salary"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/TnbEkRrK3w4",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "💥Why BCA in 2023? Dream Company of BCA Students? 🤩 We Asked BCA Students of Sushant University!"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/12HFuAvDWAQ",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA after Commerce | B.Arch after Commerce | BCA BArch Course Details"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/N1J9n9o66BM",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "💥BCA vs B.Sc CS! Which is Better? | B.Sc Computer Science Vs BCA! Admissions 2023 #bca #bsccs"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/undefined",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "💥Benefits of Doing BCA! 🤩 BCA Jobs and Careers! #shorts #youtubeshorts #bca #bcajobs"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/undefined",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "💥5 Mistakes BCA Students Must Avoid💥 Helpful for Good BCA Career! #shorts #youtubeshorts #bca"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/mxLs5WmAA_A",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA COURSE DETAILS IN HINDI | BCA COURSE KYA HOTA HAI | FEES | ADMISSION 2023 | SYLLABUS"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/e91hGbJ1AuY&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "All about BCA | Jobs | Packages | Best Colleges"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/NprOJfgm3hM&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "What is BCA? – [Full Information] – [Hindi]– Quick Support"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/R2uj7sdhZXQ&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "💥Salary After BCA? 10-12 Lakhs Expectation🤩 BCA Students Interview Sushant University #bca #bcajobs"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/K4fcgZjmEz8&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA Course full information in Gujarati | Bachelor of Computer Application |"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/AHluBQ1G0DU&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA kya hai | BCA full form | BCA ke fayde | BCA course fees | बीसीए पूरी जानकारी | BCA in Hindi |"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/TEqeo_GflAA&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "2 weeks ago",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA Degree is Worth it in 2023 or Not ? | We have to do BCA in 2023 or not ?"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/sAlxN59cwXA&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "10 Career Options after BCA in 2022"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/kLFpsMcrWug&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA COURSE DETAIL | SALARY AFTER BCA | After 12th BCA Information | Scope of BCA in India [HINDI]"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/2i8Q5T3FFZw&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "Three Years Of My Bachelors In Computer Application • BCA Course • In Hindi"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/Lcie1QiDQOc&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "5 Reasons Why I Hate BCA | BCA in 2023"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/30Knz9ZPYng&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "ये 5 Best Computer Courses जीवन बदल देंगी ! | After 10th & 12th | सबसे अधिक Salary"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/R_CHevwoLbY&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA Freshers Reveals Shocking Reality of BCA 😱| Bachelor of Computer Applications | BCA का BANDA"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/-ysh7nNtbGw&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA करने से पहले जान लो | After 12th BCA | Bachelor of Computer Application | Abhishek Chaudhary"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/8M0xAm0vwN4&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "Government jobs after BCA | jobs after BCA | career options after BCA | what to do after BCA | bca"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/uSzbiGEu3yc&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "JOB Reality after BCA | Bca course Reality in India | Don’t waste your money and time."
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/2knsFRSvF_Q&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "Benefits of B.C.A Course – [Hindi] – Quick Support"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/fKhUjHZGlZU&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA के बाद जॉब ही नहीं मिलता | What Is BCA | Job After BCA | Best Career Option After BCA |"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/XTnd3XKxEpo&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "2 weeks ago",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "HOW I SELECTED IN WIPRO | Full Story From BCA To Wipro Fresher | Story Of BCA Student From BCA To .."
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/LD5gd2-BpvA&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "Lodge repeat as BCA U19 champs"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/gMk185F4MSg&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "Should You Do BCA in 2023? BCA Reality! | BCA Roadmap, Is BCA Worth Doing?"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/CXrhDQRWawU&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "My 2 year Experience of Bachelor's In Computer Application ( BCA ) ~ A Dark Truth | BCA KA BANDA"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/9aRNQGWyr-U&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA Course full details in Tamil | Best course after 12th | Career Guidance | Salary | Tamil"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/9B9RQUms1qo&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA करने से पहले सच्चाई जान लें | Best Career Options After 12th for Science Commerce Arts| #BCA"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/UA3D06qU_XE&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "MBA kya hai kaise kare in Hindi | MBA Full Form | MBA Karne ke Fayde | MBA Course in Hindi |"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/dj99NjeqqCs&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BBA subjects | BBA subjects in India | Bachelors of Business Administration | BBA Course Subjects"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/z1usTlstJZw&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "What is B.Tech with Full Information? – [Hindi] – Quick Support"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/EX1m8i1_ddc&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA कैसे करें? || What is BCA course || Full Information in Hindi"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/lt3KDbZLa44&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA course details in hindi, Salary, Jobs and Admission | By G Study"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/KfSuTYbVMa4&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past months",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "He got TCS in BCA and cracked Amazon with 45LPA after MCA"
    },
    {
        "embedUrl": "https://youtube.com/embed/DcofJBQXV48&pp",
        "type": "youtube",
        "timestamp": "Past year",
        "searchType": "bca",
        "title": "BCA Subjects list All Semester | BCA Syllabus | BCA में कौन-कौन से सब्जेक्ट होते हैं?"
    }
]